<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Jobs - Libyanjobs</title>
	<atom:link href="https://libyanjobs.ly/jobs/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://libyanjobs.ly</link>
	<description>Libyan Job Site</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 12:46:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://media.libyanjobs.ly/uploads/2021/02/cropped-Jobs_Fav-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Jobs - Libyanjobs</title>
	<link>https://libyanjobs.ly</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Data Processing Assistant</title>
		<link>https://libyanjobs.ly/jobs/data-processing-assistant/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[International Organization for Migration (IOM)]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 12:46:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://libyanjobs.ly/?post_type=noo_job&#038;p=279656</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Position Title : Data Processing Assistant Duty Station : Tripoli, Libya Classification :  G4 Type of Appointment : Special Short Term, 9 Months with possibility of extension Estimated Start Date : As soon as possible Under the direct supervision of the Migration Health Officer (Emergencies) with the overall guidance from the Migration health Coordinator, the incumbent will be responsible for</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly/jobs/data-processing-assistant/">Data Processing Assistant</a> first appeared on <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly">Libyanjobs</a>.</p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Position Title</strong> : Data Processing Assistant<br />
<strong>Duty Station</strong> : Tripoli, Libya<br />
<strong>Classification</strong> :  G4<br />
<strong>Type of Appointment</strong> : Special Short Term, 9 Months with possibility of<br />
extension<br />
<strong>Estimated Start Date</strong> : As soon as possible</p>
<p>Under the direct supervision of the Migration Health Officer (Emergencies) with the overall guidance<br />
from the Migration health Coordinator, the incumbent will be responsible for management of data<br />
collection, transmission, analysis and storage to support Migration Health Unit activities.</p>
<p><strong>Core Functions / Responsibilities:</strong></p>
<p>1. Help to Maintain IT network and equipment in IOM Libya MHD H1.<br />
2. Registration of bio-data for all pre-screening medical forms<br />
3. Provides technical support to the medical staff including troubleshooting, software and<br />
hardware installation with the guidance of the senior IT.<br />
4. Help to design under the supervision of the senior IT queries from the Medical information<br />
system and produces reports, both regular and ad-hoc.<br />
5. Establishes and implements internal document controls, in particular handling, security,<br />
confidentiality of medical information in process.<br />
6. Contact beneficiaries and schedule the intended activities of programs like Medical<br />
assessments, Follow up and Pre-departure activities.<br />
7. Receives medical requests/forms from the OBE, keeps the forms and copy and record of the<br />
same, and transmits the completed forms to respected entities as directed.                                                8. Prepares Medical Forms as per programs and intended activities, Daily Schedules for<br />
Counseling, Laboratory and Radiology, Appointment Letters, Laboratory Codes; Chest x-ray<br />
labels and any other necessary list as per request of the Project Management.<br />
9. Managing PAC system, troubleshooting and direct communication with IOM Manila Telerad<br />
for CXR reports and follow up on monthly reports and invoices. In Addition to provide<br />
training to staff on related matters.<br />
10. Ensures accurate and timely transmission of data and information to IOM Operations and<br />
partners as required by the Project Management<br />
11. Support the Migration Health Officer on duties and tasks assigned to the Data Processing,<br />
Analysis and IT Applications Sub-Unit<br />
12. Files incoming/outgoing letters, memoranda, E-mails, telefaxes, as well as IOM documents<br />
and forms related to IOM medical operational matters.<br />
13. Follow up the needed requirements for invoices preparations/ validations with the respective<br />
staff to different programs and any other specification like the Canadian program and internal<br />
data base MiMOSA monitoring and validation.<br />
14. Follow ethics and confidentiality rules to safeguard the interests of the applicants and IOM.<br />
15. Performs any other duties that may be assigned from time to time.</p>
<p><strong>Required Qualifications and Experience</strong><br />
<strong>Education</strong><br />
• University degree or equitant in information management, business administration or other<br />
relevant field supplemented by related courses will be advantage, with two years of relevant<br />
professional experience.<br />
• Diploma/Secondary school education supplemented by courses in related fields, with<br />
four years of relevant professional experience.</p>
<p><strong>Experience</strong><br />
• Knowledge in SQL development, database integration with web-based application, power BI<br />
Experience and understanding of the public health industry.<br />
• Demonstrated skills in systems analysis techniques, testing and documentation.<br />
• Previous work experience in international organizations and companies would be an<br />
advantage.</p>
<p><strong>Skills</strong><br />
• Effective organizational skills and ability to establish priorities and plans, ability to work<br />
under pressure and cope with deadlines;<br />
• Good written and spoken communications skills, good interpersonal skills, ability to work in<br />
a multi-cultural environment;<br />
<strong>Languages</strong><br />
• Fluency in English and Arabic (oral and written).<br />
• Knowledge of French is an advantage.</p>
<p><strong>Required Competencies</strong><br />
<strong>Values</strong><br />
• Inclusion and respect for diversity: respects and promotes individual and cultural<br />
differences; encourages diversity and inclusion wherever possible.<br />
• Integrity and transparency: maintain high ethical standards and acts in a manner<br />
consistent with organizational principles/rules and standards of conduct.<br />
• Professionalism: demonstrates ability to work in a composed, competent and committed<br />
manner and exercises careful judgment in meeting day-to-day challenges.</p>
<p><strong>Core Competencies – behavioural indicators level 1</strong><br />
• Teamwork: develops and promotes effective collaboration within and across units to<br />
achieve shared goals and optimize results.<br />
• Delivering results: produces and delivers quality results in a service-oriented and timely<br />
manner; is action oriented and committed to achieving agreed outcomes.<br />
• Managing and sharing knowledge: continuously seeks to learn, share knowledge and<br />
innovate.<br />
• Accountability: takes ownership for achieving the Organization’s priorities and assumes<br />
responsibility for own action and delegated work.<br />
• Communication: encourages and contributes to clear and open communication; explains<br />
complex matters in an informative, inspiring and motivational way.</p>
<p><strong>Other</strong><br />
Any offer made to the candidate in relation to this vacancy notice is subject to funding confirmation.<br />
Appointment will be subject to certification that the candidate is medically fit for appointment and<br />
verification of residency, visa and authorizations by the concerned Government, where applicable.<br />
Only candidates residing in either the country of the duty station or from a location in a neighbouring<br />
country that is within commuting distance of the duty station will be considered. In all cases, a<br />
prerequisite for taking up the position is legal residency in the country of the duty station, or in the<br />
neighbouring country located within commuting distance, and work permit, as applicable.</p>
<p><strong>How to apply:</strong><br />
Interested candidates are invited to submit their updated CV with a cover letter to<br />
<strong>hrdlibya@iom.int</strong>, by <strong>13 July 2022</strong> at the latest, mentioning the job title in the subject line<br />
along with this special vacancy notice code <strong>SVN.LY10.2022.09</strong><br />
Emails without such indication will not be considered.<br />
Only shortlisted candidates will be contacted.</p>
<p><strong>Posting period:</strong><br />
From 07.07.2022 to 13.07.2022</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p><p>The post <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly/jobs/data-processing-assistant/">Data Processing Assistant</a> first appeared on <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly">Libyanjobs</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
				<company>International Organization for Migration (IOM)</company>
		<job_address>Libya</job_address>
		<job_category>organization</job_category>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Human Resources Assistant, UNOPS LICA-5 Contract, Duty Station &#8211; Tripoli, WHO Libya Country Office</title>
		<link>https://libyanjobs.ly/jobs/human-resources-assistant-unops-lica-5-contract-duty-station-tripoli-who-libya-country-office/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[WHO Country Office Libya]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 11:31:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://libyanjobs.ly/?post_type=noo_job&#038;p=279647</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>For Libyan nationals only. If you meet the requirements below (education and years of relevant work experience) please follow the instructions &#8216;How to apply&#8217; below. &#160; Objectives of the Programme  To ensure that effective WHO country presence is established to implement WHO country cooperation strategies that are aligned with Member State’s health and development agendas, and harmonized with the United</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly/jobs/human-resources-assistant-unops-lica-5-contract-duty-station-tripoli-who-libya-country-office/">Human Resources Assistant, UNOPS LICA-5 Contract, Duty Station – Tripoli, WHO Libya Country Office</a> first appeared on <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly">Libyanjobs</a>.</p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="text-decoration: underline"><em>For Libyan nationals only. If you meet the requirements below (education and years of relevant work experience) please follow the instructions &#8216;How to apply&#8217; below.</em></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Objectives of the Programme </strong></p>
<p>To ensure that effective WHO country presence is established to implement WHO country cooperation strategies that are aligned with Member State’s health and development agendas, and harmonized with the United Nations Country Teams.</p>
<p><strong>Organizational Context </strong></p>
<p>Under the supervision of the Human Resources Officer and general guidance of Operations Officer, the work is performed in a typical office environment. The HR Assistant is a team member; work is assigned by the supervisor who gives instructions on non-routine matters. Routine tasks are performed independently with some discretion in non-routine matters related to office procedures only. Established procedural and office guidelines are available. Some interpretation may be required and the incumbent may need to select an approach to work where precedents do not exist.</p>
<p><strong>Summary of Assigned Duties</strong></p>
<p>The incumbent will perform the following duties:<br />
1. Type post descriptions and forms required for establishment of new positions, update organization charts, initiate related position actions in GSM and liaise with HR Unit and the Global Service Center finalization of newly established positions and recruitment of professional staff.<br />
2. Administer the recruitment of staff and non staff, publish vacancy announcements, screen applicants, and finalize necessary arrangements for tests/interviews, conduct reference checks and initiate necessary appointment actions, finalize contractual arrangements for Special Service Agreements (SSAs), Consultants and Agreements for performance of work (APWs) through the procurement module.<br />
3. Monitor expiration of all types of staff and non staff contracts; initiate extensions, separations and other staffing actions in GSM; attach necessary documents, check availability of funds, and follow up with different stakeholders timely finalization of actions<br />
4. Administer the attendance system and GSM absence dashboard, update and maintain leave records for staff and non-staff (SSA holders, consultants, etc.), including:<br />
• verifying leaves claimed in GSM against the records of the Time and Attendance system, alert staff in case of any discrepancy and inform supervisors of excess leaves/absence;<br />
• submitting leave requests on behalf of absent staff members, and following up with staff to ensure<br />
confirmation of leaves in GSM;<br />
• responding to staff queries related to leave system and coordinating with Global Service Centre (GSC) and Human Resources (HR) to solve any related issues.<br />
5. Follow up with concerned units/stakeholders on necessary arrangements regarding, travel, visas, residency permits, security clearances, travel authorizations, UN ID’s, hotel bookings for staff and non-staff.<br />
6. Update and maintain HR confidential files (electronic and hard copies), including performance appraisal records, ensure confidentiality, and provide related statistical information and reports as and when necessary, follow up with staff and non-staff the timely submission of Performance Management reports.<br />
7. Liaise with Staff Development and Learning unit the induction and training of staff and non staff at country office and sub-offices and ensure its timely completion. Brief staff and non staff on HR related rules/procedures and the use of GSM staff service module.<br />
8. Perform any other duties as required, and replace other administrative staff when and if requested.</p>
<p><strong>WHO Competencies:</strong></p>
<p>1) Setting an example<br />
2) Producing results<br />
3) Communicating in a credible and effective way<br />
4) Moving forward in a changing environment<br />
5) Fostering integration and teamwork</p>
<p><strong>Functional Skills and Knowledge:</strong><br />
− Demonstrated knowledge and application of human resources management policies and procedures.<br />
− Very good time management and stress management skills.<br />
− Very good analytical skills.<br />
− Good knowledge of WHO/UN procedures and HR practices as applicable to the administrative level an asset.</p>
<p><strong>Education (Qualifications):</strong><br />
Essential: Completion of secondary education supplemented by administrative training.<br />
Desirable: University degree in business administration, social sciences or related field is an asset.</p>
<p><strong>Experience:</strong><br />
Essential: At least five years’ progressive experience in the area of administration, including experience in HR management.</p>
<p>Desirable: Relevant experience in the UN system.</p>
<p><strong>Languages:</strong><br />
Fluent knowledge of English and Arabic language.</p>
<p>Duration &#8211; initially until 31 December 2022 with possibility of extension (subject of availability of funds, satisfactory performance, continuous need for service)</p>
<p><strong>How To Apply:</strong></p>
<p><em><span style="text-decoration: underline">DULY COMPLETED CV/RESUME SHOULD BE SENT WAITH A COVER LETTER TO THE FOLLOWING ADDRESS &#8211; EMACOLIYHR@WHO.INT  </span></em></p>
<p><em><span style="text-decoration: underline">CV/Resume should indicate clearly candidate&#8217;s education, professional work experience, employment date, employer, full/part-time employment where applicable, employment dates should not overlap, description of duties and responsibilities.</span></em></p>
<p><em><span style="text-decoration: underline">PLEASE REFFER TO THE POSITION TITLE IN YOUR APPLICATION EMAIL. </span></em></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h3></h3><p>The post <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly/jobs/human-resources-assistant-unops-lica-5-contract-duty-station-tripoli-who-libya-country-office/">Human Resources Assistant, UNOPS LICA-5 Contract, Duty Station – Tripoli, WHO Libya Country Office</a> first appeared on <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly">Libyanjobs</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
				<company>WHO Country Office Libya</company>
		<job_address>Tripoli - Libya</job_address>
		<job_category>Human Resources,HUMAN RESOURCES</job_category>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Customer Service Agent</title>
		<link>https://libyanjobs.ly/jobs/customer-service-agent-2/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Crown Airlines]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 09:56:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://libyanjobs.ly/?post_type=noo_job&#038;p=279609</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Employment: Full Time Department: Sales &#8211; Commercial Department Reports To: Chief Commercial Officer &#160; &#160; Duties and Responsibilities Makes and confirms booking actions at request of customers in accordance with the company rules and procedures. Answer queries about product, rates, prepare invoices outlining terms and conditions in accordance with the company terms and conditions. Performs multiple functions related to customer</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly/jobs/customer-service-agent-2/">Customer Service Agent</a> first appeared on <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly">Libyanjobs</a>.</p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Employment: Full Time</p>
<p>Department: Sales &#8211; Commercial Department</p>
<p>Reports To: Chief Commercial Officer</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Duties and Responsibilities</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Makes and confirms booking actions at request of customers in accordance with the company rules and procedures. Answer queries about product, rates, prepare invoices outlining terms and conditions in accordance with the company terms and conditions.</li>
<li>Performs multiple functions related to customer services, at all times selling and marketing the products and services offered by the company.</li>
<li>Multi-task and handle pressure situations in a fast-paced environment per business requirements and accept roster/shift duty in different areas as assigned by the reporting line manager.</li>
<li>Persuade, influence, convince and impress clients in a way that results in favored preference for the company.</li>
<li>Ensure that clients are truly and genuinely cared for, and best service levels and customer handling/servicing are delivered on a consistent basis.</li>
<li>Writing to or calling clients to help resolve issues or inform them of any changes or communicate any relevant information in a timely and concise manner.</li>
<li>Ensure all incoming calls are converted into a sales transaction and always up selling to increase company revenues at every sales opportunity.</li>
<li>Preparing daily sales report and ensuring with finance that all transactions are closed accurately and accounted for, per company procedures.</li>
<li>Working closely with other departments to ensure up to date status of operations and ensuring that information available at all touch point are current.</li>
</ul>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Requirements</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Excellent command In English and Arabic (Speaking, Reading, Writing). Proficiency in other languages (French/Italian) would be an advantage.</li>
<li>High school diploma or equivalent, Bachelor’s or college degree preferred.</li>
<li>At least 22 years of age at the time of joining and maximum age of 32.</li>
<li>Excellent presentation and interpersonal skills, presentable and well-groomed appearance.</li>
<li>Ability to communicate effectively and behave both professionally and respectfully, with sense of setting priorities and taking initiatives.</li>
<li>Strong computer and internet skills, including Microsoft Application Skills (Word, Excel, PPT ,Outlook etc.).</li>
<li>Fast &amp; efficient typing skills.</li>
<li>Service oriented with ability to quickly gain knowledge of the company products, systems, and procedures.</li>
<li>Sales oriented and able to achieve targets.</li>
<li>Ability to work in shifts and roster basis including on weekends, at different locations or functions as required by the company.</li>
<li>Ability to work independently and also a part of a team</li>
</ul>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Send your Resume to the below email:</p>
<p>recruitment@flycrown.aero</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p><p>The post <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly/jobs/customer-service-agent-2/">Customer Service Agent</a> first appeared on <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly">Libyanjobs</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
				<company>Crown Airlines</company>
		<job_address>Libya</job_address>
		<job_category>Other,Not Classified</job_category>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>مهندس مساح</title>
		<link>https://libyanjobs.ly/jobs/%d9%85%d9%87%d9%86%d8%af%d8%b3-%d9%85%d8%b3%d8%a7%d8%ad/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Almustathmir Aldaym co]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 08:52:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://libyanjobs.ly/?post_type=noo_job&#038;p=279598</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>تعلن شركة المستثمر الدائم للمقاولات والاستثمار العقاري عن رغبتها بتوظيف مهندس مساح حاصل على مؤهل بكالوريوس هندسة مدنية او ما يعادلها ويفضل خبرة في مجال الاعمال المساحية مع شركات المقاولات. بوظيفة ( مهندس مساحة ) بخبرة عملية لا تقل عن ثلاث سنوات و تتركز مهامه وشروط الوظيفة في الآتي : &#160; أن يجيد اللغة الانجليزية بمستوى متوسط (قراءة ،كتابة ،</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly/jobs/%d9%85%d9%87%d9%86%d8%af%d8%b3-%d9%85%d8%b3%d8%a7%d8%ad/">مهندس مساح</a> first appeared on <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly">Libyanjobs</a>.</p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>تعلن شركة المستثمر الدائم للمقاولات والاستثمار العقاري عن رغبتها بتوظيف مهندس مساح حاصل على مؤهل بكالوريوس هندسة مدنية او ما يعادلها ويفضل خبرة في مجال الاعمال المساحية مع شركات المقاولات.</p>
<p>بوظيفة ( مهندس مساحة ) بخبرة عملية لا تقل عن ثلاث سنوات و تتركز مهامه وشروط الوظيفة في الآتي :</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>أن يجيد اللغة الانجليزية بمستوى متوسط (قراءة ،كتابة ، محادثة)</p>
<p>مهارة جيدة في إستخدام برنامج الميكروسوفت اوفس (وورد، اكسيل، باوربوينت،&#8230;.)</p>
<p>القدرة على استخدام برنامج الاتوكاد بمستوى جيد جداً.</p>
<p>المهارة في استعمال أجهزة المساحة المختلفة في الموقع والمتمثلة في : Theodolites &#8211; Total Station</p>
<p>المهارة العالية في استخدام جهاز الميزان (Level Survey) من حيث أخذ القراءات والمناسيب</p>
<p>إعداد الرسومات والإسكتشات والتصاميم</p>
<p>اعمال الرفع المساحي في الموقع واعادة تنزيل النقاط حسب الرسومات التنفيذية</p>
<p>اعداد الخرائط والرسم الكروكي ومراجعة المناسيب التصميمية</p>
<p>إعداد العمليات الحسابية للبيانات المساحية واستخراج النتائج</p>
<p>اعمال حصر كميات جميع البنود بجدول الكمياتB.O.Q</p>
<p>الالتزام والجدية والدقة وسرعة الإنجاز و بأعلى جودة</p>
<p>الاحتفاظ بنسخة لكل مستندات المشروع والأرشفة الإلكترونية</p>
<p>أن يكون متفرغ للعمل من الساعة 8:00 صباحاً وحتى الساعة 5:00 مساءاً (العمل في وقت إضافي في حال تطلب الأمر)</p>
<p>العمل تحت ضغط وضمن فريق عمل واحد</p>
<p>تنفيذ أي مهام أخرى لها علاقة بالوظيفة</p>
<p>على من يأنس في نفسه القدرة على شغل هذه الوظيفة يرجى التواصل معنا عبر البريد الإلكتروني التالي: arms1979r@gmail.com و ارفاق نسخة للإيميل : salimlibya80@gmail.com  برسالة معنونة (مهندس مساح)  في مدة لا تتجاوز اسبوع من تاريخ الاعلان , وسوف يتم فرز السير الذاتية وتحديد موعد للمقابلة الشخصية في خلال شهر من تاريخ الإعلان .</p>
<p>عنوان الشركة : الفرناج / طرابلس-ليبيا.</p><p>The post <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly/jobs/%d9%85%d9%87%d9%86%d8%af%d8%b3-%d9%85%d8%b3%d8%a7%d8%ad/">مهندس مساح</a> first appeared on <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly">Libyanjobs</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
				<company>Almustathmir Aldaym co</company>
		<job_address>Libya</job_address>
		<job_category>Civil Engineering</job_category>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Head of Developers</title>
		<link>https://libyanjobs.ly/jobs/head-of-developers-2/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[شركة بكم للخدمات المالية الإلكترونية]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 08:51:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://libyanjobs.ly/?post_type=noo_job&#038;p=279595</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Advertise company becom for financial and electronic services recruitment of director of development department Duties and responsibilities Develop technical aspects of the company’s strategy to ensure alignment with its business goals Discover and implement new technologies that yield competitive advantage Supervise system infrastructure to ensure functionality and efficiency Build quality assurance and data protection processes Monitor KPIs and IT budgets</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly/jobs/head-of-developers-2/">Head of Developers</a> first appeared on <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly">Libyanjobs</a>.</p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span class="Y2IQFc" lang="en">Advertise company becom for financial and electronic services recruitment of director of development department</span></p>
<p><strong>Duties and responsibilities</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Develop technical aspects of the company’s strategy to ensure alignment with its business goals</li>
<li>Discover and implement new technologies that yield competitive advantage</li>
<li>Supervise system infrastructure to ensure functionality and efficiency</li>
<li>Build quality assurance and data protection processes</li>
<li>Monitor KPIs and IT budgets to assess technological performance</li>
<li>Use stakeholders’ feedback to inform necessary improvements and adjustments to technology</li>
<li>Communicate technology strategy to partners and investors</li>
<li>Work with developers to design algorithms and flowcharts</li>
<li>Work with developers to design and manage projects’ scrums and sprints.</li>
<li>Produce clean, efficient and documented code based on specifications</li>
<li>Integrate software components and third-party programs</li>
<li>Verify and deploy programs and systems</li>
<li>Troubleshoot, debug and upgrade existing software</li>
<li>Gather and evaluate user feedback</li>
<li>Recommend and execute improvements</li>
<li>Create technical documentation for reference and reporting</li>
</ul>
<p><strong><u>Skills and qualifications</u></strong></p>
<ul>
<li>BSc/BA in Computer Science, Engineering or a related field</li>
<li>A minimum of 5-year experience in development &amp; management.</li>
<li>Good experience with (back-end &amp; front-end) in one of these web programming languages: (PHP, Python, C#, C++, JavaScript, node.JS or Java SE&amp;EE) and frameworks/systems (e.g. AngularJS, Git).</li>
<li>Good experience in dealing with database such as MSSQL or MySQL.</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li>Comprehension of algebra concepts to apply to data and to generate reports.</li>
<li>Ability to work under pressure to meet deadlines, handle multiple tasks and set priorities.</li>
<li>Willingness to work independently or with a team.</li>
<li>Analytical skills when creating computer code.</li>
<li>Attention to detail.</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li>Proven experience as a Software Developer, Software Engineer or similar role</li>
<li>Familiarity with Agile development methodologies</li>
<li>Experience with software design and development in a test-driven environment</li>
<li>Ability to learn new languages and technologies</li>
<li>Excellent communication skills</li>
<li>Resourcefulness and troubleshooting aptitude.</li>
</ul>
<p id="tw-target-text" class="tw-data-text tw-text-large tw-ta" dir="ltr" data-placeholder="Translation"><span class="Y2IQFc" lang="en">Please send your CV to the e-mail : recruiment@becom.ly</span></p>
<p dir="ltr" data-placeholder="Translation">We are working every day from Sunday to Thursday.</p>
<p dir="ltr" data-placeholder="Translation">Time from 08:30 AM to 04:30 PM.</p><p>The post <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly/jobs/head-of-developers-2/">Head of Developers</a> first appeared on <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly">Libyanjobs</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
				<company>شركة بكم للخدمات المالية الإلكترونية</company>
		<job_address>Al Shat Road - Tripoli - Libya</job_address>
		<job_category>Sales</job_category>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>موظف مبيعات</title>
		<link>https://libyanjobs.ly/jobs/%d9%85%d9%88%d8%b8%d9%81-%d9%85%d8%a8%d9%8a%d8%b9%d8%a7%d8%aa-7/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[شركة بكم للخدمات المالية الإلكترونية]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 08:29:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://libyanjobs.ly/?post_type=noo_job&#038;p=279592</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>تعلن شركة بكم للخدمات المالية الالكترونية عن رغبتها توظيف موظف /  مبيعات /  بمدينة بنغازى واجبات ومسؤوليات مندوب المبيعات • كن على دراية بالمنتج • تنظيم فرق التوزيعات جغرافيا • متابعة الديون مع فريق التوزيعات • تعيين وتدريب موظفي التوزيع • تحديد العملاء المحتملين وتوليد العملاء المحتملين والتحويل • الاتصال بالعملاء الحاليين والجدد لمناقشة الاحتياجات • التأكيد على ميزات المنتجات</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly/jobs/%d9%85%d9%88%d8%b8%d9%81-%d9%85%d8%a8%d9%8a%d8%b9%d8%a7%d8%aa-7/">موظف مبيعات</a> first appeared on <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly">Libyanjobs</a>.</p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: right">تعلن شركة بكم للخدمات المالية الالكترونية عن رغبتها توظيف موظف /  مبيعات /  بمدينة بنغازى</p>
<pre id="tw-target-text" class="tw-data-text tw-text-large tw-ta" dir="rtl" data-placeholder="Translation"><span class="Y2IQFc" lang="ar">واجبات ومسؤوليات مندوب المبيعات
• كن على دراية بالمنتج
• تنظيم فرق التوزيعات جغرافيا
• متابعة الديون مع فريق التوزيعات
• تعيين وتدريب موظفي التوزيع
• تحديد العملاء المحتملين وتوليد العملاء المحتملين والتحويل
• الاتصال بالعملاء الحاليين والجدد لمناقشة الاحتياجات
• التأكيد على ميزات المنتجات لتسليط الضوء على كيفية حلها لمشاكل العملاء
• أجب عن الأسئلة المتعلقة بالمنتجات
• التفاوض على الأسعار والشروط وإعداد اتفاقيات البيع
• التعاون مع الزملاء في العديد من القطاعات المختلفة
• الحفاظ على قوائم الاتصال والمتابعة مع العملاء لمواصلة العلاقات

مهارات ومؤهلات
• مهارات خدمة العملاء للاستماع إلى مخاوف العملاء والقدرة على تلبية احتياجاتهم
• مهارات التعامل مع الآخرين للعمل مع مجموعة متنوعة من الأشخاص كل يوم ، وبناء العلاقات والشبكات
• الثقة والاطمئنان القوي للنجاح في الاتصال البارد للعملاء وإجراء عملية بيع
• مهارات الاتصال ، وخاصة الإقناع ، لنقل مزايا المنتج بوضوح إلى العملاء المحتملين
• التحمل البدني ، حيث قد يحتاج موظف المبيعات إلى الوقوف على أقدامه لساعات طويلة ، وقضاء الكثير من الوقت في التنقل بين المواقع وحمل المنتجات الثقيلة

متطلبات العمل:
              
•	</span>دبلوم عالى او بكلوريس<span class="Y2IQFc" lang="ar">.
• خبرة لا تقل عن 1 سنة في المبيعات.</span></pre>
<p style="text-align: right">.بدوام كامل من 08:30 م الى 04:30 م على ان لا يقل عمر المتقدم 26 &#8211; متحصل على شهادة دبلوم عالى فما فوق</p>
<p style="text-align: right">دوام العمل من الاحد الى الخميس</p>
<p style="text-align: right"> recruiment@becom.ly :لن يتم الاطلاع على السيرة الذاتية بدون كتابة عنوان الايميل على المتقدمين ارسال السيرة الذاتية على الايميل</p>
<p style="text-align: right">المرسل ( مبيعات )</p><p>The post <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly/jobs/%d9%85%d9%88%d8%b8%d9%81-%d9%85%d8%a8%d9%8a%d8%b9%d8%a7%d8%aa-7/">موظف مبيعات</a> first appeared on <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly">Libyanjobs</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
				<company>شركة بكم للخدمات المالية الإلكترونية</company>
		<job_address>Al Shat Road - Tripoli - Libya</job_address>
		<job_category>Sales and Customer Service</job_category>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Project Specialist</title>
		<link>https://libyanjobs.ly/jobs/project-specialist-27957009/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 05:27:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://libyanjobs.ly/?post_type=noo_job&#038;p=279570</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Project Specialist Tripoli (LBY), Libya Job Identification 3744 Locations Tripoli (LBY), Libya Posting Date 07/06/2022, 09:59 AM Apply Before 07/20/2022, 05:59 AM Job Schedule Full time Agency UNDP Grade P3 Vacancy Type Fixed Term Practice Area Conflict Prevention, Peacebuilding and Responsive Institutions Bureau Regional Bureau for Arab States Contract Duration 1 Year with Possibility for extension Education &#38; Work Experience</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly/jobs/project-specialist-27957009/">Project Specialist</a> first appeared on <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly">Libyanjobs</a>.</p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div id="job" class="job ss-container" data-bind="scrollable, adjustToCustomHeader: { 'calc-height': ['min-height','height'] }, setBodyScrollTo: {  to: 0, device: 'isSmall' }">
<div class="ss-wrapper">
<div class="ss-content">
<div class="job-elements-wrapper">
<div class="header-row" dir="ltr" data-bind="i18nLang: job().lang">
<div class="job-title-container">
<h3 class="job-title" style="text-align: left;"><span data-bind="text: job().title">Project Specialist</span></h3>
</div>
<div class="locations txt-overflow icon-location-pin" style="text-align: left;"><span class="primary-location" data-bind="text: job().primaryLocation">Tripoli (LBY), Libya</span></div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="tiles-and-summary-wrapper" dir="ltr" style="text-align: left;" data-bind="i18nLang: job().lang">
<div id="short-info-items-list" class="job-details-summary">
<div class="job-details-list">
<div class="job-info-wrapper">
<div class="job-info-labels"><span class="job-info-label" data-bind="text: name">Job Identification</span></div>
<div class="job-info-values"><span class="job-info-value" data-bind="text: value">3744</span></div>
</div>
<div class="job-info-wrapper">
<div class="job-info-labels"><span class="job-info-label" data-bind="text: name">Locations</span></div>
<ul class="job-info-values">
<li class="job-info-value" data-bind="text: $data">Tripoli (LBY), Libya</li>
</ul>
</div>
<div class="job-info-wrapper">
<div class="job-info-labels"><span class="job-info-label" data-bind="text: name">Posting Date</span></div>
<div class="job-info-values"><span class="job-info-value" data-bind="text: value">07/06/2022, 09:59 AM</span></div>
</div>
<div class="job-info-wrapper">
<div class="job-info-labels"><span class="job-info-label" data-bind="text: name">Apply Before</span></div>
<div class="job-info-values"><span class="job-info-value" data-bind="text: value">07/20/2022, 05:59 AM</span></div>
</div>
<div class="job-info-wrapper">
<div class="job-info-labels"><span class="job-info-label" data-bind="text: name">Job Schedule</span></div>
<div class="job-info-values"><span class="job-info-value" data-bind="text: value">Full time</span></div>
</div>
<div class="job-info-wrapper">
<div class="job-info-labels"><span class="job-info-label" data-bind="text: name">Agency</span></div>
<div class="job-info-values"><span class="job-info-value" data-bind="text: value">UNDP</span></div>
</div>
<div class="job-info-wrapper">
<div class="job-info-labels"><span class="job-info-label" data-bind="text: name">Grade</span></div>
<div class="job-info-values"><span class="job-info-value" data-bind="text: value">P3</span></div>
</div>
<div class="job-info-wrapper">
<div class="job-info-labels"><span class="job-info-label" data-bind="text: name">Vacancy Type</span></div>
<div class="job-info-values"><span class="job-info-value" data-bind="text: value">Fixed Term</span></div>
</div>
<div class="job-info-wrapper">
<div class="job-info-labels"><span class="job-info-label" data-bind="text: name">Practice Area</span></div>
<div class="job-info-values"><span class="job-info-value" data-bind="text: value">Conflict Prevention, Peacebuilding and Responsive Institutions</span></div>
</div>
<div class="job-info-wrapper">
<div class="job-info-labels"><span class="job-info-label" data-bind="text: name">Bureau</span></div>
<div class="job-info-values"><span class="job-info-value" data-bind="text: value">Regional Bureau for Arab States</span></div>
</div>
<div class="job-info-wrapper">
<div class="job-info-labels"><span class="job-info-label" data-bind="text: name">Contract Duration</span></div>
<div class="job-info-values"><span class="job-info-value" data-bind="text: value">1 Year with Possibility for extension</span></div>
</div>
<div class="job-info-wrapper">
<div class="job-info-labels"><span class="job-info-label" data-bind="text: name">Education &amp; Work Experience</span></div>
<div class="job-info-values"><span class="job-info-value" data-bind="text: value">Master&#8217;s Degree &#8211; 5 year(s) experience</span></div>
</div>
<div class="job-info-wrapper">
<div class="job-info-labels"><span class="job-info-label" data-bind="text: name">Required Languages</span></div>
<div class="job-info-values"><span class="job-info-value" data-bind="text: value">English</span></div>
</div>
<div class="job-info-wrapper">
<div class="job-info-labels"><span class="job-info-label" data-bind="text: name">Desired Languages</span></div>
<div class="job-info-values"><span class="job-info-value" data-bind="text: value">Arabic</span></div>
</div>
<div class="job-info-wrapper">
<div class="job-info-labels"><span class="job-info-label" data-bind="text: name">Vacancy Timeline</span></div>
<div class="job-info-values"><span class="job-info-value" data-bind="text: value">2 Weeks</span></div>
</div>
<div class="job-info-wrapper">
<div class="job-info-labels"><span class="job-info-label" data-bind="text: name">Mobility required/no mobility</span></div>
<div class="job-info-values"><span class="job-info-value" data-bind="text: value">mobility required</span></div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="info oj-flex oj-flex-items-pad oj-sm-flex-direction-column" dir="ltr" style="text-align: left;" data-bind="i18nLang: job().lang">
<div class="details">
<h2 class="job-description-header" data-bind="i18n: 'job-details.job-description-title'">Job Description</h2>
<div class="job-description" data-bind="html: job().description">
<p>UNDP is committed to achieving workforce diversity in terms of gender, nationality and culture. Individuals from minority groups, indigenous groups and persons with disabilities are equally encouraged to apply. All applications will be treated with the strictest confidence.</p>
<p>UNDP does not tolerate sexual exploitation and abuse, any kind of harassment, including sexual harassment, and discrimination. All selected candidates will, therefore, undergo rigorous reference and background checks.</p>
<p><strong>BACKGROUND</strong></p>
<p>UNDP is working rapidly to respond to the crisis in Libya by undertaking projects to help stabilize the country and instill trust and confidence amongst communities, and between communities and the government. The UNDP Libya Country Office (CO) has made strong commitments to international donors and its Libyan counterparts to help restore and improve public services; enhance the effectiveness and reach of existing public institutions; expand civic engagement and participation in political and development processes; increase economic opportunities in a more diversified economy; strengthen social cohesion, reconciliation and transitional justice initiatives; and contribute to stability throughout the country to ensure development gains.</p>
<p>“Strengthening Local Capacities for Resilience and Recovery” (SLCRR)  is a multi-year and multi- phase action funded by the EU aiming at supporting local authorities in Libya to respond to the many conflict and human mobility induced challenges that impact negatively people’s access to essential services, sustainable livelihoods, social cohesion and community security.</p>
<p>The overall objective of the project is to contribute to improving the living conditions and resilience of vulnerable populations (including migrants, refugees, IDPs, returnees and host communities) in selected municipalities and communities across Libya.</p>
<p>The project is built around three specific objectives:</p>
<ul>
<li>Strengthening responsiveness of local institutions in delivering essential public services to crisis-affected populations and in leading recovery processes;</li>
<li>Enhancing communities and local stakeholders’ capacity to improve social cohesion and community security;</li>
<li>Strengthening economic opportunities for youth and vulnerable groups (including women) through inclusive and participatory local economic recovery.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Position Purpose:</strong></p>
<p>The Project Specialist will support on a daily basis the effective and efficient management of the project as outlined below.</p>
<p><strong>DUTIES &amp; RESPONSIBILITIES</strong></p>
<p><strong>Contributing to the strategic direction of project operations aligned with Country Office (CO) and corporate Operations policies and guidelines:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Ensures that the project is in full compliance of operations with UNDP rules, regulations and policies, implementation of corporate operational strategies, establishment of targets and monitoring achievement of results.</li>
<li>Successfully manages project operational support by provision of advice on strategies, policies and plans affecting project operations based on business principles.</li>
<li>Ensures the application of the CO internal Standard Operating Procedures (SOPs) in Finance, Human Resources Management, Procurement, Administrative services and Results Management.</li>
<li>Sets and monitors targets for Project operational efficiency and ensures the constant monitoring and analysis of the Project operating environment.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Contributing to financial resources management, personnel management, fast, efficient and compliant inputs and procedures for procurement and logistics:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Preparation of qualitative annual work plans;</li>
<li>Proper project planning, expenditures tracking, reporting and audit of financial resources in accordance with UNDP and donor rules and regulations,</li>
<li>Works in coordination with CO MSU to ensure proper management and accounting.</li>
<li>Oversight of timely accounting and reconciliation of all project transactions.</li>
<li>Routinely monitors financial exception reports for unusual activities, transactions, and investigates anomalies or unusual transactions.</li>
<li>Ensures the financial integrity of the project through appropriate controls and reporting structures; works in coordination with CO MSU for efficient and effective DIM project audit exercises, as well as donor verifications.</li>
<li>Oversight of timely recruitment processes in accordance with UNDP rules and regulations, and appropriate use of different contractual modalities.</li>
<li>Project adherence with UNDP rules and regulations for its submissions to the Operations Unit to ensure quality management of the project procurement processes for the supply of goods, works and services, customer relationship management, and introduction of performance measurement.</li>
<li>Ensures efficient and effective implementation of project contract strategy including overall oversight of tendering processes and evaluation, managing the contract and contractor.</li>
<li>Oversight of procurement processes and logistical services, in accordance with UNDP rules and regulations.</li>
<li>Oversight of programmatic processes for the engagement of partners and responsible parties, in accordance with UNDP rules and regulations.</li>
<li>Management of project assets ensuring full compliance with IPSAS in the accounting for procurement, utilization and disposal of the project assets.</li>
<li>Assume responsibility for the practical coordination of infrastructure rehabilitation, provision of livelihoods and social cohesion activities in order to meet expected results, as required by the PM.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Contributing to strategic communication, building partnerships for successful project implementation as well as resource mobilization efforts:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Contribute to the preparation of corporate and donor reports.</li>
<li>Synthesis of lessons learned and best practices from the project to feed into project contribution to ROAR, Annual Reports, and other documents as required.</li>
<li>Maintains close coordination with assigned project partners, helping at ensuring synergies and avoiding overlaps in project implementation.</li>
<li>Contribute to the wide dissemination and visibility of project achievements.</li>
<li>Support to the resource mobilizations efforts, in collaboration with the PM and the Resource Mobilization and Partnership Specialist.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Contributing to knowledge sharing and capacity building through results-based management strategies:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Document lessons learned and best practices in the area of community stabilization, local development and resilience.</li>
<li>Promote a knowledge sharing and learning culture among project staff and other implementing partners at all levels.</li>
<li>Evaluation of the project impact. Monitoring and analysis of the project environment, timely readjustments in project implementation.</li>
<li>Provide any  necessary support in coaching, guidance for the project staff that will boost their capacity to deliver.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Supervisory/Managerial Responsibilities:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>The Project Specialist will work in close coordination with the Project Associates, Project Coordinators, Project M&amp;E team and Comms Analyst.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>RECRUITMENT QUALIFICATIONS</strong></p>
<p><strong>Education</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Advanced university degree (Master’s Degree) or in International Studies, International Relations, Political Sciences, Social Sciences, International Development, Economics or in a related field. Candidates with master studies in other fields might be qualified depending on their relevant work experience</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Experience</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Minimum of 5 years of progressively responsible experience at the international level related to project management and/or project management support.</li>
<li>At least 2 years of relevant working experience in project operations and financial management</li>
<li>Prior experience with UN agencies, preferably with UNDP, and/or other international organizations including international NGOs</li>
<li>Proven experience in result-based management.</li>
<li>Working experience of in crisis and post-conflict countries.</li>
<li>Experience in working, liaising and collaborating with local authorities, international organizations, private sector and civil society organizations.</li>
<li>Experience in the areas of stabilization, resilience and recovery including provision of basic services, livelihoods and social cohesion/reconciliation activities is a strong asset.</li>
<li>Prior experience working in or managing EU funded projects is an asset.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Language Requirements</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Fluency in English.</li>
<li>Arabic is an asset.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Female candidates are strongly encouraged to apply</strong></p>
<p><strong>COMPETENCIES</strong></p>
<p><strong>Core Competencies</strong></p>
<p><strong>Achieve Results: </strong>LEVEL 3: Set and align challenging, achievable objectives for multiple projects, have lasting impact</p>
<p><strong>Think Innovatively: </strong>LEVEL 3: Proactively mitigate potential risks, develop new ideas to solve complex problems</p>
<p><strong>Learn Continuously: </strong>LEVEL 3: Create and act on opportunities to expand horizons, diversify experiences</p>
<p><strong>Adapt with Agility: </strong>LEVEL 3: Proactively initiate and champion change, manage multiple competing demands</p>
<p><strong>Act with Determination: </strong>LEVEL 3: Think beyond immediate task/barriers and take action to achieve greater results</p>
<p><strong>Engage and Partner: </strong>LEVEL 3: Political savvy, navigate complex landscape, champion inter-agency collaboration</p>
<p><strong>Enable Diversity and Inclusion: </strong>LEVEL 3: Appreciate benefits of diverse workforce and champion inclusivity</p>
<p><strong>Cross-Functional &amp; Technical competencies:</strong></p>
<p><strong>Business Management &#8211; Project Management: </strong>Ability to plan, organize, priorities and control resources, procedures and protocols to achieve specific goals</p>
<p><strong>Business Management &#8211; Portfolio Management: </strong>Ability to select, priorities and control the organizations programmes and projects, in line with its strategic objectives and capacity; ability to balance the implementation of change initiatives and the maintenance of business-as-usual, while optimizing return on investment</p>
<p><strong>Business Management &#8211; Partnerships Management</strong>: Ability to build and maintain partnerships with wide networks of stakeholders, Governments, civil society and private sector partners, experts and others in line with UNDP strategy and policies</p>
<p><strong>Business Management &#8211; Resource Management: </strong>Ability to allocate and use resources in a strategic or tactical way in line with principles of accountability and integrity</p>
<p><strong>Business Direction &amp; Strategy &#8211; Effective Decision Making: </strong>Ability to take decisions in a timely and efficient manner in line with ones authority, area of expertise and resources</p>
<p><strong>Business Management &#8211; Result Base Management: </strong>Ability to manage programmes and projects with a focus at improved performance and demonstrable results.</p>
<p><strong>IMPORTANT NOTE:</strong></p>
<p>Please note that continuance of appointment beyond the initial 12 months is contingent upon the successful completion of a probationary period.</p>
<p><strong>UNDP Disclaimer for FTA/TA International Posts</strong></p>
<p><a href="https://eur03.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=http%3A%2F%2Fjobs.undp.org%2Fcj_us_permanent_card_holders.cfm&amp;data=04%7C01%7Calp.muezzinoglu%40undp.org%7Cbba03af5ff4c4d44e94808d9e4ba2fb7%7Cb3e5db5e2944483799f57488ace54319%7C0%7C0%7C637792310570896542%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJWIjoiMC4wLjAwMDAiLCJQIjoiV2luMzIiLCJBTiI6Ik1haWwiLCJXVCI6Mn0%3D%7C3000&amp;sdata=SGMD9kdKGxgN2ppzYhQ21zOZEEFaz6kuij1SMRPxbtg%3D&amp;reserved=0" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><strong>Important information for US Permanent Residents (&#8216;Green Card&#8217; holders)</strong></a></p>
<p>Under US immigration law, acceptance of a staff position with UNDP, an international organization, may have significant implications for US Permanent Residents. UNDP advises applicants for all professional level posts that they must relinquish their US Permanent Resident status and accept a G-4 visa, or have submitted a valid application for US citizenship prior to commencement of employment.</p>
<p>UNDP is not in a position to provide advice or assistance on applying for US citizenship and therefore applicants are advised to seek the advice of competent immigration lawyers regarding any applications.</p>
<p>Applicant information about UNDP rosters</p>
<p>Note: UNDP reserves the right to select one or more candidates from this vacancy announcement.  We may also retain applications and consider candidates applying to this post for other similar positions with UNDP at the same grade level and with similar job description, experience and educational requirements.</p>
<p>Scam warning</p>
<p>The United Nations does not charge any application, processing, training, interviewing, testing or other fee in connection with the application or recruitment process. Should you receive a solicitation for the payment of a fee, please disregard it. Furthermore, please note that emblems, logos, names and addresses are easily copied and reproduced. Therefore, you are advised to apply particular care when submitting personal information on the web.</p>
</div>
</div>
<div class="job-link-wrapper"></div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="ss-scrollbar-wrapper" dir="ltr" style="text-align: left;">
<div class="ss-scroll"></div>
</div>
</div>
<h3 class="apply-section" dir="ltr" style="text-align: left;" data-bind="i18nLang: job().lang"><strong><a href="https://estm.fa.em2.oraclecloud.com/hcmUI/CandidateExperience/en/sites/CX_1/job/3744/apply/email">APPLY NOW</a></strong></h3><p>The post <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly/jobs/project-specialist-27957009/">Project Specialist</a> first appeared on <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly">Libyanjobs</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
				<company>United Nations Development Programme (UNDP) in Libya</company>
		<job_address>Tripoli</job_address>
		<job_category>organization</job_category>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Protection Specialist – Psychosocial Support</title>
		<link>https://libyanjobs.ly/jobs/protection-specialist-psychosocial-support-27956932/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 05:22:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://libyanjobs.ly/?post_type=noo_job&#038;p=279569</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Protection Specialist – Psychosocial Support TRIPOLI, LIBYA Danish Refugee Council, one of the world’s leading humanitarian NGOs, is currently looking for a highly qualified candidate to fill in the position of Protection Specialist &#8211; Psycho-Socio Support (PSS) for our Country operations in Tripoli, DRC is an equal opportunity employer, which promotes and supports durable solutions to the problems faced by</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly/jobs/protection-specialist-psychosocial-support-27956932/">Protection Specialist – Psychosocial Support</a> first appeared on <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly">Libyanjobs</a>.</p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">
<table class="AdTemplateMainTable" dir="ltr" cellspacing="0" cellpadding="0">
<tbody>
<tr>
<td class="BottomLeftColumn">
<div class="ProjectName">Protection Specialist – Psychosocial Support</div>
<div id="AdvertisementInnerContent">
<p><strong>TRIPOLI, LIBYA</strong></p>
<p>Danish Refugee Council, one of the world’s leading humanitarian NGOs, is currently looking for a highly qualified candidate to fill in the position of Protection Specialist &#8211; Psycho-Socio Support (PSS) for our Country operations in Tripoli, DRC is an equal opportunity employer, which promotes and supports durable solutions to the problems faced by refugees and internally displaced people all over the world. DRC started its Country operations in Libya in 2011, with expertise in Protection, WASH, Shelter, Economic Recovery, and Community Safety.</p>
<p><strong>About the job</strong></p>
<p>Under the supervision of the Protection Manager, and in close coordination with the Protection Coordinator and other DRC Protection teams and field units, The Protection specialist -Psychosocial support is responsible to support the quality of DRC psychosocial protection activities that are implemented as a part of an integrated comprehensive protection program in Tripolitania, Libya. The position will provide technical guidance to DRC protection staff and develop the PSS approach for DRC Libya. S/he will also contribute to strengthening DRC’s community outreach approach and engaging with Libyan and non-Libyan Community including through coaching and supervision. S/he further contributes to administrative and technical support in close coordination with the Manager and Protection Coordinator.</p>
<p>Your main duties and responsibilities will be:</p>
<ul>
<li>In coordination with the Protection Manager and Protection coordinator develop DRC’s PSS strategic direction in Libya, including by developing a PSS strategic plan</li>
<li>Conduct a Mental Health, and Psychosocial needs assessment among the affected populations in Tripoli. For this purpose lead the development/contextualization of assessment and analysis tools based on international standards</li>
<li>Develop a PSS manual and other technical guidance as requested by the Protection manager</li>
<li>Provide continual technical support and monitoring of psychosocial support program activities to ensure the applicability of quality standards.</li>
<li>Provide supervision to protection staff on community psychosocial support interventions inclusive of ongoing capacity building, professional development and technical support.</li>
<li>Lead and facilitate weekly team meetings with program staff and conduct on-the-job supervision and training assessments to evaluate key competencies and training needs in the area of psychosocial support.</li>
<li>Ensure the effective use of and compliance with relevant tools, forms, SOPs, etc. so as to ensure program quality and impact.</li>
<li>Responsible for collating information and reporting progress and challenges to Protection manager and Protection coordinator</li>
<li>In coordination with the Protection Manager and Protection Coordinator, adjust program implementation based on needs and context.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>About you</strong></p>
<p>To be successful in this role we expect you to have a</p>
<ul>
<li>At least 3-years’ experience in the fields of working for international or national humanitarian organizations in complex conflict or post-confict settings, in the area of Mental health and psychosocial support</li>
<li>Previous experience working in context of mixed migration flows and internal displacement with good knowledge of the protection issues affecting people in a situation of forced displacement or migration</li>
<li>Demonstrate ability in conceptual, analytical, and critical thinking with the ability to contribute to programmatic or advocacy strategies towards greater quality and impact</li>
<li>Experience in capacity building of staff including training and supervision.</li>
<li>Knowledge of and experiences in using established inter-agency standards and guidelines in MHPSS and child protection, such as the IASC Guidelines on Mental Health and Psychosocial Support in Emergency Settings, the Minimum Standards for Child Protection in Humanitarian Action, Inter-agency Guidelines on Separated and Unaccompanied Children, and IASC Guidelines in Emergencies.</li>
<li>Excellent technical knowledge of protection standards and principles and demonstrated capacity to develop effective responses to identified psychosocial needs protection needs and in accordance with the relevant frameworks</li>
<li>Commitment to integrate gender, conflict sensitivity, and accountability into programming</li>
<li>Demonstrate ability in thinking creatively and practically to improve the quality of programming and achieve greater impact</li>
<li>Ability to work flexibly in a diverse team; with proven leadership skills</li>
</ul>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong><em>Required</em></strong></p>
<ul>
<li>University degree, Master’s preferred, in psychology or mental health counseling</li>
</ul>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong><em>Desirable</em></strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Fluency in written and spoken English</li>
<li>Knowledge of Arabic is an asset</li>
</ul>
<p>In this position, you are expected to demonstrate DRC’ five core competencies:</p>
<p><strong>Striving for excellence: </strong>You focus on reaching results while ensuring an efficient process.</p>
<p><strong>Collaborating:</strong> You involve relevant parties and encourage feedback.</p>
<p><strong>Taking the lead:</strong> You take ownership and initiative while aiming for innovation.</p>
<p><strong>Communicating:</strong> You listen and speak effectively and honestly.</p>
<p><strong>Demonstrating integrity:</strong> You uphold and promote the highest standards of ethical and professional conduct in relation to our values and Code of Conduct, including safeguarding against sexual exploitation, abuse and harassment.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>We offer: </strong></p>
<p><strong>Contract length</strong>: 3 Months</p>
<p><strong>Band</strong>: G</p>
<p><strong>Designation of Duty Station</strong>: Accompanied Family for Nationals/Unaccomapanied Family for Internationals.</p>
<p><strong>Start date</strong>: TBC</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Application process</strong></p>
<p>All applicants must upload a Cover letter and an updated CV (no longer than four pages) in English. <strong>A</strong><strong>pplications sent by email will not be considered.</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Closing date for applications:</strong> 19 July 2022</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>For further information about the Danish Refugee Council, please consult our website <a href="https://drc.ngo/">drc.ngo</a>.</p>
</div>
<p><b>DRC as an employer</b><br />
By working in DRC, you will be joining a global workforce of around 8000 employees in 40 countries. We pride ourselves on our:</p>
<ul>
<li>Professionalism, impact &amp; expertise</li>
<li>Humanitarian approach &amp; the work we do</li>
<li>Purpose, meaningfulness &amp; own contribution</li>
<li>Culture, values &amp; strong leadership</li>
<li>Fair compensation &amp; continuous development</li>
</ul>
<p>DRC’s capacity to ensure the protection of and assistance to refugees, IDP’s and other persons of concern depends on the ability of our staff to uphold and promote the highest standards of ethical and professional conduct in relation DRC’s values and Code of Conduct, including safeguarding against sexual exploitation, abuse and harassment. DRC conducts thorough and comprehensive background checks as part of the recruitment process.</p>
<p><b>If you have questions or are facing problems with the online application process, please visit <a href="https://drc.ngo/about-us/job-and-career/support-for-job-seekers/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">drc.ngo/about-us/job-and-career/support-for-job-seekers</a>.</b></p>
<p><em><b>Danish Refugee Council is an equal opportunity employer. We are committed to creating an inclusive and positive work environment based on mutual respect for all employees. All applicants are considered for employment without attention to race, age, ability, ethnicity, nationality, religion, gender identity, sexual orientation, marital status, or any other factor. At DRC we celebrate diversity and appreciate our employees for the people they are and their unique skills, backgrounds, and perspectives. We encourage all interested candidates to apply!</b></em></td>
<td class="BottomRightColumn"></td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
<p dir="ltr">
<h2 dir="ltr"><a href="https://candidate.hr-manager.net/ApplicationInit.aspx?cid=1036&amp;DepartmentId=19105&amp;ProjectId=163156&amp;MediaId=5&amp;SkipAdvertisement=true"><img src="https://cdn-recruiter.hr-manager.net/Export/Attachments/ViewFileManagerDocument.aspx?id=82415699-60c2-453d-b61f-b28ed4bd0a7c&amp;cid=1036" /> APPLY FOR POSITION</a></h2>
<p dir="ltr">
<b>Application due:</b><br />
7/19/2022</p>
<p><b>Workplace:</b><br />
Tripoli</p>
<p><b>Department/Country:</b><br />
Libya</p>
<p><b>Contract type:</b><br />
Expatriate or national contract</p>
<p><b>Homepage:</b><br />
<a href="http://www.drc.ngo/">drc.ngo</a></p>
<div dir="ltr">
<h3>ABOUT DRC</h3>
<p>DRC (Danish Refugee Council), founded in Denmark in 1956, is Denmark’s largest and the world’s leading non-profit, independent, rights-based refugee organization.</p>
<p>Our vision is to assist refugees, internally displaced people and their host communities to a dignified life. We protect lives and human rights and empower beneficiaries throughout conflict displacement by providing shelter, food, and hope in terms of work, education and integration towards a sustainable future.</p></div><p>The post <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly/jobs/protection-specialist-psychosocial-support-27956932/">Protection Specialist – Psychosocial Support</a> first appeared on <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly">Libyanjobs</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
				<company>DRC Libya</company>
		<job_address>Tripoli</job_address>
		<job_category>organization</job_category>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>طلب وكلاء لبيع المنظومات</title>
		<link>https://libyanjobs.ly/jobs/%d8%b7%d9%84%d8%a8-%d9%88%d9%83%d9%84%d8%a7%d8%a1-%d9%84%d8%a8%d9%8a%d8%b9-%d8%a7%d9%84%d9%85%d9%86%d8%b8%d9%88%d9%85%d8%a7%d8%aa/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[كنترول سوفت للمنظومات والأمن السيبراني]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 00:14:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://libyanjobs.ly/?post_type=noo_job&#038;p=279544</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>وصف الوظيفة وكلاء لبيع المنظومات بمختلف انواعها (مبيعات،منظومات ادارية للشركات …الخ) بنسبة ربح عالية تصل إلى  خمسون بالمئة وعلى نوع كل منظومة يتم تحديد النسبة الشروط دراية بسيطة بالكومبيوتر قدرة على التعامل مع الزبائن وشرح تفاصيل المنظومات للزبائن أن يكون المتقدم لديه محل يخص الكومبيوتر أو الهواتف متطلبات الوظيفة امتلاك محل للكومبيوتر سواء بيع أو صيانة ، أو محل هواتف</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly/jobs/%d8%b7%d9%84%d8%a8-%d9%88%d9%83%d9%84%d8%a7%d8%a1-%d9%84%d8%a8%d9%8a%d8%b9-%d8%a7%d9%84%d9%85%d9%86%d8%b8%d9%88%d9%85%d8%a7%d8%aa/">طلب وكلاء لبيع المنظومات</a> first appeared on <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly">Libyanjobs</a>.</p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h3 style="text-align: right;">وصف الوظيفة</h3>
<p style="text-align: right;">وكلاء لبيع المنظومات بمختلف انواعها (مبيعات،منظومات ادارية للشركات …الخ) بنسبة ربح عالية تصل إلى  خمسون بالمئة وعلى نوع كل منظومة يتم تحديد النسبة</p>
<h3 style="text-align: right;">الشروط</h3>
<ul style="text-align: right;">
<li>دراية بسيطة بالكومبيوتر</li>
<li>قدرة على التعامل مع الزبائن وشرح تفاصيل المنظومات للزبائن</li>
<li>أن يكون المتقدم لديه محل يخص الكومبيوتر أو الهواتف</li>
</ul>
<h3 style="text-align: right;">متطلبات الوظيفة</h3>
<ol style="text-align: right;">
<li>امتلاك محل للكومبيوتر سواء بيع أو صيانة ، أو محل هواتف للتحصل على الوكالة</li>
</ol>
<h3 style="text-align: right;">التقديم على الوظيفة</h3>
<p style="text-align: right;">التواصل على الرقم</p>
<p style="text-align: right;">00218910706780</p>
<p style="text-align: right;">أو عبر الواتساب</p>
<p style="text-align: right;">00218922750078</p><p>The post <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly/jobs/%d8%b7%d9%84%d8%a8-%d9%88%d9%83%d9%84%d8%a7%d8%a1-%d9%84%d8%a8%d9%8a%d8%b9-%d8%a7%d9%84%d9%85%d9%86%d8%b8%d9%88%d9%85%d8%a7%d8%aa/">طلب وكلاء لبيع المنظومات</a> first appeared on <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly">Libyanjobs</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
				<company>كنترول سوفت للمنظومات والأمن السيبراني</company>
		<job_address>طرابلس</job_address>
		<job_category>Sales,Sales and Customer Service</job_category>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>مراجع مالى</title>
		<link>https://libyanjobs.ly/jobs/financial-auditor-2793213665/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2022 11:28:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://libyanjobs.ly/?post_type=noo_job&#038;p=279321</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>تعلن شركة العلامة لاستيراد الادويه عن حاجتها لتوظيف مراجع داخلى ( مراجع مالى) للشركة للعمل بمقر الشركة الكائن بالسراج طرابلس خلال فترة الدوام من الساعه 9 صباحا الى 2 ظهرا على ان يشترط للمتقدم او المتقدمه الشروط الاتيه :- 1- متحصل على بكالوريس محاسبه او مايعادلها 2- يجيد استعمال الحاسوب بمعدل جيد جدا وخصوصا برنامج الاكسل 3- يجيد اللغه الانجليزيه</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly/jobs/financial-auditor-2793213665/">مراجع مالى</a> first appeared on <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly">Libyanjobs</a>.</p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div>
<div class="" dir="auto">
<div id="jsc_c_11" class="ecm0bbzt hv4rvrfc dati1w0a e5nlhep0" data-ad-comet-preview="message" data-ad-preview="message">
<div class="j83agx80 cbu4d94t ew0dbk1b irj2b8pg">
<div class="qzhwtbm6 knvmm38d">
<div class="cxmmr5t8 oygrvhab hcukyx3x c1et5uql o9v6fnle ii04i59q">
<div dir="auto">تعلن شركة العلامة لاستيراد الادويه عن حاجتها لتوظيف مراجع داخلى ( مراجع مالى) للشركة للعمل بمقر الشركة الكائن بالسراج طرابلس خلال فترة الدوام من الساعه 9 صباحا الى 2 ظهرا</div>
<div dir="auto">على ان يشترط للمتقدم او المتقدمه الشروط الاتيه :-</div>
</div>
<div class="cxmmr5t8 oygrvhab hcukyx3x c1et5uql o9v6fnle ii04i59q">
<div dir="auto">1- متحصل على بكالوريس محاسبه او مايعادلها</div>
<div dir="auto">2- يجيد استعمال الحاسوب بمعدل جيد جدا وخصوصا برنامج الاكسل</div>
<div dir="auto">3- يجيد اللغه الانجليزيه قراءه وكتابه بمستوى فوق المتوسط</div>
<div dir="auto">4- الاولويه من لديهم خبره فى العمل المحاسبى</div>
<div dir="auto">من يرى فى نفسه او من ترى فى نفسها القدره والرغبه</div>
<div dir="auto">ان ترسل السيره الذاتيه على الايميل الاتى</div>
<div style="text-align: right;"><a href="mailto:Office@alalama.ly">Office@alalama.ly</a></div>
<div dir="auto">وكذلك ارسال رساله نصيه بالاسم ورقم الهاتف على هاتف الشركة ‭</div>
<div dir="auto" style="text-align: right;">0928337025</div>
<div dir="auto">لمزيد من الاستفسارات التواصل على الرقم المذكور اعلاه خلال ساعات الدوام ‬</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div>
<div class="stjgntxs ni8dbmo4 l82x9zwi uo3d90p7 h905i5nu monazrh9" data-visualcompletion="ignore-dynamic">
<div>
<div>
<div class="l9j0dhe7">
<div class="bp9cbjyn m9osqain j83agx80 jq4qci2q bkfpd7mw a3bd9o3v kvgmc6g5 wkznzc2l oygrvhab dhix69tm jktsbyx5 rz4wbd8a osnr6wyh a8nywdso s1tcr66n">
<div class="bp9cbjyn j83agx80 buofh1pr ni8dbmo4 stjgntxs"></div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="cwj9ozl2 tvmbv18p">
<h3 class="gmql0nx0 l94mrbxd p1ri9a11 lzcic4wl q45zohi1 ema1e40h ay7djpcl ni8dbmo4 stjgntxs pmk7jnqg rfua0xdk" dir="auto"></h3>
</div>
</div>
</div><p>The post <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly/jobs/financial-auditor-2793213665/">مراجع مالى</a> first appeared on <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly">Libyanjobs</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
				<company>Alalama Company for importing medicine and medical equipment</company>
		<job_address>Tripoli</job_address>
		<job_category>Medicines and medical equipment</job_category>
	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>