<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Jobs - Libyanjobs</title>
	<atom:link href="https://libyanjobs.ly/en/jobs/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://libyanjobs.ly/en/</link>
	<description>Libyan Job Site</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 10:09:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://media.libyanjobs.ly/uploads/2021/02/cropped-Jobs_Fav-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Jobs - Libyanjobs</title>
	<link>https://libyanjobs.ly/en/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Administrative Assistant (female)</title>
		<link>https://libyanjobs.ly/en/jobs/administrative-assistant-female-287664335/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[.Zone Technology Co]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 10:09:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://libyanjobs.ly/?post_type=noo_job&#038;p=265686</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Job Description Entry level administrative assistant Job Requirements Attentive Time management skills Management skills Basic computer skills Basic English level How To Apply info@zone.ly</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly/en/jobs/administrative-assistant-female-287664335/">Administrative Assistant (female)</a> first appeared on <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly/en/">Libyanjobs</a>.</p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h3>Job Description</h3>
<p>Entry level administrative assistant</p>
<h3>Job Requirements</h3>
<ol>
<li>Attentive</li>
<li>Time management skills</li>
<li>Management skills</li>
<li>Basic computer skills</li>
<li>Basic English level</li>
</ol>
<h3>How To Apply</h3>
<p><strong><a href="mailto:info@zone.ly">info@zone.ly</a></strong></p><p>The post <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly/en/jobs/administrative-assistant-female-287664335/">Administrative Assistant (female)</a> first appeared on <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly/en/">Libyanjobs</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
				<company>.Zone Technology Co</company>
		<job_category>Administration</job_category>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>E-Marketing Expert</title>
		<link>https://libyanjobs.ly/en/jobs/looking-for-an-e-marketing-expert-female-employee-5478987455/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[المجد للمقاولات و الإستثمار العقاري]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 09:02:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://libyanjobs.ly/?post_type=noo_job&#038;p=265603</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>We are Libya Al-Majd Real Estate Investment Company We are looking for an E-Marketing Expert (female employee). Job Requirements: &#8211; Proficiency in computer programs, especially MS Office programs. Availability of more than one live language (English, French&#8230;) in addition to the Arabic language. Professional handling of social media and advertising campaign management. &#8211; At least 3 years of experience in</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly/en/jobs/looking-for-an-e-marketing-expert-female-employee-5478987455/">E-Marketing Expert</a> first appeared on <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly/en/">Libyanjobs</a>.</p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>We are Libya Al-Majd Real Estate Investment Company<br />
We are looking for an E-Marketing Expert (female employee).<br />
Job Requirements:<br />
&#8211; Proficiency in computer programs, especially MS Office programs.<br />
Availability of more than one live language (English, French&#8230;) in addition to the Arabic language.<br />
Professional handling of social media and advertising campaign management.<br />
&#8211; At least 3 years of experience in e-marketing (Real Estate).<br />
It is preferable that she reside near the company’s headquarters located in AL Seyahia area behind Badr Mosque.<br />
For those who feel comfortable meeting the conditions and qualifications, please send your CV to the e-mail:<a href="mailto:info@libyaalmagd.com"> info@libyaalmagd.com</a><br />
Or contact us via the following numbers: 0918405050 &#8211; 0926991530 (WhatsApp or Viber).</p>
<p>During official working hours (9 am to 4 pm).</p>
<p><a href="https://media.libyanjobs.ly/uploads/2022/05/IMG_20220109_033048.jpg"><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-265596" src="https://media.libyanjobs.ly/uploads/2022/05/IMG_20220109_033048-300x300.jpg" alt="" width="300" height="300" srcset="https://media.libyanjobs.ly/uploads/2022/05/IMG_20220109_033048-300x300.jpg 300w, https://media.libyanjobs.ly/uploads/2022/05/IMG_20220109_033048-1024x1024.jpg 1024w, https://media.libyanjobs.ly/uploads/2022/05/IMG_20220109_033048-150x150.jpg 150w, https://media.libyanjobs.ly/uploads/2022/05/IMG_20220109_033048-768x768.jpg 768w, https://media.libyanjobs.ly/uploads/2022/05/IMG_20220109_033048-200x200.jpg 200w, https://media.libyanjobs.ly/uploads/2022/05/IMG_20220109_033048-100x100.jpg 100w, https://media.libyanjobs.ly/uploads/2022/05/IMG_20220109_033048-252x252.jpg 252w, https://media.libyanjobs.ly/uploads/2022/05/IMG_20220109_033048-500x500.jpg 500w, https://media.libyanjobs.ly/uploads/2022/05/IMG_20220109_033048-60x60.jpg 60w, https://media.libyanjobs.ly/uploads/2022/05/IMG_20220109_033048-90x90.jpg 90w, https://media.libyanjobs.ly/uploads/2022/05/IMG_20220109_033048.jpg 1440w" sizes="(max-width: 300px) 100vw, 300px" /></a></p><p>The post <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly/en/jobs/looking-for-an-e-marketing-expert-female-employee-5478987455/">E-Marketing Expert</a> first appeared on <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly/en/">Libyanjobs</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
				<company>المجد للمقاولات و الإستثمار العقاري</company>
		<job_category>Marketing, PR &amp; Advertising,Social Media</job_category>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Libya Transition Initiative (LTI) 4- Program Development Officer-Tripoli</title>
		<link>https://libyanjobs.ly/en/jobs/libya-transition-initiative-lti-4-program-development-officer-tripoli-4521887000/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chemonics International, Libya Transition Initiative 4 (LTI4) Project]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 08:31:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://libyanjobs.ly/?post_type=noo_job&#038;p=265579</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Background The Libya Transition Initiative 4 project implemented by Chemonics International aims to establish and manage a quick-response mechanism supporting activities that reinforce stability and build an inclusive and peaceful democratic future.   Purpose The Program Development Officer (PDO) plays a central role in developing activities with carefully selected organizations that further the program’s strategic objectives, in full compliance with</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly/en/jobs/libya-transition-initiative-lti-4-program-development-officer-tripoli-4521887000/">Libya Transition Initiative (LTI) 4- Program Development Officer-Tripoli</a> first appeared on <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly/en/">Libyanjobs</a>.</p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Background</strong></p>
<p>The Libya Transition Initiative 4 project implemented by Chemonics International aims to establish and manage a quick-response mechanism supporting activities that reinforce stability and build an inclusive and peaceful democratic future.</p>
<p><strong> </strong></p>
<p><strong>Purpose</strong></p>
<p>The Program Development Officer (PDO) plays a central role in developing activities with carefully selected organizations that further the program’s strategic objectives, in full compliance with Chemonics regulations and policies.</p>
<p><strong> </strong></p>
<p><strong>Reporting</strong></p>
<p>The PDO reports to the Regional Program Manager (RPM).</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Location</strong></p>
<p>Tripoli, Libya</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Responsibilities </strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Analyze Libya’s rapidly changing environment on an ongoing basis, and contribute to program strategy, under the overall direction of the senior management team.</li>
<li>Identify potential partners, communities, and community groups within the area of responsibility where program objectives can be met and work with them to design and develop grant activities.</li>
<li>Proactively identify and conceptualize potential activities that are appropriate to respond to the established program goals and objectives and strategic priorities.</li>
<li>Develop and finalize multiple activities, on an ongoing basis, in a fast-paced and highly changeable environment.</li>
<li>Provide technical oversight of all activities and ensure alignment with regional strategy.</li>
<li>Consult with grants specialists and procurement specialists in designing the mechanism of the activities to ensure effective implementation.</li>
<li>Actively participate in the problem solving and troubleshooting throughout the grant cycle to ensure alignment with grant objectives and intention.</li>
<li>Provide technical assistance to grantees and potential grantees as required, throughout the activity cycle, to enhance implementation and address challenges.</li>
<li>Conduct regular monitoring visits to assess progress of activities, follow-up on programmatic issues, and provide regular updates to the grants management unit and senior management team on activity impact, opportunities, and problems.</li>
<li>Maintain working relationships and liaison with project counterparts.</li>
<li>Write implementation plans in a timely manner.</li>
<li>Support the Monitoring, Evaluation &amp; Learning Specialist with contributions to monitoring and evaluation reports.</li>
<li>Provide regular updates on activity development and implementation to the grants management unit and senior management team.</li>
<li>Undertake other duties as assigned by supervisor.</li>
</ul>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Qualifications</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Bachelor’s degree in a relevant field required.</li>
<li>Intimate understanding of Western Libya, including key cities.</li>
<li>Minimum of three years of work experience required.</li>
<li>Fluent written and spoken English and Arabic are required.</li>
<li>Strong organizational, management and administrative skills, preferably with respect to report writing and monitoring and evaluation.</li>
<li>Demonstrated analytical ability and understanding of local and regional political context, with the ability to think creatively in conceptualizing relevant grant activities.</li>
<li>Proven experience working with governance institutions as well as with local and international NGOs and community-based organizations implementing relevant activities and programs in country.</li>
<li>An up-to-date understanding and knowledge of the political environment and social conditions in country and the surrounding region.</li>
<li>Experience and/or good understanding of donor organizations.</li>
<li>Ability/willingness to travel throughout Libya.</li>
<li>Undertake other duties as assigned by supervisor.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>How to Apply?</strong></p>
<p>Interested applicants can apply through the below link, deadline for accepting CVs is May 20, 2022.  <a href="https://fs3.formsite.com/n3f3pk/eadgawwfyw/index.html">https://fs3.formsite.com/n3f3pk/eadgawwfyw/index.html</a></p><p>The post <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly/en/jobs/libya-transition-initiative-lti-4-program-development-officer-tripoli-4521887000/">Libya Transition Initiative (LTI) 4- Program Development Officer-Tripoli</a> first appeared on <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly/en/">Libyanjobs</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
				<company>Chemonics International, Libya Transition Initiative 4 (LTI4) Project</company>
		<job_address>Tripoli - Libya</job_address>
		<job_category>Other,Not Classified</job_category>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Marketing Manager</title>
		<link>https://libyanjobs.ly/en/jobs/marketing-manager-265776543/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[mohamed]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 05:08:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://libyanjobs.ly/?post_type=noo_job&#038;p=265776</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Alhadaf Pharmaceuticals, Medical Equipment &#38; Sundries is one of the leading pharmaceutical &#38; medical products’ importers &#38; distributors  in the Libyan market, representing a number of multinational manufacturers. The company is currently looking for candidates for the position of “Marketing Manager, with the following  requirements and responsibilities: The ideal candidate should have at least a Bachelor in marketing or in</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly/en/jobs/marketing-manager-265776543/">Marketing Manager</a> first appeared on <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly/en/">Libyanjobs</a>.</p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="font-weight: 400;">Alhadaf Pharmaceuticals, Medical Equipment &amp; Sundries is one of the leading pharmaceutical &amp; medical products’ importers &amp; distributors  in the Libyan market, representing a number of multinational manufacturers.</p>
<p style="font-weight: 400;">The company is currently looking for candidates for the position of “Marketing Manager, with the following  requirements and responsibilities:</p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">The ideal candidate should have at least a Bachelor in marketing or in one of the medical sciences.</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">A Master degree in marketing or business will represent an additional asset.</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">A high level of problem solving skills and analytical abilities are required.</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">Good experience in marketing &amp; selling.</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">Good communication, presentation, negotiation &amp; selling skills.</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;">Leadership in sales &amp; marketing (people, service &amp; product leadership).</li>
</ul>
<p style="font-weight: 400;">The C.V., including the candidate’s contact details &amp; references can be sent to: Alhadaf for Pharmaceuticals, Medical Equipment &amp; Sundries, by Email: <a href="mailto:sales@alhadafgroup.com">sales@alhadafgroup.com</a></p>
<p style="font-weight: 400;"><p>The post <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly/en/jobs/marketing-manager-265776543/">Marketing Manager</a> first appeared on <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly/en/">Libyanjobs</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
				<company>Alhadaf for Pharmaceuticals, Medical Equipment  Sundries</company>
		<job_address>Tripoli</job_address>
		<job_category>Healthcare Services</job_category>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Trade Marketing Representative &#8211; Tobacco</title>
		<link>https://libyanjobs.ly/en/jobs/trade-marketing-representative-tobacco/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Salvo Grima]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 11:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://libyanjobs.ly/?post_type=noo_job&#038;p=264208</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Job Overview The Trade Marketing Representative’s primary role is to directly support the local manager, handle the day-to-day administration of the office, and manage and coordinate the marketing activities of Salvo Grima in Libya. The candidate will also be responsible for the daily market surveillance regarding product availability and pricing while ensuring the highest quality of services and maintaining a</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly/en/jobs/trade-marketing-representative-tobacco/">Trade Marketing Representative – Tobacco</a> first appeared on <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly/en/">Libyanjobs</a>.</p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2><strong>Job Overview</strong></h2>
<p>The Trade Marketing Representative’s primary role is to directly support the local manager, handle the day-to-day administration of the office, and manage and coordinate the marketing activities of Salvo Grima in Libya. The candidate will also be responsible for the daily market surveillance regarding product availability and pricing while ensuring the highest quality of services and maintaining a positive relationship with retailers and consumers.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h2><strong>Duties &amp; Responsibilities</strong></h2>
<ul>
<li>Leading marketing campaigns and promotional strategies.</li>
<li>Assisting in the preparation, coordination, collection, production, supervision and follow-ups of promotions and marketing events.</li>
<li>Representing Salvo Grima and its clients by maintaining a positive and professional demeanour.</li>
<li>Building and maintaining customer relationships.</li>
<li>Daily market surveillance and weekly reports.</li>
<li>Preparing daily reports on market research.</li>
<li>Initiating and analysing consumer and market research to identify market trends and target consumer preferences to improve marketing efforts.</li>
<li>Monitoring competition activity, producing a weekly market summary report.</li>
<li>Maintaining an internal database on product availability and pricing.</li>
<li>Contributing to the daily growth and development of our company.</li>
<li>Other duties as assigned.</li>
</ul>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h2>Knowledge &amp; Skills:</h2>
<ul>
<li>Basic marketing and promotional principles.</li>
<li>Proficiency in Microsoft Office.</li>
<li>Ability to establish effective working relationships with colleagues and customers.</li>
<li>Ability to multitask and meet deadlines.</li>
<li>Professional appearance and demeanour.</li>
<li>Excellent communication skills.</li>
<li>Strong time management and organisational skills.</li>
<li>Outgoing, energetic, detail-oriented, and responsible.</li>
<li>Entrepreneurial attitude and ability to think outside the box with a desire to grow and learn.</li>
<li>A basic level of English would be appreciated.</li>
</ul><p>The post <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly/en/jobs/trade-marketing-representative-tobacco/">Trade Marketing Representative – Tobacco</a> first appeared on <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly/en/">Libyanjobs</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
				<company>Salvo Grima</company>
		<job_address>Tripoli - Libya</job_address>
		<job_category>Marketing, PR , Advertising</job_category>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Salesman</title>
		<link>https://libyanjobs.ly/en/jobs/salesman-289023615/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Maggadit for Food and Beverage]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 10:44:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://libyanjobs.ly/?post_type=noo_job&#038;p=265458</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Responsibilities: Present, promote and sell products/services using solid arguments to existing and prospective customers Perform cost-benefit and needs analysis of existing/potential customers to meet their needs Establish, develop, and maintain positive business and customer relationships Reach out to customer leads through cold calling Expedite the resolution of customer problems and complaints to maximize satisfaction Achieve agreed upon sales targets and</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly/en/jobs/salesman-289023615/">Salesman</a> first appeared on <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly/en/">Libyanjobs</a>.</p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h3>Responsibilities:</h3>
<ul>
<li>Present, promote and sell products/services using solid arguments to existing and prospective customers</li>
<li>Perform cost-benefit and needs analysis of existing/potential customers to meet their needs</li>
<li>Establish, develop, and maintain positive business and customer relationships</li>
<li>Reach out to customer leads through cold calling</li>
<li>Expedite the resolution of customer problems and complaints to maximize satisfaction</li>
<li>Achieve agreed upon sales targets and outcomes within schedule</li>
<li>Coordinate sales effort with team members and other departments</li>
<li>analyse the territory /market’s potential, track sales and status reports</li>
<li>Supply management with reports on customer needs, problems, interests, competitive activities, and potential for new products and services</li>
<li>Keep abreast of best practices and promotional trends</li>
<li>Continuously improve through feedback</li>
</ul>
<h3>Requirements:</h3>
<ul>
<li>A degree in sales, marketing, commerce, or a related field would be advantageous</li>
<li>Excellent communication skills</li>
<li>Flexible work hours</li>
<li>Basic mathematics skills</li>
<li>Prior experience in wholesale</li>
<li>Excellent customer service skills</li>
</ul>
<p>&nbsp;</p><p>The post <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly/en/jobs/salesman-289023615/">Salesman</a> first appeared on <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly/en/">Libyanjobs</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
				<company>Maggadit for Food and Beverage</company>
		<job_address>Tripoli,Tripoli - Libya</job_address>
		<job_category>Sales,Sales and Customer Service</job_category>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Database Programmer  Administrator</title>
		<link>https://libyanjobs.ly/en/jobs/database-programmer-administrator-282828334/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Maggadit for Food and Beverage]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 10:43:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://libyanjobs.ly/?post_type=noo_job&#038;p=265471</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Responsibilities: Design databases with both front-end and back-end users in mind Configure and ensure that the database is adequately backed up and able to be recovered in the event of memory loss Protect the database against threats or unauthorized access Receive requests pertaining to the layout, appearance, and special features of each database Design and create appropriate frameworks that are</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly/en/jobs/database-programmer-administrator-282828334/">Database Programmer & Administrator</a> first appeared on <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly/en/">Libyanjobs</a>.</p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h3>Responsibilities:</h3>
<ul>
<li>Design databases with both front-end and back-end users in mind</li>
<li>Configure and ensure that the database is adequately backed up and able to be recovered in the event of memory loss</li>
<li>Protect the database against threats or unauthorized access</li>
<li>Receive requests pertaining to the layout, appearance, and special features of each database</li>
<li>Design and create appropriate frameworks that are sufficiently large</li>
<li>Review each development to detect and amend coding and typographical errors, as well as bugs</li>
<li>Formulate data dictionaries that are congruent with task specifications</li>
<li>Create technical documents that outline the purpose, capacity, and guidelines attached to each database</li>
<li>Monitor system performance and identify problems that arise</li>
<li>Respond in a timely manner to user-reported errors</li>
<li>Report on metrics regarding usage and performance</li>
<li>Suggest changes and improvements for database maintenance or protection</li>
<li>Gather all salient information regarding the intended functions of each database</li>
<li>Provide practical guidance on the use and migration of each database</li>
<li>Service and update databases as required</li>
</ul>
<h3>Requirements:</h3>
<ul>
<li>Bachelor’s degree in IT field</li>
<li>5 – 8 Years’ experience as a Database Developer &amp; Administrator</li>
<li>Certificate in Database Development is strongly advantageous</li>
<li>Portfolio of previous developments is preferred</li>
<li>Advanced proficiency in SQL, C++, or Java, with a preference for more than one of these</li>
<li>Exceptional critical thinking and troubleshooting abilities</li>
<li>Ability to craft detailed technical manuals</li>
</ul><p>The post <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly/en/jobs/database-programmer-administrator-282828334/">Database Programmer & Administrator</a> first appeared on <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly/en/">Libyanjobs</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
				<company>Maggadit for Food and Beverage</company>
		<job_address>Tripoli,Tripoli - Libya</job_address>
		<job_category>Information, Communications Technology,Information Technology</job_category>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Front Desk operator (Evening shift)</title>
		<link>https://libyanjobs.ly/en/jobs/front-desk-operator-evening-shift-289763433/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nuqta Co-working Space]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 10:43:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://libyanjobs.ly/?post_type=noo_job&#038;p=265185</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Job Description The front desk operator is often the first person that members go to, and their purpose is to improve the relationships within the space to build the desired environment. This type of role is filled by someone who is an extrovert and loves people and making connections. The front desk operator be in charge of all member signups,</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly/en/jobs/front-desk-operator-evening-shift-289763433/">Front Desk operator (Evening shift)</a> first appeared on <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly/en/">Libyanjobs</a>.</p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h3>Job Description</h3>
<p>The front desk operator is often the first person that members go to, and their purpose is to improve the relationships within the space to build the desired environment. This type of role is filled by someone who is an extrovert and loves people and making connections. The front desk operator be in charge of all member signups, tours, customer service, answering phone &amp; emails, host member gatherings like workshops, training events, and create the overall environment and vibe of the space. A good front desk operator keeps things running smoothly in the space while also curating the company culture.</p>
<h3>Benefits</h3>
<ul>
<li>Gain experience in doing various types of activities.</li>
<li>Build a strong network and make new connections.</li>
<li>An ideal environment to grow your skills, and boost your creativity.</li>
</ul>
<h3>Job Requirements</h3>
<ol>
<li>Welcoming members</li>
<li>Help desk</li>
<li>Basic IT services</li>
<li>System and data entry.</li>
<li>Booking room management</li>
<li>Customer service</li>
<li>Social media posts</li>
</ol>
<h3>How To Apply</h3>
<p><a href="mailto:kusai@nuqta.ly">kusai@nuqta.ly</a></p>
<p><a href="mailto:info@nuqta.ly">info@nuqta.ly</a></p><p>The post <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly/en/jobs/front-desk-operator-evening-shift-289763433/">Front Desk operator (Evening shift)</a> first appeared on <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly/en/">Libyanjobs</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
				<company>Nuqta Co-working Space</company>
		<job_address>Tripoli - Libya</job_address>
		<job_category>Administration,Receptionist</job_category>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cleaner &#8211; ( Libyans Only)</title>
		<link>https://libyanjobs.ly/en/jobs/cleaner-libyans-only-25630/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Norwegian Refugee Council NRC]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 10:38:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://libyanjobs.ly/?post_type=noo_job&#038;p=265489</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>  Job Description   A job description is a written statement that describes the employee’s role and responsibilities. The role and responsibilities shall be executed within the NRC framework. The job description facilitates the recruitment process by stating the necessary competencies. It is mandatory for all positions. &#160; Position:                                              Cleaner Reports to:                                          HR/Admin Staff Supervision of:</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly/en/jobs/cleaner-libyans-only-25630/">Cleaner – ( Libyans Only)</a> first appeared on <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly/en/">Libyanjobs</a>.</p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong> </strong></p>
<p>Job Description</p>
<p><strong> </strong></p>
<p><em>A job description is a written statement that describes the employee’s role and responsibilities. The role and responsibilities shall be executed within the NRC framework. The job description facilitates the recruitment process by stating the necessary competencies. It is mandatory for all positions.</em></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Position:                                              Cleaner</p>
<p>Reports to:                                          HR/Admin Staff</p>
<p>Supervision of:                                  HR &amp; Admin Department</p>
<p>Duty station:                                      Tripoli, Libya</p>
<p>Travel:                                                  0%</p>
<p>Project number:                            XXXX</p>
<p>Duration and type of contract:    XXXX</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>All NRC employees are expected to work in accordance with the organization’s core values: dedication, innovation, inclusivity and accountability. These attitudes and believes shall guide our actions and relationships.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<ol>
<li><strong>Role and responsibilities</strong></li>
</ol>
<p>The following is a brief description of the role.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><u>Generic responsibilities (max 10)</u></p>
<p>These responsibilities shall be the same for all positions with the same title. The responsibilities shall be short and essential. Details belong in the Work- and Professional Development Plan.</p>
<p><u> </u></p>
<ol>
<li>Clean the, rooms, washrooms/WC, kitchen and other common areas such as the yard.</li>
<li>Ensure compliance with NRC procedures and policies</li>
<li>Ensure that cleaning supplies are properly stocked.</li>
<li>Dust and polish furniture, windows, doors and equipment</li>
<li>Empty waste paper baskets, dustbins and shredding machines</li>
<li>Report any relevant gaps, damages and breakages to line manager</li>
<li>Support the administration with ad hoc duties</li>
</ol>
<p><u> </u></p>
<p><u>Specific responsibilities </u></p>
<p>These responsibilities shall be adapted to the particularities of the job location and context, phase of operation, strategic focus and type of programme intervention. This section shall be revised whenever a new employee is hired or the context changes significantly.</p>
<ul>
<li>Clean the offices, class rooms, main rooms, living rooms, washrooms/WC, kitchen and other common areas such as the yard, corridors and stairs.</li>
<li>Ensure that cleaning supplies are properly stocked.</li>
<li>Ensure that all classrooms are ready and clean before and after each session</li>
<li>Ensure the outdoor area is clean and well prepared</li>
<li>Dust and polish furniture, windows, doors and equipment are all well-stored.</li>
<li>Empty waste paper basket, dustbins and shredding machines</li>
<li>Report any relevant gaps, damages and breakages to line manager</li>
<li>Support the administration with general duties</li>
<li>Ensure the availability of all kitchen and toilet supplies at all times (i.e. soap, air freshener, tissue, coffee, tea, sugar, etc.)</li>
<li>Watering indoor and outdoor plants.</li>
</ul>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><u>Critical interfaces</u></p>
<p>By interfaces, NRC means processes and projects that are interlinked with other departments/units or persons. Relevant interfaces for this position are:</p>
<p><strong> </strong></p>
<p><strong> </strong></p>
<ol start="2">
<li><strong>Competencies </strong></li>
</ol>
<p>Competencies are important in order for the employee and the organisation to deliver desired results. They are relevant for all staff and are divided into the following two categories:</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<ol>
<li><u> Professional competencies </u></li>
</ol>
<p>These are skills, knowledge and experience that are important for effective performance.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Generic professional competencies for this position</strong>:</p>
<ul>
<li>Experience from working as a Cleaner in a humanitarian/recovery context</li>
<li>Previous experience from working in complex and volatile contexts</li>
<li>Documented results related to the position’s responsibilities</li>
<li>Knowledge about own skills/profile</li>
<li>Arabic</li>
<li>Other Language is considered</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Context related skills, knowledge and experience</strong> (shall be adapted to the specific position):</p>
<ul>
<li>Organized, Clean and Neat</li>
<li>Knowledge in preparing various tea and coffee</li>
<li>Respectful and courteous</li>
<li>Attention to details and structured</li>
</ul>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<ol start="2">
<li><u> Behavioural competencies (max 6)</u></li>
</ol>
<p>These are personal qualities that influence how successful people are in their job. NRC’s Competency Framework states 12 behavioural competencies, and the following are <strong>essential</strong> for this position:</p>
<ul>
<li>Planning and delivering results</li>
<li>Working with people</li>
<li>Handling insecure environments</li>
</ul>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<ol start="3">
<li><strong>Performance Management</strong></li>
</ol>
<p>The employee will be accountable for the responsibilities and the competencies, in accordance with the NRC Performance Management Manual. The following documents will be used for performance reviews:</p>
<ul>
<li>The Job Description</li>
<li>The individual Work- and Professional Development Plan</li>
<li>The Competency Framework</li>
</ul>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://ekum.fa.em2.oraclecloud.com/hcmUI/CandidateExperience/en/sites/CX_1001/requisitions/job/5919/?keyword=Cleaner+-+%28+Libyans+Only%29"><strong> APPLY NOW </strong></a></p><p>The post <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly/en/jobs/cleaner-libyans-only-25630/">Cleaner – ( Libyans Only)</a> first appeared on <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly/en/">Libyanjobs</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
				<company>Norwegian Refugee Council  NRC</company>
		<job_address>Tripoli - Libya</job_address>
		<job_category>Cleaning Services</job_category>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>HR Specialist New</title>
		<link>https://libyanjobs.ly/en/jobs/hr-specialist-2800098123-new/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Alwadi Communications]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 10:38:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://libyanjobs.ly/?post_type=noo_job&#038;p=265478</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Job Title: HR Specialist Job Type:. Full-time Work Location: Tripoli-Libya  Department: HR MAIN DUTIES/RESPONSIBILITIES: Responsible on updating HR and payroll system Record related to employment, hiring ,attendance, promoting, and terminating Maintains personnel files in compliance with applicable ISO requirements. Ensuring new hire paperwork is completed and processed Overseeing hiring process, which includes coordinating job posts, reviewing &#38; short listed resumes,</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly/en/jobs/hr-specialist-2800098123-new/">HR Specialist New</a> first appeared on <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly/en/">Libyanjobs</a>.</p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Job Title: </strong>HR Specialist</p>
<p><strong>Job Type</strong><strong>:</strong><em>. </em>Full-time</p>
<p><strong>Work Location:</strong> Tripoli-Libya<strong> </strong></p>
<p><strong>Department: </strong>HR</p>
<p><strong>MAIN DUTIES/RESPONSIBILITIES: </strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Responsible on updating HR and payroll system</li>
<li>Record related to employment, hiring ,attendance, promoting, and terminating</li>
<li>Maintains personnel files in compliance with applicable ISO requirements.</li>
<li>Ensuring new hire paperwork is completed and processed</li>
<li>Overseeing hiring process, which includes coordinating job posts, reviewing &amp; short listed resumes, conducting interviews and contracting</li>
<li>Informing job applicants of job duties, responsibilities, benefits, schedules, working conditions, promotion opportunities, etc,administering pre-employment tests &amp; updating job description</li>
<li>Explaining human resources policies, procedures, laws, and standards to new and existing employees</li>
<li>Administering on-the-job training programs</li>
<li>Conducting training sessions</li>
<li>Evaluating the effectiveness of training programs</li>
<li>Maintaining records of employee participation in all training and development programs</li>
<li>Addressing any employment relations issues, such as work complaints and harassment allegations</li>
<li>Overseeing engagement programs and other employee relations work</li>
<li>Assist in establishing &amp; executing recognition programs, to carryout exit leave interviews, to assist in employee surveys.</li>
<li>Carry out administration work e.g. filing forms, logs…etc</li>
<li>Processing all personnel action forms and ensuring proper approval</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>SKILLS &amp; EXPERIENCE </strong></p>
<p><strong>Qualifications:  </strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Bachelor’s degree in business administration, human resources or a relevant field.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Experience: </strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Minimum of 1 year of job-related experience in HR.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Skills:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Skills related to interpersonal communication: listening, speaking and writing.</li>
<li>Time and Priority Management.</li>
<li>Strong computer skills.</li>
<li>Excellent written and verbal communication skills.</li>
<li>Ability to maintain a high level of confidentiality.</li>
<li>Fluent in Arabic and advanced level of English language is a must.</li>
<li>Critical thinking skills.</li>
<li>Knowledge of labor and employment law, organizational development and best practices.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Apply now:</strong></p>
<p>Send your CV&#8217;s to <strong><a href="mailto:Vacancies@alwadi.ly">Vacancies@alwadi.ly</a></strong></p><p>The post <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly/en/jobs/hr-specialist-2800098123-new/">HR Specialist New</a> first appeared on <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly/en/">Libyanjobs</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
				<company>Alwadi Communications</company>
		<job_address>Tripoli - Libya</job_address>
		<job_category>Human Resources</job_category>
	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>