<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Jobs - Libyanjobs</title>
	<atom:link href="https://libyanjobs.ly/en/jobs/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://libyanjobs.ly/en/</link>
	<description>Libyan Job Site</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Jan 2022 15:43:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://media.libyanjobs.ly/uploads/2021/02/cropped-Jobs_Fav-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Jobs - Libyanjobs</title>
	<link>https://libyanjobs.ly/en/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>3 Job Vacancies</title>
		<link>https://libyanjobs.ly/en/jobs/3-job-vacancies/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[mohamed]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Jan 2022 15:43:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://libyanjobs.ly/?post_type=noo_job&#038;p=247949</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#160; Generic Job Opening Field Security Assistant UNSMIL-LL4-GJO003/2022 Field Security AssistantApplication period:27 Jan 2022 to 25 Feb 2022  Download PDF (602.02 KB) Title: Field Security Assistant Level / Type: LL-4 Duty Station:                                    Tripoli Section: Integrated Security Workforce Date of Issue:                                    27 January 2022 Deadline for applications: 25 February 2022 Women candidates are strongly encouraged to apply to the mentioned position HOW TO APPLY: ANY</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly/en/jobs/3-job-vacancies/">3 Job Vacancies</a> first appeared on <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly/en/">Libyanjobs</a>.</p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&nbsp;</p>
<ul>
<li style="list-style-type: none;">
<ul>
<li><a href="https://unsmil.unmissions.org/sites/default/files/va_-_field_security_assistant_-_ll-4.gjo003.2022-_tripoli_libya.pdf">Generic Job Opening Field Security Assistant UNSMIL-LL4-GJO003/2022 Field Security Assistant</a><b>Application period:</b>27 Jan 2022 to 25 Feb 2022</li>
<li> <a href="https://unsmil.unmissions.org/file/11210/download?token=Bjn11q7y">Download PDF</a> (602.02 KB)</li>
<li>
<div>
<table>
<tbody>
<tr>
<td><b><strong>Title:</strong></b></td>
<td>Field Security Assistant</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><b><strong>Level / Type:</strong></b></td>
<td>LL-4</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><b><strong>Duty Station:                                   </strong></b></td>
<td>Tripoli</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><b><strong>Section:</strong></b></td>
<td>Integrated Security Workforce</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><b><strong>Date of Issue:                                   </strong></b></td>
<td>27 January 2022</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><b><strong>Deadline for applications:</strong></b></td>
<td>25 February 2022</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
</div>
<div>
<table>
<tbody>
<tr>
<td><b><strong><u>Women candidates are strongly encouraged to apply to the mentioned position</u></strong></b></td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
</div>
<p><b><strong>HOW TO APPLY:</strong></b> <b><strong>ANY APPLICATIONS RECEIVED IN A FORMAT DIFFERENT TO THE UNITED NATIONS PERSONAL HISTORY FORM (P.11) WILL NOT BE CONSIDERED.</strong></b><b><strong>ORGANIZATIONAL SETTING AND REPORTING:</strong></b>On 30 September 2021, the Security Council renewed the mandate of United Nations Support Mission in Libya (UNSMIL) until 31 January 2022, through resolution 2599 (2021). The Security Council has tasked UNSMIL, as an integrated special political Mission, in full accordance with the principles of national ownership, to exercise mediation and through its good offices to: (i) further an inclusive political process and security and economic dialogue; (ii) further the continued implementation of the Libya Political Agreement; (iii) help consolidate the governance, security and economic arrangements of the Government of National Accord, including support for economic reform in collaboration with international financial institutions; (iv) help to achieve a ceasefire and, once it is agreed by the Libyan parties, provide appropriate support to its implementation; (v) support subsequent phases of the Libyan transition process, including the constitutional process and the organization of elections; (vi) coordinate and engage closely with international actors including neighboring countries and regional organizations; (vii) provide support to key Libyan institutions; (viii) support, on request, the provision of essential services and delivery of humanitarian assistance, including in response to the COVID-19 pandemic, in accordance with humanitarian principles; (ix) monitor and report abuses and violations of human rights and violations of international humanitarian law, including sexual violence in conflict, notably through the effective deployment of women and child protection advisers; (x) provide support in securing uncontrolled arms and related materiel and countering their proliferation; and (xi) co-ordinate international assistance, and provision of advice and assistance to Government-led efforts to stabilize post-conflict zones, including those liberated from Da’esh. The Security Council, through resolution 2570 (2021), tasked UNSMIL to provide support to the Libyan-led and Libyan-owned ceasefire monitoring mechanism including through the facilitation of confidence-building measures and the scalable and incremental deployment of UNSMIL ceasefire monitors.<b><strong>Responsibilities:</strong></b> Within delegated authority, the Field Security Assistant may be responsible for the following duties:</p>
<div>
<ul>
<li>Provides general administrative support services in order to assist the Security Officers fulfill their duties vis-à-vis staff members and their dependents.</li>
<li>Assists with data consolidation and dissemination of relevant security information required for the analysis of the security situation by the Chief Security Information and Operations Center, Senior Operations Officer, and Security Officers.</li>
<li>Assists the Security Officers in the Security Operations Center with the preparations of security related documents including Security Plans, and other reports related to the security section activities as well as providing the Operations Center with administrative assistance.</li>
<li>Drafts correspondence and maintains records for the Security Training Courses delivered to security and field mission’s personnel.</li>
<li>Provides support during the implementation of the Security Plan under the directions of the Chief Security Officer.</li>
<li>Assists in reviewing the logistics requirements and other related actions required for the preparation of training courses, drills and other security exercises.</li>
<li>Assists in implementing the required security measures for UN missions and activities.</li>
<li>Assists with liaison and coordination with Host government representatives and other security counterparts.</li>
<li>Monitors and facilitates the implementation of security policies and procedures in close coordination with the security operation units’ supervisors and others.</li>
<li>Provides support in organizing and conducting security awareness and preparedness activities, and provides security orientation to newly assigned staff members, as well as conduction security briefings, as required.</li>
<li>Escort UN missions and staff members when required.</li>
<li>Assists with the preparation of the Induction Training courses, related presentations and documents.</li>
<li>When and if required, prepares security presentations for the Chief SIOC and the Operations Officers.</li>
</ul>
</div>
<p><b><strong>Professionalism: </strong></b>Shows pride in work and in achievements; demonstrates professional competence and mastery of subject matter; is conscientious and efficient in meeting commitments, observing deadlines and achieving results; is motivated by professional rather than personal concerns; shows persistence when faced with difficult problems or challenges; remains calm in stressful situations. Commitment to implementing the goal of gender equality by ensuring the equal participation and full involvement of women and men in all aspects of work.<b><strong>Accountability</strong></b>: Takes ownership of all responsibilities and honors commitments; Delivers outputs for which one has responsibility within prescribed time, cost and quality standards, operates in compliance with organizational rules and regulations, supports subordinates, provides oversight and takes responsibility for delegated assignments; takes personal responsibility for his/her own shortcomings and those of work unit, where applicable.<b><strong>Education: </strong></b>High school diploma or equivalent is required. Specialized Security training/courses are desirable.Experience in close protection services is desirable.<b><strong>Language</strong></b>: English and French are the working languages of the United Nations Secretariat. For the position advertised, fluency in English and Arabic is required.<b><strong>ASSESMENT:</strong></b> The purpose of this job opening is to generate a list of qualified candidates for inclusion in the Field Security Assistant, GS4 roster. Successful candidates will be placed on the roster and subsequently will be considered for available Field Security Assistant, GS4 positions open only to roster members. Roster membership does not guarantee selection.An appointment shall not be granted to a person who is the father, mother, son, daughter, brother, sister, stepchildren or step sibling of a staff member. This restriction applies to relationships within the United Nations Secretariat and not to those with the separately administered Agencies, Funds or Programmes.40% of the daily work is office work. While 60% of work requires physical effort: moving through the compound and escorting the Security Officers.Due to the high volume of applications received, ONLY those applicants who are short-listed will be notified.<b><strong><u>Incomplete applications or applications received after the deadline will not be considered.</u></strong></b>THE UNITED NATIONS DOES NOT CHARGE A FEE AT ANY STAGE OF THE RECRUITMENT PROCESS (APPLICATION, INTERVIEW MEETING, PROCESSING, OR TRAINING). THE UNITED NATIONS DOES NOT CONCERN ITSELF WITH INFORMATION ON APPLICANTS’ BANK ACCOUNTS.</li>
<li></li>
<li></li>
<li></li>
<li>The incumbent will be required to work in the Security Section in the field mission. The incumbent is required to use: Computers, Fax, photocopier, VHF and radios at the Security Operation Centre.</li>
<li><b><strong>ADDITIONAL INFORMATION:</strong></b></li>
<li>Recruitment in the General Service category shall be made in the country or within commuting distance of each office, irrespective of their nationality and of the length of time they may have been in the country and shall comply with any host country agreement in effect. Applicants who are not nationals from Libya must meet the relevant employment requirements of the host country, including fulfilling visa or work permit stipulations.</li>
<li><b><strong>SPECIAL NOTICE:</strong></b></li>
<li>Evaluation of qualified candidates may include an assessment exercise which may be followed by a competency-based interview.</li>
<li></li>
<li>Experience in drafting reports and in organizing meetings is desirable.</li>
<li><b><strong>Experience</strong></b>: A minimum of three (3) years of progressively responsible experience in Security or related areas such as Police and Military experience is required.</li>
<li><b><strong>QUALIFICATIONS:</strong></b></li>
<li><b><strong>Teamwork</strong></b>: Works collaboratively with colleagues to achieve organizational goals; solicits input by genuinely valuing others’ ideas and expertise; is willing to learn from others; places team agenda before personal agenda; supports and acts in accordance with final group decision, even when such decisions may not entirely reflect own position; shares credit for team accomplishments and accepts joint responsibility for team shortcomings.</li>
<li><b><strong>COMPETENCIES:</strong></b></li>
<li></li>
<li></li>
<li><b><strong>JOB DESCRIPTION:</strong></b></li>
<li>These positions are located within various Organizational Units of the Integrated Security Workforce in the United Nations Support Mission in Libya (UNSMIL). The positions are based in Tripoli, Libya. The Field Security Assistants are under the overall supervision of the Chief Security Advisor.</li>
<li><b><strong>STEP 2:</strong></b> Qualified candidates must submit their application using the P.11 template listed in STEP 1 by e-mail to unsmil-hrstaffing@un.org. The application MUST include only the Job Opening No. in the subject line of their e-mail (e.g. UNSMIL-LL4-GJO003/2022)</li>
<li>(P.11 obtainable at the following web site: (<a href="https://unsmil.unmissions.org/sites/default/files/p11-form.doc">https://unsmil.unmissions.org/sites/default/files/p11-form.doc</a>)</li>
<li><b><strong>STEP 1:</strong></b> <b><strong><u>INTERESTED APPLICANTS SHOULD SUBMIT THEIR APPLICATION USING THE UNITED NATIONS PERSONAL HISTORY FORM P.11</u></strong></b></li>
<li><a href="https://unsmil.unmissions.org/sites/default/files/va_-_field_security_radio_operator_-_ll-5.gjo001.2022.tripoli_libya.pdf">Generic Job Opening: Field Security Radio Operator UNSMIL-LL5-GJO001/2022</a><b>Application period:</b>27 Jan 2022 to 25 Feb 2022</li>
<li> <a href="https://unsmil.unmissions.org/file/11209/download?token=R52rzIep">Download PDF</a> (340.03 KB)</li>
<li>
<div>
<table>
<tbody>
<tr>
<td><b><strong>Title:</strong></b></td>
<td>Field Security Radio Operator</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><b><strong>Level/type:</strong></b></td>
<td>LL-5</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><b><strong>Duty Station:</strong></b></td>
<td>Tripoli, Libya</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><b><strong>Section:</strong></b></td>
<td>Integrated Security Workforce</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><b><strong>Date of Issue:</strong></b></td>
<td>27 January 2022</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><b><strong>Deadline for applications:</strong></b></td>
<td>25 February 2022</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
</div>
<div>
<table>
<tbody>
<tr>
<td><b><strong><u>Women candidates are strongly encouraged to apply to the mentioned position</u></strong></b></td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
</div>
<p>HOW TO APPLY:                                                                                                                             (P.11 obtainable at the following web site: <u>(</u><a href="https://unsmil.unmissions.org/sites/default/files/p11-form.doc">https://unsmil.unmissions.org/sites/default/files/p11-form.doc</a><u>)</u><b><strong>STEP 2: </strong></b>Qualified candidates must submit their application using the P.11 template listed in STEP 1 by e- mail to unsmil-hrstaffing@un.org<u>.</u>The application MUST include only the Job Opening No. in the subject line of their e-mail (e.g. UNSMIL-LL-5-GJO001/2022)This post is located within the Integrated Security Workforce of the United Nations Support Mission in Libya (UNSMIL). The post is located in Tripoli, Libya. The incumbent will be under the overall supervision of the Chief Security Adviser. JOB DESCRIPTION:</p>
<div>
<ul>
<li>Conducts radio checks with all Security Guards on duty daily.</li>
<li>Conducts radio checks with all International Security Officers at designated hours daily (including weekends and holidays).Assesses issues which can affect service delivery and reports them to the attention of the supervisor.</li>
<li>Conducts radio checks with all International Staff and Re-locatable National Staff including UN Agencies and Visitors at designated hours daily.</li>
<li>Monitors the various radio channels and reports all security incidents to the Security Duty Officer.</li>
<li>Broadcasts all security related information to the Mission Staff Members via the various radio channels as directed by OIC Guard Force Management/Security Duty Officer.</li>
<li>Provides necessary assistance to all UN staff and staff of other affiliated organizations who may need security assistance through radio channels or telephone.</li>
<li>Advises all radio users who stray to the security channel with matters not related to security to switch to the proper channel.</li>
<li>Responds to all telephone calls coming into the radio room and directs the person to the appropriate section.</li>
<li>Maintains control of all spare keys to mission offices. Registers the withdrawal and return of all keys in the key register logbook. Maintains the key control register.</li>
<li>Records and maintains all activities occurring during his/her shifts.</li>
<li>Maintains an updated list of all emergency contact numbers.</li>
<li>Maintains the telephone numbers and call signs of all senior security personnel, International and National Staff including UN Agencies and Visitors.</li>
<li>Creates and maintains familiarity with the weekly/monthly duty rosters for the various sections within the mission.</li>
<li>Maintains all equipment assigned to the radio room.</li>
<li>Reports any damages of any equipment assigned to the radio room and arranges for the repairs of such equipment.</li>
<li>Supervises the daily work and tasks provided by the head of SOC.</li>
</ul>
</div>
<p>•Prepares the monthly roster for all RROs before sending the final one to the HR after the end of each month.</p>
<div>
<ul>
<li>Updates the Movement Statistics System.</li>
<li>Updates the Overall Radio Check system.</li>
<li>Updates the system for daily Staff member&#8217;s radio check per day</li>
<li>Assists the Finance department with preparation the monthly cost recovery report for all agencies.</li>
<li>Performs other duties as directed by the Supervisor.</li>
</ul>
</div>
<div>
<table>
<tbody>
<tr>
<td></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td></td>
<td></td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
</div>
<p><b><strong>Planning and Organizing</strong></b>: Develops clear goals that are consistent with agreed strategies; Identifies priority activities and assignments; Adjusts priorities as required; Allocates appropriate amount of time and resources for completing work;Foresees risks and allows for contingencies when planning; Monitors and adjusts plans and actions as necessary; Uses timeefficiently.</p>
<div>
<table>
<tbody>
<tr>
<td></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td></td>
<td></td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
</div>
<p><b><strong>Accountability</strong></b>: Takes ownership of all responsibilities and honors commitments; Delivers outputs for which one has responsibility within prescribed time, cost and quality standards, operates in compliance with organizational rules and regulations, supports subordinates, provides oversight and takes responsibility for delegated assignments; takes personal responsibility for his/her own shortcomings and those of work unit, where applicable.<b><strong>Experience</strong></b>:Relevant experience using UHF/HF/VHF communications system is required.Experience in Geographical Information Systems and data entry is desirable.English and French are the working languages of the United Nations Secretariat. For the position advertised, fluency in English and Arabic is required.</p>
<div>
<table>
<tbody>
<tr>
<td></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td></td>
<td></td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
</div>
<p>SPECIAL NOTICE:                                                                                                                           Recruitment in the General Service category shall be made in the country or within commuting distance of each office,irrespective of their nationality and of the length of time they may have been in the country and shall comply with any hostcountry agreement in effect. Applicants who are not nationals from Libya must meet the relevant employment requirements of the host country, including fulfilling visa or work permit stipulations. ADDITIONAL INFORMATION:                                                                                                      Main work is carried indoor and includes using radios, telephones, computers, printers, and scanners.<u>Incomplete applications or applications received after the deadline will not be considered.</u></li>
<li></li>
<li>The necessity for ensuring the highest standards of efficiency, competence and integrity remain the paramount considerations in the employment of personnel. To ensure fairness and transparency, selection will be made on a competitive basis through a selection panel.</li>
<li>Due to the high volume of applications received, ONLY those applicants who are short-listed will be notified.</li>
<li>Ability to remain calm and assist the colleagues in emergency situations, willingness to work extra hours, alertness, emotional stability, a high sense of confidentiality.</li>
<li>An appointment shall not be granted to a person who is the father, mother, son, daughter, brother, sister, stepchildren or step sibling of a staff member. This restriction applies to relationships within the United Nations Secretariat and not to those with the separately administered Agencies, Funds or Programmes.</li>
<li>The purpose of this job opening is to generate a list of qualified candidates for inclusion in the Field Security Radio Operator, GS5 roster. Successful candidates will be placed on the roster and subsequently will be considered for available Field Security Radio Operator Assistant, GS5 positions open only to roster members. Roster membership does not guarantee selection.</li>
<li>Evaluation of qualified candidates may include an assessment exercise which may be followed by a competency-based interview.</li>
<li></li>
<li><b><strong>Language</strong></b>:</li>
<li>Experience in the application of security rules, regulations, and procedures of UN, or a similar international organization including fire safety and first aid procedures, as well as standard security and safety procedures is desirable.</li>
<li>At least five (5) years of progressive experience as a Radio Operator or in related field such as Security Communication Center, Emergency Operation Center, and Quick Response Control Center, is required.</li>
<li><b><strong>Education</strong></b>: High school diploma or equivalent is required.</li>
<li><b><strong>Professionalism: </strong></b>Ability to use UHF/HF/VHF communications system, ability to remain calm and assist the colleagues in emergency situations, willingness to work extra hours, alertness, emotional stability, a high sense of confidentiality. Shows pride in work and in achievements; demonstrates professional competence and mastery of subject matter; is conscientious and efficient in meeting commitments, observing deadlines and achieving results; is motivated by professional rather than personal concerns; shows persistence when faced with difficult problems or challenges; remains calm in stressful situations. Takes responsibility for incorporating gender perspectives and ensuring the equal participation of women and men in all areas of work.</li>
<li></li>
<li>Within delegated authority, the Field Security Radio Operator will be responsible for the following duties:</li>
<li>On 30 September 2021, the Security Council renewed the mandate of United Nations Support Mission in Libya (UNSMIL) until 31 January 2022, through resolution 2599 (2021). The Security Council has tasked UNSMIL, as an integrated special political Mission, in full accordance with the principles of national ownership, to exercise mediation and through its good offices to: (i) further an inclusive political process and security and economic dialogue; (ii) further the continued implementation of the Libya Political Agreement; (iii) help consolidate the governance, security and economic arrangements of the Government of National Accord, including support for economic reform in collaboration with international financial institutions; (iv) help to achieve a ceasefire and, once it is agreed by the Libyan parties, provide appropriate support to its implementation; (v) support subsequent phases of the Libyan transition process, including the constitutional process and the organization of elections; (vi) coordinate and engage closely with international actors including neighboring countries and regional organizations; (vii) provide support to key Libyan institutions; (viii) support, on request, the provision of essential services and delivery of humanitarian assistance, including in response to the COVID-19 pandemic, in accordance with humanitarian principles; (ix) monitor and report abuses and violations of human rights and violations of international humanitarian law, including sexual violence in conflict, notably through the effective deployment of women and child protection advisers; (x) provide support in securing uncontrolled arms and related materiel and countering their proliferation; and (xi) co-ordinate international assistance, and provision of advice and assistance to Government-led efforts to stabilize post-conflict zones, including those liberated from Da’esh. The Security Council, through resolution 2570 (2021), tasked UNSMIL to provide support to the Libyan-led and Libyan-owned ceasefire monitoring mechanism including through the facilitation of confidence-building measures and the scalable and incremental deployment of UNSMIL ceasefire monitors.</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li> ORGANIZATIONAL SETTING AND REPORTING:</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li><u>ANY APPLICATIONS RECEIVED IN A FORMAT DIFFERENT TO THE UNITED NATIONS</u> <u>PERSONAL HISTORY FORM (P.11) WILL NOT BE CONSIDERED.</u></li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li><b><strong>STEP 1: <u>INTERESTED APPLICANTS SHOULD SUBMIT THEIR APPLICATION USING THE</u> <u>UNITED NATIONS PERSONAL HISTORY FORM P.11</u></strong></b></li>
<li></li>
<li><a href="https://unsmil.unmissions.org/sites/default/files/va-_field_security_radio_operator_-_ll-4.gjo002.2022.tripoli.libya_.pdf">Generic Job Opening Field Security Radio Operator UNSMIL-LL4-GJO002/2022</a><b>Application period:</b>27 Jan 2022 to 25 Feb 2022</li>
<li> <a href="https://unsmil.unmissions.org/file/11208/download?token=GbFJMZsE">Download PDF</a> (573.88 KB)</li>
<li>
<div>
<table>
<tbody>
<tr>
<td><b><strong>Title:</strong></b></td>
<td>Field Security Assistant</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><b><strong>Level / Type:</strong></b></td>
<td>LL-4</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><b><strong>Duty Station:                                   </strong></b></td>
<td>Tripoli</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><b><strong>Section:</strong></b></td>
<td>Integrated Security Workforce</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><b><strong>Date of Issue:                                   </strong></b></td>
<td>27 January 2022</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><b><strong>Deadline for applications:</strong></b></td>
<td>25 February 2022</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
</div>
<div>
<table>
<tbody>
<tr>
<td><b><strong><u>Women candidates are strongly encouraged to apply to the mentioned position</u></strong></b></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><b><strong>HOW TO APPLY:</strong></b></p>
<p><b><strong>STEP 1:</strong></b> <b><strong><u>INTERESTED APPLICANTS SHOULD SUBMIT THEIR APPLICATION USING THE UNITED NATIONS PERSONAL HISTORY FORM P.11</u></strong></b></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>(P.11 obtainable at the following web site: (<a href="https://unsmil.unmissions.org/sites/default/files/p11-form.doc">https://unsmil.unmissions.org/sites/default/files/p11-form.doc</a>)</p>
<p><b><strong>ANY APPLICATIONS RECEIVED IN A FORMAT DIFFERENT TO THE UNITED NATIONS PERSONAL HISTORY FORM (P.11) WILL NOT BE CONSIDERED.</strong></b></p>
<p><b><strong>STEP 2:</strong></b> Qualified candidates must submit their application using the P.11 template listed in STEP 1 by e-mail to unsmil-hrstaffing@un.org. The application MUST include only the Job Opening No. in the subject line of their e-mail (e.g. UNSMIL-LL4-GJO003/2022)</p>
<p><b><strong>ORGANIZATIONAL SETTING AND REPORTING:</strong></b></p>
<p>These positions are located within various Organizational Units of the Integrated Security Workforce in the United Nations Support Mission in Libya (UNSMIL). The positions are based in Tripoli, Libya. The Field Security Assistants are under the overall supervision of the Chief Security Advisor.</p>
<p>On 30 September 2021, the Security Council renewed the mandate of United Nations Support Mission in Libya (UNSMIL) until 31 January 2022, through resolution 2599 (2021). The Security Council has tasked UNSMIL, as an integrated special political Mission, in full accordance with the principles of national ownership, to exercise mediation and through its good offices to: (i) further an inclusive political process and security and economic dialogue; (ii) further the continued implementation of the Libya Political Agreement; (iii) help consolidate the governance, security and economic arrangements of the Government of National Accord, including support for economic reform in collaboration with international financial institutions; (iv) help to achieve a ceasefire and, once it is agreed by the Libyan parties, provide appropriate support to its implementation; (v) support subsequent phases of the Libyan transition process, including the constitutional process and the organization of elections; (vi) coordinate and engage closely with international actors including neighboring countries and regional organizations; (vii) provide support to key Libyan institutions; (viii) support, on request, the provision of essential services and delivery of humanitarian assistance, including in response to the COVID-19 pandemic, in accordance with humanitarian principles; (ix) monitor and report abuses and violations of human rights and violations of international humanitarian law, including sexual violence in conflict, notably through the effective deployment of women and child protection advisers; (x) provide support in securing uncontrolled arms and related materiel and countering their proliferation; and (xi) co-ordinate international assistance, and provision of advice and assistance to Government-led efforts to stabilize post-conflict zones, including those liberated from Da’esh. The Security Council, through resolution 2570 (2021), tasked UNSMIL to provide support to the Libyan-led and Libyan-owned ceasefire monitoring mechanism including through the facilitation of confidence-building measures and the scalable and incremental deployment of UNSMIL ceasefire monitors.</p>
<p><b><strong>JOB DESCRIPTION:</strong></b></p>
<p><b><strong>Responsibilities:</strong></b> Within delegated authority, the Field Security Assistant may be responsible for the following duties:</p>
<ul>
<li>Provides general administrative support services in order to assist the Security Officers fulfill their duties vis-à-vis staff members and their dependents.</li>
<li>Assists with data consolidation and dissemination of relevant security information required for the analysis of the security situation by the Chief Security Information and Operations Center, Senior Operations Officer, and Security Officers.</li>
<li>Assists the Security Officers in the Security Operations Center with the preparations of security related documents including Security Plans, and other reports related to the security section activities as well as providing the Operations Center with administrative assistance.</li>
<li>Drafts correspondence and maintains records for the Security Training Courses delivered to security and field mission’s personnel.</li>
<li>Provides support during the implementation of the Security Plan under the directions of the Chief Security Officer.</li>
<li>Assists in reviewing the logistics requirements and other related actions required for the preparation of training courses, drills and other security exercises.</li>
<li>Assists in implementing the required security measures for UN missions and activities.</li>
<li>Assists with liaison and coordination with Host government representatives and other security counterparts.</li>
<li>Monitors and facilitates the implementation of security policies and procedures in close coordination with the security operation units’ supervisors and others.</li>
<li>Provides support in organizing and conducting security awareness and preparedness activities, and provides security orientation to newly assigned staff members, as well as conduction security briefings, as required.</li>
<li>Escort UN missions and staff members when required.</li>
<li>Assists with the preparation of the Induction Training courses, related presentations and documents.</li>
<li>When and if required, prepares security presentations for the Chief SIOC and the Operations Officers.</li>
</ul>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><b><strong>COMPETENCIES:</strong></b></p>
<p><b><strong>Professionalism: </strong></b>Shows pride in work and in achievements; demonstrates professional competence and mastery of subject matter; is conscientious and efficient in meeting commitments, observing deadlines and achieving results; is motivated by professional rather than personal concerns; shows persistence when faced with difficult problems or challenges; remains calm in stressful situations. Commitment to implementing the goal of gender equality by ensuring the equal participation and full involvement of women and men in all aspects of work.</p>
<p><b><strong>Teamwork</strong></b>: Works collaboratively with colleagues to achieve organizational goals; solicits input by genuinely valuing others’ ideas and expertise; is willing to learn from others; places team agenda before personal agenda; supports and acts in accordance with final group decision, even when such decisions may not entirely reflect own position; shares credit for team accomplishments and accepts joint responsibility for team shortcomings.</p>
<p><b><strong>Accountability</strong></b>: Takes ownership of all responsibilities and honors commitments; Delivers outputs for which one has responsibility within prescribed time, cost and quality standards, operates in compliance with organizational rules and regulations, supports subordinates, provides oversight and takes responsibility for delegated assignments; takes personal responsibility for his/her own shortcomings and those of work unit, where applicable.</p>
<p><b><strong>QUALIFICATIONS:</strong></b></p>
<p><b><strong>Education: </strong></b>High school diploma or equivalent is required. Specialized Security training/courses are desirable.</p>
<p><b><strong>Experience</strong></b>: A minimum of three (3) years of progressively responsible experience in Security or related areas such as Police and Military experience is required.</p>
<p>Experience in close protection services is desirable.</p>
<p>Experience in drafting reports and in organizing meetings is desirable.</p>
<p><b><strong>Language</strong></b>: English and French are the working languages of the United Nations Secretariat. For the position advertised, fluency in English and Arabic is required.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><b><strong>ASSESMENT:</strong></b></p>
<p>Evaluation of qualified candidates may include an assessment exercise which may be followed by a competency-based interview.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><b><strong>SPECIAL NOTICE:</strong></b></p>
<p>The purpose of this job opening is to generate a list of qualified candidates for inclusion in the Field Security Assistant, GS4 roster. Successful candidates will be placed on the roster and subsequently will be considered for available Field Security Assistant, GS4 positions open only to roster members. Roster membership does not guarantee selection.</p>
<p>Recruitment in the General Service category shall be made in the country or within commuting distance of each office, irrespective of their nationality and of the length of time they may have been in the country and shall comply with any host country agreement in effect. Applicants who are not nationals from Libya must meet the relevant employment requirements of the host country, including fulfilling visa or work permit stipulations.</p>
<p>An appointment shall not be granted to a person who is the father, mother, son, daughter, brother, sister, stepchildren or step sibling of a staff member. This restriction applies to relationships within the United Nations Secretariat and not to those with the separately administered Agencies, Funds or Programmes.</p>
<p><b><strong>ADDITIONAL INFORMATION:</strong></b></p>
<p>40% of the daily work is office work. While 60% of work requires physical effort: moving through the compound and escorting the Security Officers.</p>
<p>The incumbent will be required to work in the Security Section in the field mission. The incumbent is required to use: Computers, Fax, photocopier, VHF and radios at the Security Operation Centre.</p>
<p>Due to the high volume of applications received, ONLY those applicants who are short-listed will be notified.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><b><strong><u>Incomplete applications or applications received after the deadline will not be considered.</u></strong></b></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>THE UNITED NATIONS DOES NOT CHARGE A FEE AT ANY STAGE OF THE RECRUITMENT PROCESS (APPLICATION, INTERVIEW MEETING, PROCESSING, OR TRAINING). THE UNITED NATIONS DOES NOT CONCERN ITSELF WITH INFORMATION ON APPLICANTS’ BANK ACCOUNTS.</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
</div>
</li>
</ul><p>The post <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly/en/jobs/3-job-vacancies/">3 Job Vacancies</a> first appeared on <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly/en/">Libyanjobs</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
				<company>The United Nations Support Mission in Libya (UNSMIL)</company>
		<job_address>Tripoli</job_address>
		<job_category>organization</job_category>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Field Security Radio Operator</title>
		<link>https://libyanjobs.ly/en/jobs/field-security-radio-operator/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[mohamed]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Jan 2022 15:41:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://libyanjobs.ly/?post_type=noo_job&#038;p=247948</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Generic Job Opening: Field Security Radio Operator UNSMIL-LL5-GJO001/2022 Title: Field Security Radio Operator Level/type: LL-5 Duty Station: Tripoli, Libya Section: Integrated Security Workforce Date of Issue: 27 January 2022 Deadline for applications: 25 February 2022 Women candidates are strongly encouraged to apply to the mentioned position JOB DESCRIPTION: Within delegated authority, the Field Security Radio Operator will be responsible for</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly/en/jobs/field-security-radio-operator/">Field Security Radio Operator</a> first appeared on <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly/en/">Libyanjobs</a>.</p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div>
<h3><a href="https://unsmil.unmissions.org/sites/default/files/va_-_field_security_radio_operator_-_ll-5.gjo001.2022.tripoli_libya.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Generic Job Opening: Field Security Radio Operator UNSMIL-LL5-GJO001/2022</a></h3>
</div>
<div class="field-body">
<table class="Table">
<tbody>
<tr>
<td>
<p class="TableParagraph"><b>Title:</b></p>
</td>
<td>
<p class="TableParagraph">Field Security Radio Operator</p>
</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>
<p class="TableParagraph"><b>Level/type:</b></p>
</td>
<td>
<p class="TableParagraph">LL-5</p>
</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>
<p class="TableParagraph"><b>Duty Station:</b></p>
</td>
<td>
<p class="TableParagraph">Tripoli, Libya</p>
</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>
<p class="TableParagraph"><b>Section:</b></p>
</td>
<td>
<p class="TableParagraph">Integrated Security Workforce</p>
</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>
<p class="TableParagraph"><b>Date of Issue:</b></p>
</td>
<td>
<p class="TableParagraph">27 January 2022</p>
</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>
<p class="TableParagraph"><b>Deadline for applications:</b></p>
</td>
<td>
<p class="TableParagraph">25 February 2022</p>
</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
<table class="Table">
<tbody>
<tr>
<td>
<p class="TableParagraph"><b><u>Women candidates are strongly encouraged to apply to the mentioned position</u></b></p>
</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
</div>
<h1></h1>
<p>JOB DESCRIPTION:</p>
<p>Within delegated authority, the Field Security Radio Operator will be responsible for the following duties:</p>
<ul>
<li>Conducts radio checks with all Security Guards on duty daily.</li>
<li>Conducts radio checks with all International Security Officers at designated hours daily (including weekends and holidays).Assesses issues which can affect service delivery and reports them to the attention of the supervisor.</li>
<li>Conducts radio checks with all International Staff and Re-locatable National Staff including UN Agencies and Visitors at designated hours daily.</li>
<li>Monitors the various radio channels and reports all security incidents to the Security Duty Officer.</li>
<li>Broadcasts all security related information to the Mission Staff Members via the various radio channels as directed by OIC Guard Force Management/Security Duty Officer.</li>
<li>Provides necessary assistance to all UN staff and staff of other affiliated organizations who may need security assistance through radio channels or telephone.</li>
<li>Advises all radio users who stray to the security channel with matters not related to security to switch to the proper channel.</li>
<li>Responds to all telephone calls coming into the radio room and directs the person to the appropriate section.</li>
<li>Maintains control of all spare keys to mission offices. Registers the withdrawal and return of all keys in the key register logbook. Maintains the key control register.</li>
<li>Records and maintains all activities occurring during his/her shifts.</li>
<li>Maintains an updated list of all emergency contact numbers.</li>
<li>Maintains the telephone numbers and call signs of all senior security personnel, International and National Staff including UN Agencies and Visitors.</li>
<li>Creates and maintains familiarity with the weekly/monthly duty rosters for the various sections within the mission.</li>
<li>Maintains all equipment assigned to the radio room.</li>
<li>Reports any damages of any equipment assigned to the radio room and arranges for the repairs of such equipment.</li>
<li>Supervises the daily work and tasks provided by the head of SOC.</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li>Prepares the monthly roster for all RROs before sending the final one to the HR after the end of each month.</li>
</ul>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<ul>
<li>Updates the Movement Statistics System.</li>
<li>Updates the Overall Radio Check system.</li>
<li>Updates the system for daily Staff member&#8217;s radio check per day</li>
<li>Assists the Finance department with preparation the monthly cost recovery report for all agencies.</li>
<li>Performs other duties as directed by the Supervisor.</li>
</ul>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><b><strong>Professionalism: </strong></b>Ability to use UHF/HF/VHF communications system, ability to remain calm and assist the colleagues in emergency situations, willingness to work extra hours, alertness, emotional stability, a high sense of confidentiality. Shows pride in work and in achievements; demonstrates professional competence and mastery of subject matter; is conscientious and efficient in meeting commitments, observing deadlines and achieving results; is motivated by professional rather than personal concerns; shows persistence when faced with difficult problems or challenges; remains calm in stressful situations. Takes responsibility for incorporating gender perspectives and ensuring the equal participation of women and men in all areas of work.</p>
<p><b><strong>Planning and Organizing</strong></b>: Develops clear goals that are consistent with agreed strategies; Identifies priority activities and assignments; Adjusts priorities as required; Allocates appropriate amount of time and resources for completing work;Foresees risks and allows for contingencies when planning; Monitors and adjusts plans and actions as necessary; Uses timeefficiently.</p>
<table>
<tbody>
<tr>
<td></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td></td>
<td></td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
<p><b><strong>Accountability</strong></b>: Takes ownership of all responsibilities and honors commitments; Delivers outputs for which one has responsibility within prescribed time, cost and quality standards, operates in compliance with organizational rules and regulations, supports subordinates, provides oversight and takes responsibility for delegated assignments; takes personal responsibility for his/her own shortcomings and those of work unit, where applicable.</p>
<p><b><strong>Education</strong></b>: High school diploma or equivalent is required.</p>
<p><b><strong>Experience</strong></b>:</p>
<p>At least five (5) years of progressive experience as a Radio Operator or in related field such as Security Communication Center, Emergency Operation Center, and Quick Response Control Center, is required.</p>
<p>Relevant experience using UHF/HF/VHF communications system is required.</p>
<p>Experience in the application of security rules, regulations, and procedures of UN, or a similar international organization including fire safety and first aid procedures, as well as standard security and safety procedures is desirable.</p>
<p>Experience in Geographical Information Systems and data entry is desirable.</p>
<p><b><strong>Language</strong></b>:</p>
<p>English and French are the working languages of the United Nations Secretariat. For the position advertised, fluency in English and Arabic is required.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Evaluation of qualified candidates may include an assessment exercise which may be followed by a competency-based interview.</p>
<h1>SPECIAL NOTICE:</h1>
<p>The purpose of this job opening is to generate a list of qualified candidates for inclusion in the Field Security Radio Operator, GS5 roster. Successful candidates will be placed on the roster and subsequently will be considered for available Field Security Radio Operator Assistant, GS5 positions open only to roster members. Roster membership does not guarantee selection.</p>
<p>Recruitment in the General Service category shall be made in the country or within commuting distance of each office,irrespective of their nationality and of the length of time they may have been in the country and shall comply with any hostcountry agreement in effect. Applicants who are not nationals from Libya must meet the relevant employment requirements of the host country, including fulfilling visa or work permit stipulations.</p>
<p>An appointment shall not be granted to a person who is the father, mother, son, daughter, brother, sister, stepchildren or step sibling of a staff member. This restriction applies to relationships within the United Nations Secretariat and not to those with the separately administered Agencies, Funds or Programmes.</p>
<h1> ADDITIONAL INFORMATION:</h1>
<p>Ability to remain calm and assist the colleagues in emergency situations, willingness to work extra hours, alertness, emotional stability, a high sense of confidentiality.</p>
<p>Main work is carried indoor and includes using radios, telephones, computers, printers, and scanners.</p>
<p>Due to the high volume of applications received, ONLY those applicants who are short-listed will be notified.</p>
<h1><u>Incomplete applications or applications received after the deadline will not be considered.</u></h1>
<p>The necessity for ensuring the highest standards of efficiency, competence and integrity remain the paramount considerations in the employment of personnel. To ensure fairness and transparency, selection will be made on a competitive basis through a selection panel.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h1><b>Application period:</b></h1>
<p style="font-weight: 400;">27 Jan 2022 to 25 Feb 2022</p>
<p style="font-weight: 400;"> <a href="https://unsmil.unmissions.org/file/11209/download?token=R52rzIep">Download PDF</a> (340.03 KB)</p>
<h1></h1>
<p><b><strong>STEP 1: <u>INTERESTED APPLICANTS SHOULD SUBMIT THEIR APPLICATION USING THE</u> <u>UNITED NATIONS PERSONAL HISTORY FORM P.11</u></strong></b></p>
<p>(P.11 obtainable at the following web site: <u>(</u><a href="https://unsmil.unmissions.org/sites/default/files/p11-form.doc">https://unsmil.unmissions.org/sites/default/files/p11-form.doc</a><u>)</u></p>
<p><u>ANY APPLICATIONS RECEIVED IN A FORMAT DIFFERENT TO THE UNITED NATIONS</u> <u>PERSONAL HISTORY FORM (P.11) WILL NOT BE CONSIDERED.</u></p>
<p><b><strong>STEP 2: </strong></b>Qualified candidates must submit their application using the P.11 template listed in STEP 1 by e- mail to <a href="mailto:unsmil-hrstaffing@un.org"><strong>unsmil-hrstaffing@un.org</strong></a><u>.</u>The application MUST include only the Job Opening No. in the subject line of their e-mail (e.g. UNSMIL-LL-5-GJO001/2022)</p><p>The post <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly/en/jobs/field-security-radio-operator/">Field Security Radio Operator</a> first appeared on <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly/en/">Libyanjobs</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
				<company>The United Nations Support Mission in Libya (UNSMIL)</company>
		<job_address>Tripoli</job_address>
		<job_category>organization</job_category>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Field Security Assistant</title>
		<link>https://libyanjobs.ly/en/jobs/field-security-assistant/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[mohamed]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Jan 2022 15:37:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://libyanjobs.ly/?post_type=noo_job&#038;p=247947</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Generic Job Opening Field Security Assistant UNSMIL-LL4-GJO003/2022 Field Security Assistant Title: Field Security Assistant Level / Type: LL-4 Duty Station:                                    Tripoli Section: Integrated Security Workforce Date of Issue:                                    27 January 2022 Deadline for applications: 25 February 2022 Women candidates are strongly encouraged to apply to the mentioned position JOB DESCRIPTION: Responsibilities: Within delegated authority, the Field Security Assistant may be responsible for</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly/en/jobs/field-security-assistant/">Field Security Assistant</a> first appeared on <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly/en/">Libyanjobs</a>.</p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li><a href="https://unsmil.unmissions.org/sites/default/files/va_-_field_security_assistant_-_ll-4.gjo003.2022-_tripoli_libya.pdf">Generic Job Opening Field Security Assistant UNSMIL-LL4-GJO003/2022 Field Security Assistant</a></li>
<li>
<div>
<table>
<tbody>
<tr>
<td><b><strong>Title:</strong></b></td>
<td>Field Security Assistant</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><b><strong>Level / Type:</strong></b></td>
<td>LL-4</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><b><strong>Duty Station:                                   </strong></b></td>
<td>Tripoli</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><b><strong>Section:</strong></b></td>
<td>Integrated Security Workforce</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><b><strong>Date of Issue:                                   </strong></b></td>
<td>27 January 2022</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><b><strong>Deadline for applications:</strong></b></td>
<td>25 February 2022</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
</div>
<div>
<table>
<tbody>
<tr>
<td><b><strong><u>Women candidates are strongly encouraged to apply to the mentioned position</u></strong></b></td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
</div>
<div class="field-body">
<p><b>JOB DESCRIPTION:</b></p>
<p><b>Responsibilities:</b> Within delegated authority, the Field Security Assistant may be responsible for the following duties:</p>
<ul>
<li>Provides general administrative support services in order to assist the Security Officers fulfill their duties vis-à-vis staff members and their dependents.</li>
<li>Assists with data consolidation and dissemination of relevant security information required for the analysis of the security situation by the Chief Security Information and Operations Center, Senior Operations Officer, and Security Officers.</li>
<li>Assists the Security Officers in the Security Operations Center with the preparations of security related documents including Security Plans, and other reports related to the security section activities as well as providing the Operations Center with administrative assistance.</li>
<li>Drafts correspondence and maintains records for the Security Training Courses delivered to security and field mission’s personnel.</li>
<li>Provides support during the implementation of the Security Plan under the directions of the Chief Security Officer.</li>
<li>Assists in reviewing the logistics requirements and other related actions required for the preparation of training courses, drills and other security exercises.</li>
<li>Assists in implementing the required security measures for UN missions and activities.</li>
<li>Assists with liaison and coordination with Host government representatives and other security counterparts.</li>
<li>Monitors and facilitates the implementation of security policies and procedures in close coordination with the security operation units’ supervisors and others.</li>
<li>Provides support in organizing and conducting security awareness and preparedness activities, and provides security orientation to newly assigned staff members, as well as conduction security briefings, as required.</li>
<li>Escort UN missions and staff members when required.</li>
<li>Assists with the preparation of the Induction Training courses, related presentations and documents.</li>
<li>When and if required, prepares security presentations for the Chief SIOC and the Operations Officers.</li>
</ul>
<p><b>COMPETENCIES:</b></p>
<p><b>Professionalism: </b>Shows pride in work and in achievements; demonstrates professional competence and mastery of subject matter; is conscientious and efficient in meeting commitments, observing deadlines and achieving results; is motivated by professional rather than personal concerns; shows persistence when faced with difficult problems or challenges; remains calm in stressful situations. Commitment to implementing the goal of gender equality by ensuring the equal participation and full involvement of women and men in all aspects of work.</p>
<p class="TableParagraph"><b>Teamwork</b>: Works collaboratively with colleagues to achieve organizational goals; solicits input by genuinely valuing others’ ideas and expertise; is willing to learn from others; places team agenda before personal agenda; supports and acts in accordance with final group decision, even when such decisions may not entirely reflect own position; shares credit for team accomplishments and accepts joint responsibility for team shortcomings.</p>
<p class="TableParagraph"><b>Accountability</b>: Takes ownership of all responsibilities and honors commitments; Delivers outputs for which one has responsibility within prescribed time, cost and quality standards, operates in compliance with organizational rules and regulations, supports subordinates, provides oversight and takes responsibility for delegated assignments; takes personal responsibility for his/her own shortcomings and those of work unit, where applicable.</p>
<p><b>QUALIFICATIONS:</b></p>
<p><b>Education: </b>High school diploma or equivalent is required. Specialized Security training/courses are desirable.</p>
<p><b>Experience</b>: A minimum of three (3) years of progressively responsible experience in Security or related areas such as Police and Military experience is required.</p>
<p>Experience in close protection services is desirable.</p>
<p>Experience in drafting reports and in organizing meetings is desirable.</p>
<p><b>Language</b>: English and French are the working languages of the United Nations Secretariat. For the position advertised, fluency in English and Arabic is required.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><b>ASSESMENT:</b></p>
<p>Evaluation of qualified candidates may include an assessment exercise which may be followed by a competency-based interview.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><b>SPECIAL NOTICE:</b></p>
<p>The purpose of this job opening is to generate a list of qualified candidates for inclusion in the Field Security Assistant, GS4 roster. Successful candidates will be placed on the roster and subsequently will be considered for available Field Security Assistant, GS4 positions open only to roster members. Roster membership does not guarantee selection.</p>
<p>Recruitment in the General Service category shall be made in the country or within commuting distance of each office, irrespective of their nationality and of the length of time they may have been in the country and shall comply with any host country agreement in effect. Applicants who are not nationals from Libya must meet the relevant employment requirements of the host country, including fulfilling visa or work permit stipulations.</p>
<p>An appointment shall not be granted to a person who is the father, mother, son, daughter, brother, sister, stepchildren or step sibling of a staff member. This restriction applies to relationships within the United Nations Secretariat and not to those with the separately administered Agencies, Funds or Programmes.</p>
<p><b>ADDITIONAL INFORMATION:</b></p>
<p>40% of the daily work is office work. While 60% of work requires physical effort: moving through the compound and escorting the Security Officers.</p>
<p>The incumbent will be required to work in the Security Section in the field mission. The incumbent is required to use: Computers, Fax, photocopier, VHF and radios at the Security Operation Centre.</p>
<p>Due to the high volume of applications received, ONLY those applicants who are short-listed will be notified.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><b><u>Incomplete applications or applications received after the deadline will not be considered.</u></b></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>THE UNITED NATIONS DOES NOT CHARGE A FEE AT ANY STAGE OF THE RECRUITMENT PROCESS (APPLICATION, INTERVIEW MEETING, PROCESSING, OR TRAINING). THE UNITED NATIONS DOES NOT CONCERN ITSELF WITH INFORMATION ON APPLICANTS’ BANK ACCOUNTS.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
</div>
<p><span class="left bold">Application period:</span></p>
<div class="field-expiration-date"><span class="date-display-range"><span class="date-display-start">27 Jan 2022</span> to <span class="date-display-end">25 Feb 2022</span></span></div>
<div class="field-pdf"><span class="file"><img class="file-icon" title="application/pdf" src="https://unsmil.unmissions.org/modules/file/icons/application-pdf.png" alt="PDF icon" /> <a href="https://unsmil.unmissions.org/file/11210/download?token=Bjn11q7y" type="application/pdf; length=616472">Download PDF</a> <span class="file-size">(602.02 KB)</span></span></div>
</li>
</ul>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p style="font-weight: 400;"><b><strong>HOW TO APPLY:</strong></b></p>
<p style="font-weight: 400;"><b><strong>STEP 1:</strong></b> <b><strong><u>INTERESTED APPLICANTS SHOULD SUBMIT THEIR APPLICATION USING THE UNITED NATIONS PERSONAL HISTORY FORM P.11</u></strong></b></p>
<p style="font-weight: 400;">
<p style="font-weight: 400;">(P.11 obtainable at the following web site: (<a href="https://unsmil.unmissions.org/sites/default/files/p11-form.doc">https://unsmil.unmissions.org/sites/default/files/p11-form.doc</a>)</p>
<p style="font-weight: 400;"><b><strong>ANY APPLICATIONS RECEIVED IN A FORMAT DIFFERENT TO THE UNITED NATIONS PERSONAL HISTORY FORM (P.11) WILL NOT BE CONSIDERED.</strong></b></p>
<p style="font-weight: 400;"><b><strong>STEP 2:</strong></b> Qualified candidates must submit their application using the P.11 template listed in STEP 1 by e-mail to <strong><a href="mailto:unsmil-hrstaffing@un.org">unsmil-hrstaffing@un.org</a></strong>. The application MUST include only the Job Opening No. in the subject line of their e-mail (e.g. UNSMIL-LL4-GJO003/2022)</p><p>The post <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly/en/jobs/field-security-assistant/">Field Security Assistant</a> first appeared on <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly/en/">Libyanjobs</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
				<company>The United Nations Support Mission in Libya (UNSMIL)</company>
		<job_address>Tripoli</job_address>
		<job_category>organization</job_category>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Senior IP Engineer</title>
		<link>https://libyanjobs.ly/en/jobs/senior-ip-engineer/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[mohamed]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Jan 2022 10:41:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://libyanjobs.ly/?post_type=noo_job&#038;p=247939</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>About the job Key Responsibilities :- Customer Engagement Solution Design Internal &#38; External Stakeholder Engagement Customer Proposal Access Price/Supplier Negotiation Order Form Creation Order Form Processing Supplier &#38; Customer) Stakeholder in MSA Review and Partner onboarding &#160; Presales ‐ Solution Develop, design and implement solutions for our customers telecommunications &#38; ICT requirements Interface between sales and the rest of GBI</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly/en/jobs/senior-ip-engineer/">Senior IP Engineer</a> first appeared on <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly/en/">Libyanjobs</a>.</p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div id="job-details" class="jobs-box__html-content jobs-description-content__text t-14 t-normal
          " tabindex="-1" data-artdeco-is-focused="true"></p>
<h2 class="mt5 t-20 t-bold mb4">About the job</h2>
<p><strong>Key Responsibilities :-</strong></p>
<p>Customer Engagement</p>
<p>Solution Design</p>
<p>Internal &amp; External Stakeholder Engagement</p>
<p>Customer Proposal</p>
<p>Access Price/Supplier Negotiation</p>
<p>Order Form Creation</p>
<p>Order Form Processing Supplier &amp; Customer)</p>
<p>Stakeholder in MSA Review and Partner onboarding</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Presales ‐ Solution</strong></p>
<p>Develop, design and implement solutions for our customers telecommunications &amp; ICT requirements</p>
<p>Interface between sales and the rest of GBI to provide the necessary solution</p>
<p>End to End owner of a sales opportunity to deliver the best in class solution to maximize win probability</p>
<p>Engage commercial, technical, legal, financial stakeholders to get necessary sign off for the offer</p>
<p>Ensure proper handover to delivery team with necessary documentation, support, sign off to kick start the project</p>
<p>Provide support when needed during the lifecycle of the project (through change management)</p>
<p>Manage the day‐to‐day operations of the Bid Assigned</p>
<p>Conduct sales bidding process and develop selection criteria and methodology for each stage of the evaluation process</p>
<p>Manage the commercial and technical aspect of the bidders including negotiations</p>
<p>Maintain a strong relationship with strategic partners and keep them informed of additional business opportunities</p>
<p>Act as the link between the technical, sales and marketing functions during the pre‐sales and bid process</p>
<p>Direct customers on solutions and propositions</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Presales – Access Management</strong></p>
<p>Provides Access Pricing and Solution for Customer Projects</p>
<p>Maintains an up‐to‐date database of submarine cable &amp; access network availability and pricing.</p>
<p>Assists in procurement of capacity in order to optimize technological parameters and priorities of GBI Projects.</p>
<p>Verifies the invoices of capacity purchase for certification and maintains database of certified payments.</p>
<p>Verify the agreements and coordinate with contracts.</p>
<p>Updates and maintains database for the availability and pricing details of all submarine cable and Partner Access Networks.</p>
<p>Closely coordinates with other teams within Presales and suppliers for new capacity purchase and closures.</p>
<p>Prepare Conversion Forms/ SOF etc. to facilitate the activation of capacity</p>
<p>Verifies invoices of capacity purchases and certification of invoices for payments; maintains database of payments certified.</p>
<p>Assist in preparing the capacity dashboard in all existing cables and Access.</p>
<p>Performs any other related duties as required.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Education and Experience:</strong></p>
<p>Have a Bachelor degree from recognized educational institutions. Preferred disciplines include: Engineering, computing and Business degree.</p>
<p>Have 6-9 years of Global Solutions and Pricing experience in Telecommunications industry.</p>
<p>Have experience and understanding of cost models and cost saving execution.</p>
<p>Have proven understanding of any Telco domain, including Fixed Network, Transmission/Transport, SDWAN, IOT &amp; IP technologies.</p>
<p>Have proven success managing telco Customers and international contracts.</p>
<p>Have the ability to confidently interact, communicate and collaborate effectively with stakeholders across key business functions.</p>
<p>Have intermediate-level proficiency in Microsoft Excel.</p>
<p>Be able to maintain high personal and professional standards.</p>
<p>Have the ability to work in a dynamic/fast paced environment, high level of autonomy.</p>
<p>Have excellent written and oral presentation skills.</p>
<p>Have good understanding of different product solutions and map Customer requirement’s within the Product offerings, to cater to Customer needs with optimized cost.</p>
<p>Be willing to challenge ‘business as usual’; curiosity to think ‘outside the box’ and passion for driving improvements. Ability to be creative to meet business needs, but also pragmatic and results oriented.</p>
<p>Be able to adjust communications style to different audiences.</p>
<p>Have sound judgment and decision making among competing demands.</p>
<p>For the applicate that fit job profile , please  send it directly to recruiter email . <a href="mailto:Libyainterns@huawei.com"><strong>Libyainterns@huawei.com</strong></a></p>
</div>
<div class="jobs-description__details">
<div class="jobs-poster
    mt4 

    "></p>
<div class="jobs-poster__info-container mb4">
<p class="jobs-poster__name name t-16 t-black t-bold mb0">
<p class="jobs-poster__headline t-16 t-black--light t-normal mb0">HR deputy at Huawei</p>
</div>
<div class="jobs-poster__action-container jobs-box--fadein"></div>
</div>
</div><p>The post <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly/en/jobs/senior-ip-engineer/">Senior IP Engineer</a> first appeared on <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly/en/">Libyanjobs</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
				<company>Huawei Libya office</company>
		<job_address>Tripoli</job_address>
		<job_category>organization</job_category>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Senior Child Protection Manager</title>
		<link>https://libyanjobs.ly/en/jobs/senior-child-protection-manager/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[mohamed]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jan 2022 20:26:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://libyanjobs.ly/?post_type=noo_job&#038;p=247926</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Senior Child Protection Manager Tripoli, Libya Requisition ID: req23945 Job Title: Senior Child Protection Manager Sector: Child Protection Employment Category: Fixed Term Employment Type: Full-Time Open to Expatriates: Yes Location: Tripoli, Libya Job Description &#160; In April 2019, military and armed forces from the parties of the conflict engaged in armed clashes in Tripoli. Since, over 60,000 Libyans and non-Libyans have been displaced, many are still trapped</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly/en/jobs/senior-child-protection-manager/">Senior Child Protection Manager</a> first appeared on <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly/en/">Libyanjobs</a>.</p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="p-view-jobdetailsbanner">
<div>
<div class="p-panel p-bg-grey40">
<div>
<div class="p-viewSL-jobdetailsbannercontent">
<div class="p-content-wrapper">
<div class="p-panel p-p-t-sm p-p-b-md">
<div>
<div class="p-panel p-p-v-xl">
<div>
<div class="p-gridlayout center-device-none start-device-sm gutter-vertical-xs-device-none">
<div class="p-gridcol col-12-device-none">
<h1 class="p-sectionheader p-f-sz-4x p-t-light" title="Senior Child Protection Manager" data-tag="ReqTitle">Senior Child Protection Manager</h1>
</div>
<div class="p-gridcol col-12-device-none">
<div class="p-gridlayout middle-device-none gutter-horizontal-sm-device-none">
<div class="p-gridcol col-12-device-none col-auto-device-sm"><span class="p-text p-f-sz-xl p-t-light  p-f-w-n" data-tag="displayLocationMessage">Tripoli, Libya</span></div>
<div class="p-gridcol col-12-device-none col-auto-device-sm">
<div class="p-mediaquerycontainer"></div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="p-content-wrapper">
<div>
<div class="p-panel p-p-t-xs">
<div>
<div class="p-gridlayout gutter-horizontal-md-device-none gutter-vertical-sm-device-none">
<div class="p-gridcol col-12-device-none">
<div class="p-view-jobdetailsad">
<div class="p-panel p-p-b-xl">
<div>
<div id="" class="p-htmlviewer" data-tag="">
<p><span style="font-size: large;"><strong>Requisition ID:</strong> req23945</span></p>
<p><span style="font-size: large;"><strong>Job Title: </strong>Senior Child Protection Manager</span></p>
<p><span style="font-size: large;"><strong>Sector: </strong>Child Protection</span></p>
<p><span style="font-size: large;"><strong>Employment Category:</strong> Fixed Term</span></p>
<p><span style="font-size: large;"><strong>Employment Type:</strong> Full-Time</span></p>
<p><span style="font-size: large;"><strong>Open to Expatriates:</strong> Yes<br />
</span></p>
<p><strong>Location:</strong> Tripoli, Libya<span style="font-size: large;"><br />
</span></p>
<p><strong><span style="font-size: large;">Job Description</span></strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<div><span style="font-size: large;"><span style="font-size: medium;">In April 2019, military and armed forces from the parties of the conflict engaged in armed clashes in Tripoli. Since, over 60,000 Libyans and non-Libyans have been displaced, many are still trapped in the active conflict areas, and more than 1 million people in need of life-saving health care and protection services. The situation, coupled with the Covid-19 pandemic, has impacted the physical and mental wellbeing and living standards of Libyans, migrants, and refugees while exposing them to significant protection risks. The breakdown in governance structures has resulted in deterioration of public services, exacerbating existing vulnerabilities and diminishing people’s coping capacities. Children are exposed to high levels of psychosocial distress, trauma, and protection risks due to the ongoing conflict and prolonged insecurity, which has an immediate and long-term psychological and social impact for children and their caregivers who experience displacement, death of or separation from family members, discrimination, and movement restrictions: These cause negative behaviors and emotional changes in children. </span></span></div>
<div><span style="font-size: large;"><span style="font-size: medium;">At present, the IRC is conducting health, protection, and governance programming, directly and in partnership, in Tripoli and Misrata, aiming to expand its reach across the portfolio. IRC Libya’s targeted and integrated protection work focuses on Child Protection, Women’s Protection and Empowerment (including GBV prevention and response), rule of law, and MHPSS.</span></span></div>
<div><span style="font-size: large;"><strong><span style="font-size: medium;">Scope of work</span></strong></span></div>
<div><span style="font-size: large;"><span style="font-size: medium;">The Child Protection (CP) Senior Manager will report to and assist the Integrated Protection Coordinator (IPC) in setting up new and strengthening existing child protection programs for families and children vulnerable to abuse, exploitation, neglect and violence in informal settlements and urban areas. He/she will be responsible to supervise the day-to-day activities of all CP teams in the different locations in Libya, as well as the activities of newly selected partners. Moreover, the CP Senior Manager will also support the IPC in strategic decisions for child protection programs and play a key role in staff and partner capacity building.   </span></span></div>
<div><span style="font-size: large;"><strong><span style="font-size: medium;">Key responsibilities</span></strong></span></div>
<div><span style="font-size: large;"><strong><span style="font-size: medium;">Program Management (50%)</span></strong></span></div>
<div><span style="font-size: large;"><span style="font-size: medium;">• Oversee all child protection activities in the different locations where IRC is present; </span></span></div>
<div><span style="font-size: large;"><span style="font-size: medium;">• Responsible for the development and implementation of project work plans in line with the projects’ goals, objectives, staffing and budget. </span></span></div>
<div><span style="font-size: large;"><span style="font-size: medium;">• Work closely with the IPC to develop spending plans and budgets for new child protection programs; </span></span></div>
<div><span style="font-size: large;"><span style="font-size: medium;">• Develop monthly and weekly plans for all child protection activities, and any other reports according to donors’ requirement and as supervisor’s request; </span></span></div>
<div><span style="font-size: large;"><span style="font-size: medium;">• Ensure smooth implementation of daily field activities in relation to child protection and case management in accordance with the standard tools and IRC procedures; </span></span></div>
<div><span style="font-size: large;"><span style="font-size: medium;">• Ensure Child Protection Minimum Standards and Guiding Principles are abided and upheld throughout all Child Protection activities.</span></span></div>
<div><span style="font-size: large;"><span style="font-size: medium;">• Ensure case management steps, case management meetings, referrals, data protection and documentation are happening in timely, safe and quality manner, by conducting case conferences with the different teams on a regular basis;  </span></span></div>
<div><span style="font-size: large;"><span style="font-size: medium;">• Plan and monitor the procurement/distribution of new materials for all Child Protection activities as per work plans and donors’ requirements; </span></span></div>
<div><span style="font-size: large;"><span style="font-size: medium;">• Coordinate with the supply chain manager to ensure proper equipment and materials for the activities in place  </span></span></div>
<div><span style="font-size: large;"><span style="font-size: medium;">• Develop new/regular Child Protection Assessments in all IRC selected locations, including revising tools, directing the child protection staff on how to conduct these assessments and translating the finding to IPC;  </span></span></div>
<div><span style="font-size: large;"><span style="font-size: medium;">• Work together with IRC’s CP partners selected to ensure completion of activities as per donors’ proposals and plans.</span></span></div>
<div><span style="font-size: large;"><span style="font-size: medium;"> </span></span></div>
<div><span style="font-size: large;"><span style="font-size: medium;"><strong>Project Reporting (20%)</strong></span></span></div>
<div><span style="font-size: large;"><span style="font-size: medium;">• Ensure regular communication with IPC for updates on achievements, challenges, donor reports and proposals’ development;  </span></span></div>
<div><span style="font-size: large;"><span style="font-size: medium;">• Work closely with IPC and M&amp;E Team to create templates for child protection activity reports and monitoring tools, to compile qualitative and quantitative data for donors’ reports and for program quality documentation;  </span></span></div>
<div><span style="font-size: large;"><span style="font-size: medium;">• Translate and analyze regularly reports coming from inside Libya as per request from IPC;</span></span></div>
<div><span style="font-size: large;"><span style="font-size: medium;">• Review of CP partners’ donor’s reports and spending plans. </span></span></div>
<div><span style="font-size: large;"><span style="font-size: medium;"> </span></span></div>
<div><span style="font-size: large;"><strong><span style="font-size: medium;">Representation and Coordination (10%) </span></strong></span></div>
<div><span style="font-size: large;"><span style="font-size: medium;">• Represent child protection sector in relevant coordination meetings and other internal/external meetings as requested by IPC (Child Protection Sub-Sector, CP Case Management Task Force, BvA meetings, weekly protection team meetings, and weekly program meetings); </span></span></div>
<div><span style="font-size: large;"><span style="font-size: medium;">• Liaise with other child protection actors working in Libya, IRC’s Protection and WPE teams and any other relevant service provider on management of caseload and referrals;  </span></span></div>
<div><span style="font-size: large;"><span style="font-size: medium;">• In coordination with Grants Department, ensure regular coordination with CP partners for monitoring of activities, donors’ meeting and reports, and any other programmatic purpose</span></span></div>
<div><span style="font-size: large;"><span style="font-size: medium;"> </span></span></div>
<div><span style="font-size: large;"><strong><span style="font-size: medium;">Staff development/capacity building (20%) </span></strong></span></div>
<div><span style="font-size: large;"><span style="font-size: medium;">• Supervise and guide on a daily basis the Child Protection Officers, Child Protection Assistants, and Community Volunteers in charge of the child protection activities in different locations, including: setting up clear objectives for them, training them on IRC’s methodologies and Standards and ensuring they provide timely and quality daily reports of their activities and tasks; </span></span></div>
<div><span style="font-size: large;"><span style="font-size: medium;">• Gradually build the capacity of CP staff, especially direct reports, through identifying/conducting appropriate trainings, delegation of more responsibilities, etc. to ensure a smooth transition to nationalization of the position in the future; </span></span></div>
<div><span style="font-size: large;"><span style="font-size: medium;">• Maintain open and professional relations with team members, promoting a strong team spirit and providing oversight and guidance to all Child Protection team in Libya;   </span></span></div>
<div><span style="font-size: large;"><span style="font-size: medium;">• Conduct performance monitoring and reviews for the supervised staff on regular basis;</span></span></div>
<div><span style="font-size: large;"><span style="font-size: medium;">• Work closely with Capacity Building Officer to create a child protection capacity building plan for both IRC staff and the other stakeholders IRC works closely;</span></span></div>
<div><span style="font-size: large;"><span style="font-size: medium;">• Train new staff in IRC’s child protection standards and approaches, PSS activities, SOPs and case management;</span></span></div>
<div><span style="font-size: large;"><span style="font-size: medium;">• Conduct regular spot-checks in the areas of activities to ensure the SOPs are compiled by the staff;</span></span></div>
<div><span style="font-size: large;"><span style="font-size: medium;">• Train non-CP program staff on how to mainstream child protection throughout each step of program implementation;</span></span></div>
<div><span style="font-size: large;"><span style="font-size: medium;">• Create a country specific Child Protection SOP for IRC Libya’s Child Protection activities and Child Protection Mainstreaming throughout other program activities;</span></span></div>
<div><span style="font-size: large;"><span style="font-size: medium;">• Works with the CP partner organization identified to ensure donors’ requirements are met, according to child protection global standards.  </span></span></div>
<div><span style="font-size: large;"><span style="font-size: medium;"> </span></span></div>
<div><span style="font-size: large;"><span style="font-size: medium;">Any other duties as assigned by IPC. </span></span></div>
<div><span style="font-size: large;"><span style="font-size: medium;"> </span></span></div>
<div><span style="font-size: large;"><span style="font-size: medium;"><strong>Key working relationships</strong>: </span></span></div>
<div><span style="font-size: large;"><span style="font-size: medium;">Position Reports to: Integrated Protection Coordinator (IPC)</span></span></div>
<div><span style="font-size: large;"><span style="font-size: medium;">Position directly supervises: Two Child Protection Officers (Misrata and Tripoli) </span></span></div>
<div><span style="font-size: large;"><span style="font-size: medium;">Indirect Reporting: Child Protection Assistants/Caseworkers, Parenting Skills Trainers, SHLS Facilitators, and Community Volunteers</span></span></div>
<div><span style="font-size: large;"><span style="font-size: medium;"> </span></span></div>
<div><span style="font-size: large;"><span style="font-size: medium;">Other Internal and/or external contacts: </span></span></div>
<div><span style="font-size: large;"><span style="font-size: medium;">Internal: Other IRC Libya Departments (Supply Chain, Human Resources, M&amp;E, Finance, Health Programs) and other VPRU Departments (WPE and PRoL)  </span></span></div>
<div><span style="font-size: large;"><span style="font-size: medium;">External: local authorities, community members, volunteers inside of Libya, INGOs and other local charities/actors working in education, child protection and any other relevant sector  </span></span></div>
<div><span style="font-size: large;"><span style="font-size: medium;"> </span></span></div>
<div><span style="font-size: large;"><strong><span style="font-size: medium;">Job requirements </span></strong></span></div>
<div><span style="font-size: large;"><span style="font-size: medium;">• Technical diploma or degree in social sciences, social work, psychology, human rights, or related degree;  </span></span></div>
<div><span style="font-size: large;"><span style="font-size: medium;">• Minimum four years’ experience working in the field of child protection or related; at least two years in a managerial role and in conflict setting; </span></span></div>
<div><span style="font-size: large;"><span style="font-size: medium;">• Demonstrated experience and knowledge in project management (including budget management, developing spending plans, overseeing project indicators and writing donor reports); </span></span></div>
<div><span style="font-size: large;"><span style="font-size: medium;">• Previous experience in working with children with special needs or psychological distress; </span></span></div>
<div><span style="font-size: large;"><span style="font-size: medium;">• Experience in conducting training for volunteers and other staff members in PSS activities for children, or related;  </span></span></div>
<div><span style="font-size: large;"><span style="font-size: medium;">• Good understanding of child protection in emergencies;  </span></span></div>
<div><span style="font-size: large;"><span style="font-size: medium;">• Confident communicator, excellent negotiations skills;  </span></span></div>
<div><span style="font-size: large;"><span style="font-size: medium;">• Very well organized and with good reporting skills; </span></span></div>
<div><span style="font-size: large;"><span style="font-size: medium;">• Able to work under pressure;  </span></span></div>
<div><span style="font-size: large;"><span style="font-size: medium;">• Works well in teamwork, comfortable in a multi-cultural environment, flexible and able to handle pressure well</span></span></div>
<div><span style="font-size: large;"><span style="font-size: medium;">• Excellent Computer skills: MS Word and Excel  </span></span></div>
<div><span style="font-size: large;"><span style="font-size: medium;">• Fluency in English required and Arabic is highly desired </span></span></div>
<div><span style="font-size: large;"><span style="font-size: medium;">• Previous experience in INGOs </span></span></div>
<div><span style="font-size: large;"><span style="font-size: medium;"> </span></span></div>
<div><span style="font-size: large;"><strong><span style="font-size: medium;">Working environment</span></strong></span></div>
<div><span style="font-size: large;"><span style="font-size: medium;">The Senior Child Protection Manager will be based in Tripoli, Libya with regular travels to Misrata. Please note that Libya is not a family duty station.</span></span></div>
<div><span style="font-size: large;"><span style="font-size: medium;"> </span></span></div>
<div><span style="font-size: large;"><span style="font-size: medium;"><strong>Standards for professional conduct: </strong>The IRC and IRC staff must adhere to the values and principles outlined in The IRC Way &#8211; Standards for Professional Conduct.  These are Integrity, Equality, Service, and Accountability.  In accordance with these values, the IRC operates and enforces a range of policies, including on Beneficiary Protection from Exploitation and Abuse, Child Safeguarding, Anti Workplace Harassment, Fiscal Integrity, and Anti-Retaliation.    </span></span></div>
<div><span style="font-size: large;"><span style="font-size: medium;"> </span></span></div>
<p><span style="font-size: large;"><span style="font-size: medium;">#LI-GR2</span></span></div>
</div>
<div data-tag=""></div>
</div>
<h2 class="p-gridcol"><a href="https://rescue.csod.com/ux/ats/careersite/1/requisition/23945/application?c=rescue&amp;jobboardid=0#1"><strong>APPLY NOW</strong></a></h2>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div><p>The post <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly/en/jobs/senior-child-protection-manager/">Senior Child Protection Manager</a> first appeared on <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly/en/">Libyanjobs</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
				<company>International Rescue Committee (IRC)</company>
		<job_address>Tripoli</job_address>
		<job_category>organization</job_category>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>IT Officer</title>
		<link>https://libyanjobs.ly/en/jobs/it-officer-4/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[mohamed]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jan 2022 20:23:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://libyanjobs.ly/?post_type=noo_job&#038;p=247925</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>IT Officer Tripoli, Libya Requisition ID: req23988 Job Title: IT Officer Sector: Information Technology Employment Category: Regular Employment Type: Full-Time Location: Tripoli, Libya Job Description &#160; CONTEXTUAL BACKGROUND Founded in 1933, the International Rescue Committee (IRC) responds to the world’s worst humanitarian crises and helps people to survive, recover, and rebuild their lives. At work today in over 40 countries and 22 U.S. cities, we restore</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly/en/jobs/it-officer-4/">IT Officer</a> first appeared on <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly/en/">Libyanjobs</a>.</p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="p-view-jobdetailsbanner">
<div class="p-panel p-bg-grey40">
<div class="p-viewSL-jobdetailsbannercontent">
<div class="p-content-wrapper">
<div class="p-panel p-p-t-sm p-p-b-md">
<div class="p-panel p-p-v-xl">
<div class="p-gridlayout center-device-none start-device-sm gutter-vertical-xs-device-none">
<div class="p-gridcol col-12-device-none">
<h1 class="p-sectionheader p-f-sz-4x p-t-light" title="IT Officer" data-tag="ReqTitle">IT Officer</h1>
</div>
<div class="p-gridcol col-12-device-none">
<div class="p-gridlayout middle-device-none gutter-horizontal-sm-device-none">
<div class="p-gridcol col-12-device-none col-auto-device-sm"><span class="p-text p-f-sz-xl p-t-light  p-f-w-n" data-tag="displayLocationMessage">Tripoli, Libya</span></div>
<div class="p-gridcol col-12-device-none col-auto-device-sm"></div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="p-gridcol col-12-device-none">
<div class="p-gridlayout center-device-none start-device-sm gutter-horizontal-xs-device-none gutter-horizontal-sm-device-xs gutter-vertical-xs-device-none gutter-vertical-none-device-sm"></div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="p-content-wrapper">
<div class="p-panel p-p-t-lg p-p-b-xl">
<div>
<div class="p-view-jobdetailsnavigation">
<div class="p-gridlayout gutter-horizontal-md-device-none">
<div class="p-gridcol col-fill-device-none"></div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div>
<div class="p-panel p-p-t-xs">
<div>
<div class="p-gridlayout gutter-horizontal-md-device-none gutter-vertical-sm-device-none">
<div class="p-gridcol col-12-device-none">
<div class="p-view-jobdetailsad">
<div class="p-panel p-p-b-xl">
<div>
<div id="" class="p-htmlviewer" data-tag="">
<p><span style="font-size: large;"><strong>Requisition ID:</strong> req23988</span></p>
<p><span style="font-size: large;"><strong>Job Title: </strong>IT Officer</span></p>
<p><span style="font-size: large;"><strong>Sector: </strong>Information Technology</span></p>
<p><span style="font-size: large;"><strong>Employment Category:</strong> Regular</span></p>
<p><span style="font-size: large;"><strong>Employment Type:</strong> Full-Time</span></p>
<p><strong>Location:</strong> Tripoli, Libya</p>
<p><strong><span style="font-size: large;">Job Description</span></strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-size: large;"><span style="font-size: medium;"><strong>CONTEXTUAL BACKGROUND<br />
</strong><br />
Founded in 1933, the International Rescue Committee (IRC) responds to the world’s worst humanitarian crises and helps people to survive, recover, and rebuild their lives. At work today in over 40 countries and 22 U.S. cities, we restore safety, dignity, and hope to millions who are uprooted and struggling to endure. The IRC leads the way from harm to home. The IRC launched an emergency health response in Libya in September 2016 as the humanitarian situation in the country was deteriorating following the 2014 civil war. Since then, the IRC has broadened its portfolio with health, protection, and governance programs aiming, directly and in partnership, to employ a holistic approach to meeting the needs of crisis affected and vulnerable communities across the Libya to survive, recover, and gain control of their futures.</p>
<p><strong>Job Summary</strong></span></span></p>
<p><span style="font-size: large;"><span style="font-size: medium;">The Information Technology department supports the organization’s work by providing reliable and scalable application development and infrastructure for the IRC’s offices in the US and around the world, including many technologically challenging locations.</p>
<p>The IT Officer will be primarily responsible with assisting and facilitating the installation and configuration of IT infrastructure, staff training and operations of IT activities in the IRC Libya offices and Libya representative office in Tunis, including, nearby IRC site offices.<br />
The IT Officer will work closely with the Senior IT Manager and the Regional Deputy Director IT and all program sectors to ensure proper ICT functioning and support.</p>
<p><strong>RESPONSIBILITIES:<br />
</strong><br />
Installation &amp; Configuration of:<br />
Servers, server operating system and software, desktop/laptop hardware and software, and peripherals.<br />
Local Area Network, wireless network, Layer 7 devices, Firewalls, essential network services peer-to-peer or client server architecture, as appropriate.<br />
Windows 10 operating system image.<br />
IT assessment of new field offices.<br />
Perform preventative maintenance on all IRC computers and network resources.<br />
Implement and manage backup solutions for office/individual users as per IRC IT recommendations and provide the necessary training on the use of these back-up solutions.<br />
Maintain the entire life cycle of IT Asset Management, to ensure tracking of all IT hardware movement and status.<br />
Update appropriate network security and data loss prevention procedures to safeguard system from physical harm, viruses, unauthorized users and damage to data.<br />
Create and maintain IRC computer software/hardware inventory and ensuring accuracy of IT asset management system.<br />
Support core IRC applications such as Office 365, Teams, Sun systems and Box and provide 1­­th line support for finance and bespoke, in-house applications.<br />
Create and maintain network documentation to include but not limited to IP address, system access, email creation system, upgrades and changes to original network, etc.<br />
Diagnose hardware and software faults by questioning clients patiently about a problem and explaining the procedures to them.<br />
Closely collaborate with International and HQ IT, team, on helpdesk, connectivity and other in the country and global IRC IT projects.</p>
<p><strong>Training, Evaluation, &amp; Testing:<br />
</strong>Develop and implement user and support local staff training, including training on basic care and maintenance of computers and equipment for users.<br />
Test and evaluate new technology as required by HQ IT.<br />
Assist new hire staff to complete IT Setup for Computers.<br />
Various Projects – Position will need to assist in various IT projects as needed.<br />
Support the rollout of an ERP platform (Microsoft Dynamics).<br />
Test and evaluate new technology.<br />
Prepare and submit reports.</p>
<p><strong> Policies &amp; Protocols:<br />
</strong>Contribute to procurement processes, as per standard IRC policies and procedures and in co-operation with the local Operations Team.</p>
<p>General duties as part of the IRC Libya Operations Team.<br />
This position reports directly to the IT Manager in Libya.<br />
Working closely with Supply chain Team.</p>
<p><strong> Key Working Relationships<br />
</strong>Position reports to: Senior IT Manager<br />
Position directly supervises: N/A<br />
Other internal: IRC Staffs, Helpdesk Team<br />
</span></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong><span style="font-size: large;">Qualifications</span></strong></p>
<p><span style="font-size: large;"><span style="font-size: medium;"><strong>Job Requirements:<br />
</strong><br />
University Degree in Computer Science or equivalent technical work experience.<br />
At least three years of experience in IT profession<br />
MCP, CCNA courses desired, MCSE or equivalent experience is required.<br />
Experience installing, configuring, and managing both wired and wireless LAN, and firewalls.<br />
Computer Windows imaging skills required.<br />
Experience of Microsoft Dynamic (or similar ERP platform), RPA, excel macros are desirable but not required.<br />
Strong written and interpersonal skills, customer service experience<br />
Problem solving skills.<br />
Outlook experience required.<br />
Able to work independently within a team environment<br />
Flexible working hours and a possibility to work remotely.</p>
<p>Desirable:<br />
Attention to details.<br />
Work experience with INGO.<br />
Advanced knowledge of Excel.</p>
<p>WORK ENVIRONMENT:<br />
The position will cover work in Tripoli IRC Offices, is expected to be on-site or work remotely.</p>
<p>____________________________________________________________________________________<br />
The IRC and IRC workers must adhere to the values and principles outlined in IRC Way &#8211; Standards for Professional Conduct.  These are Integrity, Service, and Accountability.  In accordance with these values, the IRC operates and enforces policies on Beneficiary Protection from Exploitation and Abuse, Child Safeguarding, Anti Workplace Harassment, Fiscal Integrity, and Anti-Retaliation.</span></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="p-panel p-p-v-xl">
<div>
<div class="p-gridlayout center-device-none start-device-sm gutter-horizontal-xs-device-none gutter-horizontal-sm-device-xs gutter-vertical-xs-device-none gutter-vertical-none-device-sm">
<h2 class="p-gridcol"><a href="https://rescue.csod.com/ux/ats/careersite/1/requisition/23988/application?c=rescue&amp;jobboardid=0#1"><strong>APPLY NOW</strong></a></h2>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div><p>The post <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly/en/jobs/it-officer-4/">IT Officer</a> first appeared on <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly/en/">Libyanjobs</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
				<company>International Rescue Committee (IRC)</company>
		<job_address>Tripoli,Tripoli - Libya</job_address>
		<job_category>organization</job_category>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>ICT Associate</title>
		<link>https://libyanjobs.ly/en/jobs/ict-associate-5/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[mohamed]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jan 2022 20:19:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://libyanjobs.ly/?post_type=noo_job&#038;p=247924</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>ICT Associate Tripoli (LBY), Libya Job Identification 2170 Locations Tripoli (LBY), Libya Posting Date 01/25/2022, 11:19 AM Apply Before 02/24/2022, 11:59 AM Degree Level Secondary School Leaving Certificate Job Schedule Full time Agency UNDP Grade G6 Vacancy Type Fixed Term Practice Area Management Bureau Regional Bureau for Arab States Contract Duration 1 Year Education &#38; Work Experience Bachelor&#8217;s Degree &#8211;</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly/en/jobs/ict-associate-5/">ICT Associate</a> first appeared on <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly/en/">Libyanjobs</a>.</p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="main-view" tabindex="-1" role="main" data-bind="view: 'main', adjustToCustomHeader: { 'fixed-height': 'min-height' }">
<div data-bind="view: 'search-main'">
<div class="search-results job-selected" data-bind="css: {'job-selected': selectedJobId}, i18nAttr: {'aria-label': 'search.a11y.search-results-title'}" aria-label="Search Results">
<div class="job-details-container job-details-full-view" data-bind="adjustToCustomHeader: { css: 'job-details-container--with-custom-header' },
                    css:{'closing': isJobDetailsContainerClosing(), 'job-details-half-view': isJobHalfView(), 'job-details-full-view': !isJobHalfView()},
                    setBodyScrollTo: { to: 0, when: isJobFullView }"></p>
<div id="job-preview" data-bind="view: 'search-aside'">
<div class="job-wrapper" role="region" data-bind="i18nAttr: {'aria-label': 'job-details.page-title'}, swipe: {right: closeOnSwipe},
                adjustToCustomHeader: { 'calc-height': 'min-height' },
                css: { 'job-wrapper--ios': isIOS, 'job-wrapper--visible-footer': isFooterInViewport }" aria-label="Job Details"></p>
<div id="job" class="job ss-container" data-bind="scrollable, adjustToCustomHeader: { 'calc-height': ['min-height','height'] }, setBodyScrollTo: {  to: 0, device: 'isSmall' }">
<div class="ss-wrapper">
<div class="ss-content">
<div class="job-elements-wrapper">
<div class="header-row" dir="ltr" data-bind="i18nLang: job().lang">
<div class="job-title-container">
<h2 class="job-title"><span data-bind="text: job().title">ICT Associate</span></h2>
</div>
<div class="locations txt-overflow icon-location-pin"><span class="primary-location" data-bind="text: job().primaryLocation">Tripoli (LBY), Libya</span></div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="tiles-and-summary-wrapper" dir="ltr" data-bind="i18nLang: job().lang">
<div id="short-info-items-list" class="job-details-summary">
<div class="job-details-list">
<div class="job-info-wrapper">
<div class="job-info-labels"><span class="job-info-label" data-bind="text: name">Job Identification</span></div>
<div class="job-info-values"><span class="job-info-value" data-bind="text: value">2170</span></div>
</div>
<div class="job-info-wrapper">
<div class="job-info-labels"><span class="job-info-label" data-bind="text: name">Locations</span></div>
<ul class="job-info-values">
<li class="job-info-value" data-bind="text: $data">Tripoli (LBY), Libya</li>
</ul>
</div>
<div class="job-info-wrapper">
<div class="job-info-labels"><span class="job-info-label" data-bind="text: name">Posting Date</span></div>
<div class="job-info-values"><span class="job-info-value" data-bind="text: value">01/25/2022, 11:19 AM</span></div>
</div>
<div class="job-info-wrapper">
<div class="job-info-labels"><span class="job-info-label" data-bind="text: name">Apply Before</span></div>
<div class="job-info-values"><span class="job-info-value" data-bind="text: value">02/24/2022, 11:59 AM</span></div>
</div>
<div class="job-info-wrapper">
<div class="job-info-labels"><span class="job-info-label" data-bind="text: name">Degree Level</span></div>
<div class="job-info-values"><span class="job-info-value" data-bind="text: value">Secondary School Leaving Certificate</span></div>
</div>
<div class="job-info-wrapper">
<div class="job-info-labels"><span class="job-info-label" data-bind="text: name">Job Schedule</span></div>
<div class="job-info-values"><span class="job-info-value" data-bind="text: value">Full time</span></div>
</div>
<div class="job-info-wrapper">
<div class="job-info-labels"><span class="job-info-label" data-bind="text: name">Agency</span></div>
<div class="job-info-values"><span class="job-info-value" data-bind="text: value">UNDP</span></div>
</div>
<div class="job-info-wrapper">
<div class="job-info-labels"><span class="job-info-label" data-bind="text: name">Grade</span></div>
<div class="job-info-values"><span class="job-info-value" data-bind="text: value">G6</span></div>
</div>
<div class="job-info-wrapper">
<div class="job-info-labels"><span class="job-info-label" data-bind="text: name">Vacancy Type</span></div>
<div class="job-info-values"><span class="job-info-value" data-bind="text: value">Fixed Term</span></div>
</div>
<div class="job-info-wrapper">
<div class="job-info-labels"><span class="job-info-label" data-bind="text: name">Practice Area</span></div>
<div class="job-info-values"><span class="job-info-value" data-bind="text: value">Management</span></div>
</div>
<div class="job-info-wrapper">
<div class="job-info-labels"><span class="job-info-label" data-bind="text: name">Bureau</span></div>
<div class="job-info-values"><span class="job-info-value" data-bind="text: value">Regional Bureau for Arab States</span></div>
</div>
<div class="job-info-wrapper">
<div class="job-info-labels"><span class="job-info-label" data-bind="text: name">Contract Duration</span></div>
<div class="job-info-values"><span class="job-info-value" data-bind="text: value">1 Year</span></div>
</div>
<div class="job-info-wrapper">
<div class="job-info-labels"><span class="job-info-label" data-bind="text: name">Education &amp; Work Experience</span></div>
<div class="job-info-values"><span class="job-info-value" data-bind="text: value">Bachelor&#8217;s Degree &#8211; 3 year(s) experience OR High School certificate- 6 year(s) experience</span></div>
</div>
<div class="job-info-wrapper">
<div class="job-info-labels"><span class="job-info-label" data-bind="text: name">Required Languages</span></div>
<div class="job-info-values"><span class="job-info-value" data-bind="text: value">Proficiency in oral and written English and Arabic Languages</span></div>
</div>
<div class="job-info-wrapper">
<div class="job-info-labels"><span class="job-info-label" data-bind="text: name">Vacancy Timeline</span></div>
<div class="job-info-values"><span class="job-info-value" data-bind="text: value">4 Weeks</span></div>
</div>
<div class="job-info-wrapper">
<div class="job-info-labels"><span class="job-info-label" data-bind="text: name">Mobility required/no mobility</span></div>
<div class="job-info-values"><span class="job-info-value" data-bind="text: value">no mobility required</span></div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="info oj-flex oj-flex-items-pad oj-sm-flex-direction-column" dir="ltr" data-bind="i18nLang: job().lang">
<div class="job-link-wrapper"></div>
<div class="details">
<h2 class="job-description-header" data-bind="i18n: 'job-details.job-description-title'">Job Description</h2>
<div class="job-description" data-bind="html: job().description">
<div><strong>Background</strong></div>
<div></div>
<div><strong>UNDP is committed to achieving workforce diversity in terms of gender, nationality and culture. Individuals from minority groups, indigenous groups and persons with disabilities are equally encouraged to apply. All applications will be treated with the strictest confidence.</strong></div>
<div></div>
<div><strong>UNDP does not tolerate sexual exploitation and abuse, any kind of harassment, including sexual harassment, and discrimination. All selected candidates will, therefore, undergo rigorous reference and background checks.</strong></div>
<div></div>
<div>
<p>UNDP Libya is working rapidly to respond to several crises in Libya by formulating and implementing projects that help stabilize the country and instill trust and confidence amongst communities, and between communities and the government. The UNDP Libya Country Office (CO) has made strong commitments to international donors,  its Libyan counterparts and citizens to help restore and improve public services; enhance the effectiveness and reach of existing public institutions; expand civic engagement and participation in political and development processes; increase economic opportunities in a more diversified economy; strengthen social cohesion, support elections, reconciliation and politic dialogue initiatives; and contribute to stability throughout the country to ensure development gains.</p>
<p>In this context, the UNDP Libya is rapidly responding to the situation in Libya. To this end, the Country Office is strengthening its internal capacities through an enhanced recruitment approach and re alignment of its programmatic offer in a bid to respond to the needs and priorities of the country. It is envisaged that this support will provide timely, cost effective, integrated and dynamic solutions for the delivery of much needed services under a rapidly changing context in the country thus ensuring smooth business continuity and sustainable development.<br />
Under the overall guidance of the DRR-O and direct supervision of the UN Compound Manager, the ICT Associate provides ICT services, implements ICT management systems and strategies, provides daily technical support to users of information management tools and technology infrastructure. The ICT Support Associate promotes a client-oriented approach.<br />
The ICT Associate works in close collaboration with the Front Office, Management Support and Business Development, Programme and Operations teams in the CO and UNDP HQ staff for resolving complex ICT-related issues, collaborates with Regional ICT Officers (RIO), Regional Bureau ICT Managers (RBIMs), ICT Managers and other ICT Staff.
</p></div>
<div><strong>Duties and Responsibilities</strong></div>
<div></div>
<div><strong>Ensures implementation of ICT strategies and introduction/implementation of new technologies, focusing on achievement of the following results:</strong></div>
<div>•  Compliance with corporate information management and technology standards, guidelines and procedures for the CO technology environment.<br />
•  Participation in development and implementation of ICT annual plan and Standard Operating Procedures in ICT services.<br />
•  Provision of support to the use of Atlas (UNDP’s implementation of ERP) functionality for improved business results and improved client services.
</div>
<div><strong>Ensures effective functioning of the CO hardware and software packages, focusing on the achievement of the following results:</strong></div>
<div>•  Effective functioning (installation, operation and maintenance) of all UNDP hardware equipment and acquisition of hardware supplies.<br />
•  Performance of specific technical functions, including changing of hardware electronic components (disks, memories, network wiring, power sources, etc.) and routine repairs.<br />
•  Installation of commercial and in-house developed software and related upgrades, anti-virus programs on a timely basis.</div>
<div></div>
<div><strong>Ensures efficient networks administration, focusing on achievement of the following results:</strong></div>
<div>•    Monitoring of the network connection on a daily basis to ensure a stable and responsive network environment.<br />
•  Trouble-shooting and monitoring of network problems.<br />
•  Ensure that the UNDP desktop and network resources are protected from malicious virus attacks and deploy countermeasures in the event of the attacks.<br />
•  Response to user needs and questions regarding network access.<br />
•  Maintain of up-to-date parameters of information for the network clients and electronic mail.<br />
•  Implementation of backup and restoration procedures for local drives. Maintenance of backup log. Organization of off-site storage of backups.<br />
•  Maintenance of measures in place for business continuity and disaster recover processes and procedures including backup and restoration of both server and local storage facilities.<br />
•  Networks administration support to other UN agencies as required and preparation of bills for recovery for the service provided.
</div>
<div><strong>Provides web management services, focusing on achievement of the following results:</strong></div>
<div>•  Support to the maintenance of the CO websites and Intranet.<br />
•  Trouble-shooting and monitoring of websites for UNDP and other UN agencies upon request and preparation of bills for cost recovery for the service provided.</div>
<div></div>
<div><strong>Provides administrative support, focusing on achievement of the following results:</strong></div>
<div>•  Provision of advice on and assistance in procurement of new ICT equipment for the CO and projects, provision of technical specifications and information on best options in both local and international markets, review of quotations and bids<br />
•  Maintenance of an up-to-date inventory of the software and hardware.<br />
•  Maintenance of a library of ICT related reference materials</div>
<div>•  Maintenance of the inventory and stock of supplies and spare parts in cooperation with the Administration and procurement Teams.<br />
•  Provision of ICT support to key events.
</div>
<div><strong>Ensures facilitation of knowledge building and knowledge sharing in the CO, focusing on achievement of the following results:</strong></div>
<div>•  Identification and promotion of different systems and applications for optimal content management, knowledge management and sharing, information provision.<br />
•  Participation in the organization of training for the CO staff on ICT issues.<br />
•  Maintenance of staff training profiles.<br />
•  Synthesis of lessons learned and best practices in ICT.<br />
•  Sound contributions to knowledge networks and communities of practice
</div>
<div><strong>Competencies</strong></div>
<div></div>
<div><strong>Core</strong></div>
<ul>
<li><strong>Achieve Results: </strong>LEVEL 1: Plans and monitors own work, pays attention to details, delivers quality work by deadline</li>
<li><strong>Think Innovatively:</strong> LEVEL 1: Open to creative ideas/known risks, is pragmatic problem solver, makes improvements</li>
<li><strong>Learn Continuously:</strong> LEVEL 1: Open minded and curious, shares knowledge, learns from mistakes, asks for feedback</li>
<li><strong>Adapt with Agility: </strong>LEVEL 1: Adapts to change, constructively handles ambiguity/uncertainty, is flexible</li>
<li><strong>Act with Determination: </strong>LEVEL 1: Shows drive and motivation, able to deliver calmly in face of adversity, confident</li>
<li><strong>Engage and Partner:</strong> LEVEL 1: Demonstrates compassion/understanding towards others, forms positive relationships</li>
<li><strong>Enable Diversity and Inclusion:</strong> LEVEL 1: Appreciate/respect differences, aware of unconscious bias, confront discrimination</li>
</ul>
<div>
<p><strong><em>Cross-Functional &amp; Technical competencies</em></strong></p>
<ul>
<li><strong>IT Customer Support: </strong>Ability to support l customers on IT related issues and generate and contribute to continuous improvement processes to deliver a great user experience. Knowledge of ISO 9001 desirable. ITIL certification or similar is desirable.</li>
<li><strong>I</strong><strong>T Security Management:</strong> Knowledge of Cyber Security technologies, processes, techniques and tools. Apply practical innovations to solve cybersecurity problems. Capability to keep UNDP systems and data safe. Knowledge of ISO 27001 principles. CSSIP, CSIM, CISA or equivalent certification desirable.</li>
<li><strong>IT Quality Management: </strong>Ability to manage quality of IT services. ISO 9001, 20000. Certification in ITIL desirable</li>
<li><strong>IT Service Delivery &amp; Operations: </strong>Ability to deliver the IT products and services to customers at the right level of Quality and Costs, taking into account user experience. ISO 20000 knowledge. ITIL certification or similar desirable</li>
<li><strong>Network, Communication and Infrastructure Management: </strong>Ability to develop/integrate/operate/manage IT network, communications, Cloud or on-premise infrastructure, and new technologies like IoT. Cisco CCIE CCNP or similar is desirable.</li>
</ul>
</div>
<div></div>
<div><strong>Required Skills and Experience</strong></div>
<div><strong>Education:</strong></div>
<ul>
<li>Secondary education with relevant certifications in hardware and software management and application (Microsoft Certification, Cisco Certification).</li>
<li>A University Degree in Computer Science will be given due consideration.</li>
<li>Cisco Certified Network Administrator (CCNA) and Microsoft Certified Professional (MCP) is required. If certification is not available at the time of recruitment, it should be obtained within 6 months.</li>
</ul>
<div><strong>Experience:</strong></div>
<div>
<ul>
<li>6 years (Secondary education) or 3 years (Bachelors Degree) of relevant working experience, including network administration, management of hardware and software platforms, telecommunications facilities, knowledge of Windows-based packages/applications.</li>
<li>Experience in providing daily technical support to users of information management tools and technology infrastructure.</li>
<li>Experience of desktop operating systems (Windows) and associated hardware and software (MS office, MS project, Visio) necessary to install and support users is an asset.</li>
<li>Experience with UN system and international organization is an asset.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Language Requirements:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Proficiency in oral and written English and Arabic Languages</li>
</ul>
<div></div>
<div>Please note that continuance of appointment beyond the initial 12 months is contingent upon the successful completion of a probationary period.</div>
<div></div>
</div>
<div><strong>Disclaimer</strong></div>
<div></div>
<div>
<div><a href="https://jobs.undp.org/cj_us_permanent_card_holders.cfm" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Important information for US Permanent Residents (&#8216;Green Card&#8217; holders)</a></div>
<div></div>
<div>Under US immigration law, acceptance of a staff position with UNDP, an international organization, may have significant implications for US Permanent Residents. UNDP advises applicants for all professional level posts that they must relinquish their US Permanent Resident status and accept a G-4 visa, or have submitted a valid application for US citizenship prior to commencement of employment.</div>
<div></div>
<div>UNDP is not in a position to provide advice or assistance on applying for US citizenship and therefore applicants are advised to seek the advice of competent immigration lawyers regarding any applications.</div>
<div></div>
<div>Applicant information about UNDP rosters</div>
<div></div>
<div>Note: UNDP reserves the right to select one or more candidates from this vacancy announcement.  We may also retain applications and consider candidates applying to this post for other similar positions with UNDP at the same grade level and with similar job description, experience and educational requirements.</div>
<div></div>
<div>Scam warning</div>
<div></div>
<div>The United Nations does not charge any application, processing, training, interviewing, testing or other fee in connection with the application or recruitment process. Should you receive a solicitation for the payment of a fee, please disregard it. Furthermore, please note that emblems, logos, names and addresses are easily copied and reproduced. Therefore, you are advised to apply particular care when submitting personal information on the web.</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="job-link-wrapper"></div>
<div class="ai-jobs-search" data-bind="css: className"></div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="ss-scrollbar-wrapper">
<h2 class="ss-scroll"><a href="https://estm.fa.em2.oraclecloud.com/hcmUI/CandidateExperience/en/sites/CX_1/job/2170/apply/email"><strong>APPLY NOW</strong></a></h2>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div><p>The post <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly/en/jobs/ict-associate-5/">ICT Associate</a> first appeared on <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly/en/">Libyanjobs</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
				<company>United Nations Development Programme (UNDP) in Libya</company>
		<job_address>Tripoli,Tripoli - Libya</job_address>
		<job_category>organization</job_category>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Procurement Analyst</title>
		<link>https://libyanjobs.ly/en/jobs/procurement-analyst/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[mohamed]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jan 2022 20:17:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://libyanjobs.ly/?post_type=noo_job&#038;p=247923</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Procurement Analyst Tripoli (LBY), Libya Job Identification 2168 Locations Tripoli (LBY), Libya Posting Date 01/26/2022, 03:13 PM Apply Before 02/23/2022, 06:59 AM Job Schedule Full time Agency UNDP Grade NOB Vacancy Type Fixed Term Practice Area Crisis management / Country Management Support Bureau Regional Bureau for Arab States Contract Duration 1 Year Education &#38; Work Experience Master&#8217;s Degree Other Criteria 2 years (Master’s degree) or 4 years (Bachelor) of relevant</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly/en/jobs/procurement-analyst/">Procurement Analyst</a> first appeared on <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly/en/">Libyanjobs</a>.</p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div id="job" class="job ss-container" data-bind="scrollable, adjustToCustomHeader: { 'calc-height': ['min-height','height'] }, setBodyScrollTo: {  to: 0, device: 'isSmall' }">
<div class="ss-wrapper">
<div class="ss-content">
<div class="job-elements-wrapper">
<div class="header-row" dir="ltr" data-bind="i18nLang: job().lang">
<div class="job-title-container">
<h2 class="job-title"><span data-bind="text: job().title">Procurement Analyst</span></h2>
</div>
<div class="locations txt-overflow icon-location-pin"><span class="primary-location" data-bind="text: job().primaryLocation">Tripoli (LBY), Libya</span></div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="tiles-and-summary-wrapper" dir="ltr" data-bind="i18nLang: job().lang">
<div id="short-info-items-list" class="job-details-summary">
<div class="job-details-list">
<div class="job-info-wrapper">
<div class="job-info-labels"><span class="job-info-label" data-bind="text: name">Job Identification </span><span class="job-info-value" data-bind="text: value">2168</span></div>
</div>
<div class="job-info-wrapper">
<div class="job-info-labels"><span class="job-info-label" data-bind="text: name">Locations </span>Tripoli (LBY), Libya</div>
</div>
<div class="job-info-wrapper">
<div class="job-info-labels"><span class="job-info-label" data-bind="text: name">Posting Date </span><span class="job-info-value" data-bind="text: value">01/26/2022, 03:13 PM</span></div>
</div>
<div class="job-info-wrapper">
<div class="job-info-labels"><span class="job-info-label" data-bind="text: name">Apply Before </span><span class="job-info-value" data-bind="text: value">02/23/2022, 06:59 AM</span></div>
</div>
<div class="job-info-wrapper">
<div class="job-info-labels"><span class="job-info-label" data-bind="text: name">Job Schedule </span><span class="job-info-value" data-bind="text: value">Full time</span></div>
</div>
<div class="job-info-wrapper">
<div class="job-info-labels"><span class="job-info-label" data-bind="text: name">Agency </span><span class="job-info-value" data-bind="text: value">UNDP</span></div>
</div>
<div class="job-info-wrapper">
<div class="job-info-labels"><span class="job-info-label" data-bind="text: name">Grade </span><span class="job-info-value" data-bind="text: value">NOB</span></div>
</div>
<div class="job-info-wrapper">
<div class="job-info-labels"><span class="job-info-label" data-bind="text: name">Vacancy Type </span><span class="job-info-value" data-bind="text: value">Fixed Term</span></div>
</div>
<div class="job-info-wrapper">
<div class="job-info-labels"><span class="job-info-label" data-bind="text: name">Practice Area </span><span class="job-info-value" data-bind="text: value">Crisis management / Country Management Support</span></div>
</div>
<div class="job-info-wrapper">
<div class="job-info-labels"><span class="job-info-label" data-bind="text: name">Bureau </span><span class="job-info-value" data-bind="text: value">Regional Bureau for Arab States</span></div>
</div>
<div class="job-info-wrapper">
<div class="job-info-labels"><span class="job-info-label" data-bind="text: name">Contract Duration </span><span class="job-info-value" data-bind="text: value">1 Year</span></div>
</div>
<div class="job-info-wrapper">
<div class="job-info-labels"><span class="job-info-label" data-bind="text: name">Education &amp; Work Experience</span></div>
<div class="job-info-values"><span class="job-info-value" data-bind="text: value">Master&#8217;s Degree</span></div>
</div>
<div class="job-info-wrapper">
<div class="job-info-labels"><span class="job-info-label" data-bind="text: name">Other Criteria</span></div>
<div class="job-info-values"><span class="job-info-value" data-bind="text: value">2 years (Master’s degree) or 4 years (Bachelor) of relevant experience at the national or international level in procurement management</span></div>
</div>
<div class="job-info-wrapper">
<div class="job-info-labels"><span class="job-info-label" data-bind="text: name">Required Languages</span></div>
<div class="job-info-values"><span class="job-info-value" data-bind="text: value">Proficiency in oral and written English and Arabic languages</span></div>
</div>
<div class="job-info-wrapper">
<div class="job-info-labels"><span class="job-info-label" data-bind="text: name">Vacancy Timeline</span></div>
<div class="job-info-values"><span class="job-info-value" data-bind="text: value">4 Weeks</span></div>
</div>
<div class="job-info-wrapper">
<div class="job-info-labels"><span class="job-info-label" data-bind="text: name">Mobility required/no mobility</span></div>
<div class="job-info-values"><span class="job-info-value" data-bind="text: value">no mobility required</span></div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="info oj-flex oj-flex-items-pad oj-sm-flex-direction-column" dir="ltr" data-bind="i18nLang: job().lang">
<div class="job-link-wrapper"></div>
<div class="details">
<h2 class="job-description-header" data-bind="i18n: 'job-details.job-description-title'">Job Description</h2>
<div class="job-description" data-bind="html: job().description">
<div><strong>Background</strong></div>
<div></div>
<div><strong>UNDP is committed to achieving workforce diversity in terms of gender, nationality and culture. Individuals from minority groups, indigenous groups and persons with disabilities are equally encouraged to apply. All applications will be treated with the strictest confidence.</strong></div>
<div></div>
<div><strong>UNDP does not tolerate sexual exploitation and abuse, any kind of harassment, including sexual harassment, and discrimination. All selected candidates will, therefore, undergo rigorous reference and background checks.</strong></div>
<div>
<p>UNDP Libya is working rapidly to respond to several crises in Libya by formulating and implementing projects that help stabilize the country and instill trust and confidence amongst communities, and between communities and the government. The UNDP Libya Country Office (CO) has made strong commitments to international donors,  its Libyan counterparts and citizens to help restore and improve public services; enhance the effectiveness and reach of existing public institutions; expand civic engagement and participation in political and development processes; increase economic opportunities in a more diversified economy; strengthen social cohesion, support elections, reconciliation and politic dialogue initiatives; and contribute to stability throughout the country to ensure development gains.</p>
<p>In this context, the UNDP Libya is rapidly responding to the situation in Libya. To this end, the Country Office is strengthening its internal capacities through an enhanced recruitment approach and re alignment of its programmatic offer in a bid to respond to the needs and priorities of the country. It is envisaged that this support will provide timely, cost effective, integrated and dynamic solutions for the delivery of much needed services under a rapidly changing context in the country thus ensuring smooth business continuity and sustainable development.</p>
<p>Under the overall guidance of the DRR-Operations and direct supervision of the Procurement Specialist, the Procurement Analyst is responsible for effective delivery of procurement services to obtain the best value for money. He/she analyzes and interprets the financial rules and regulations and provides solutions to a wide spectrum of complex issues related to procurement. The Procurement Analyst promotes a collaborative, client-focused, quality and results-oriented approach in the Unit.</p>
<p>The Procurement Analyst works in close collaboration with the operations, program and project teams in the CO, UNDP HQs staff, other UN agencies and Government officials, to successfully deliver procurement services.</p>
</div>
<div><strong>Duties and Responsibilities</strong></div>
<div>
<ul>
<li>Elaboration and implementation of operational strategies</li>
<li>Management of procurement processes</li>
<li>Introduction and implementation of sourcing strategy and e-procurement tools</li>
<li>Control of CO Assets</li>
<li>Logistical Services</li>
</ul>
<p>Facilitation of knowledge building and knowledge sharing</p></div>
<div>
<p><strong> Ensures elaboration and implementation of operational strategies focusing on achievement of the following results:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Full compliance of procurement activities with UN/UNDP rules, regulations, policies, and strategies; implementation of the effective internal control, proper design and functioning of a client-oriented procurement management system.</li>
<li>CO Procurement business processes mapping and elaboration/establishment of internal Standard Operating Procedures (SOPs) in Supply Chain, control of the workflows in the Procurement Unit.</li>
<li>Elaboration and implementation of cost saving and reduction strategies.</li>
<li>Implementation of contract strategy in the CO including tendering processes and evaluation, contractor appraisal, managing the contract and contractor, legal considerations and payment conditions, risk assessment.</li>
<li>Implementation of the strategic procurement in the CO including sourcing strategy, supplier selection and evaluation, quality management, customer relationship management, e-procurement introduction and promotion, performance measurement.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Manages and guides procurement processes for CO, NIM/DIM projects, UNCC and at the request of other Agencies focusing on achievement of the following results:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Timely and duly preparation of procurement plans for the office and projects and monitoring of their implementation.</li>
<li>Implementation of proper monitoring and control of procurement processes including organization of RFQ, ITB or RFP, receipt of quotations, bids or proposals, their evaluation, negotiation of certain conditions of contracts in full compliance with UNDP rules and regulation.</li>
<li>Review and certification of submissions to the Contract, Asset and Procurement Committee (CAP) and Advisory Committee on Procurement (ACP).</li>
<li>Management of procurement contracts.</li>
<li>Analysis of requirements and synthesis of proposals for cost saving and reduction strategies.</li>
<li>Establishment of the procurement processes monitoring system and mechanisms to eliminate deficiencies in procurement.</li>
<li>Preparation of cost-recovery bills in Atlas for procurement services provided by UNDP to other Agencies.</li>
<li>Implementation of harmonized procurement services and elaboration of proposals on common services expansion in the UNCC, introduction of joint procurement for the UN Agencies in line with the UN reform</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Ensures introduction and implementation of sourcing strategy and e-procurement tools focusing on achievement of the following results</strong>:</p>
<ul>
<li>Development and management of the rosters of suppliers, elaboration of supplier selection and evaluation, quality, and performance measurement mechanisms.</li>
<li>Management of e-procurement module.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Ensures facilitation of knowledge building and knowledge sharing in the CO focusing on achievement of the following results:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Organization of trainings for the operations/ projects staff on Procurement.</li>
<li>Synthesis of lessons learnt and best practices in Procurement.</li>
<li>Sound contributions to knowledge networks and communities of practice. Timely follow up of bank reconciliation in co- ordinations  with  GSSU , including documented review of exceptions.</li>
<li>Initiation of bank transfers and deals, selecting bank transfers and deals for approval and settlement.</li>
<li>Timely preparation of monthly cashflow forecast. Liaison with UN Agencies to obtain estimate of their cash requirements.</li>
<li>Role as cashier for cash disbursements made on site</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Ensures facilitation of knowledge building and knowledge sharing in the CO and guidance to all stakeholders on financial matters focusing on achievement of the following results:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Organization/conduct of training for the operations/programme/projects staff on financial management and RBM.</li>
<li>Synthesis of lessons learnt and best practices in Finance.</li>
<li>Sound contributions to knowledge networks and communities of practice.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Competencies</strong></p>
</div>
<div><strong><em>Core</em></strong></div>
<div>
<ul>
<li><strong>Achieve Results: </strong>LEVEL 2: Plans and monitors own work, pays attention to details, delivers quality work by deadline</li>
<li><strong>Think Innovatively: </strong>LEVEL 2: Open to creative ideas/known risks, is pragmatic problem solver, makes improvements</li>
<li><strong>Learn Continuously: </strong>LEVEL 2: Open minded and curious, shares knowledge, learns from mistakes, asks for feedback</li>
<li><strong>Adapt with Agility: </strong>LEVEL 2: Adapts to change, constructively handles ambiguity/uncertainty, is flexible</li>
<li><strong>Act with Determination : </strong>LEVEL 2: Shows drive and motivation, able to deliver calmly in face of adversity, confident</li>
<li><strong>Engage and Partner: </strong>LEVEL 2: Demonstrates compassion/understanding towards others, forms positive relationships</li>
<li><strong>Enable Diversity and Inclusion: </strong>LEVEL 2: Appreciate/respect differences, aware of unconscious bias, confront discrimination</li>
</ul>
<p><strong><em>Cross-Functional &amp; Technical competencies </em></strong></p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Contract Management : </strong>Knowledge of contract management concepts, principles and methods, and ability to apply this to strategic and/or practical situations</li>
<li><strong>Procurement management: </strong>The ability to acquire goods, services or works from an outside external source</li>
<li><strong>Supplier/relationship management: </strong>Knowledge of supplier management concepts, principles and methods, and ability to apply this to strategic and/or practical situations</li>
<li><strong>Stakeholder management : </strong>Ability to work with incomplete information and balance competing interests to create value for all stakeholders</li>
<li><strong>Sourcing : </strong>Ability to find, evaluate and engage suppliers of goods and services</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Required Skills and Experience</strong></p>
</div>
<div>
<p><strong><em>Education</em></strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Master’s Degree or equivalent in Business Administration, Public Administration, Finance, Economics, Logistic or related field is required.</li>
<li>A Bachelor’s Degree will be given due consideration with additional 2 years of relevant work experience in lieu of Master’s Degree</li>
<li>Procurement Certificate (CIPS II) is an asset.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong><em> Experience, Knowledge, and Skills</em></strong></p>
<ul>
<li>2 years (Master’s Degree) or 4 years (Bachelor) of relevant experience at the national or international level in procurement management.</li>
<li>Experience in the usage of computers and office software packages (MS Word, Excel, etc.) and advanced knowledge of web-based management systems.</li>
<li>Experience in Logistics Operations management is preferable,</li>
<li>Experience with the UN system is an advantage</li>
</ul>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Language Requirements:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Proficiency in oral and written English and Arabic Languages</li>
</ul>
<p>Please note that continuance of appointment beyond the initial 12 months is contingent upon the successful completion of a probationary period.</p>
<div></div>
</div>
<div><strong>Disclaimer</strong></div>
<div></div>
<div>
<div><a href="https://jobs.undp.org/cj_us_permanent_card_holders.cfm" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Important information for US Permanent Residents (&#8216;Green Card&#8217; holders)</a></div>
<div></div>
<div>Under US immigration law, acceptance of a staff position with UNDP, an international organization, may have significant implications for US Permanent Residents. UNDP advises applicants for all professional level posts that they must relinquish their US Permanent Resident status and accept a G-4 visa, or have submitted a valid application for US citizenship prior to commencement of employment.</div>
<div></div>
<div>UNDP is not in a position to provide advice or assistance on applying for US citizenship and therefore applicants are advised to seek the advice of competent immigration lawyers regarding any applications.</div>
<div></div>
<div>Applicant information about UNDP rosters</div>
<div></div>
<div>Note: UNDP reserves the right to select one or more candidates from this vacancy announcement.  We may also retain applications and consider candidates applying to this post for other similar positions with UNDP at the same grade level and with similar job description, experience and educational requirements.</div>
<div></div>
<div>Scam warning</div>
<div></div>
<div>The United Nations does not charge any application, processing, training, interviewing, testing or other fee in connection with the application or recruitment process. Should you receive a solicitation for the payment of a fee, please disregard it. Furthermore, please note that emblems, logos, names and addresses are easily copied and reproduced. Therefore, you are advised to apply particular care when submitting personal information on the web.</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="job-link-wrapper"></div>
<div class="ai-jobs-search" data-bind="css: className"></div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="ss-scrollbar-wrapper">
<h2 class="ss-scroll"><a href="https://estm.fa.em2.oraclecloud.com/hcmUI/CandidateExperience/en/sites/CX_1/job/2168/apply/email"><strong>APPLY NOW</strong></a></h2>
</div>
</div>
<h2 class="apply-section" dir="ltr" data-bind="i18nLang: job().lang"></h2><p>The post <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly/en/jobs/procurement-analyst/">Procurement Analyst</a> first appeared on <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly/en/">Libyanjobs</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
				<company>United Nations Development Programme (UNDP) in Libya</company>
		<job_address>Tripoli,Tripoli - Libya</job_address>
		<job_category>organization</job_category>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Economic Recovery Assistant (Cash Assistant)</title>
		<link>https://libyanjobs.ly/en/jobs/economic-recovery-assistant-cash-assistant/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[mohamed]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jan 2022 13:43:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://libyanjobs.ly/?post_type=noo_job&#038;p=247898</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Economic Recovery Assistant (Cash Assistant) Danish Refugee Council (DRC) Grade: Unspecified Occupations: Economic Development, Humanitarian and Crisis Response Closing soon: 6 Feb 2022  New  Apply Now Added 14 hours ago JOB DESCRIPTION &#160; Tripoli, Libya &#160; The Danish Refugee Council assists refugees and internally displaced persons across the globe: we provide emergency aid, fight for their rights, and strengthen their opportunity for a</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly/en/jobs/economic-recovery-assistant-cash-assistant/">Economic Recovery Assistant (Cash Assistant)</a> first appeared on <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly/en/">Libyanjobs</a>.</p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div id="jheader" class="container bg-white border" data-v-app="">
<div class="row py-5">
<div class="col-lg-7 col-md-9 p-4 p-md-0 pe-lg-4">
<div class="h5 text-success mb-3">Economic Recovery Assistant (Cash Assistant)</div>
<div class="fw-bold mb-2">Danish Refugee Council (DRC)</div>
<div class="mb-2"></div>
<div class="mb-2"></div>
<div class="small mb-2"><b>Grade: </b>Unspecified</div>
<div class="small mb-3"><b>Occupations: </b><a href="https://www.unjobnet.org/jobs/areas-of-work/economic-development">Economic Development</a>, <a href="https://www.unjobnet.org/jobs/areas-of-work/humanitarian-and-crisis-response">Humanitarian and Crisis Response</a></div>
<div class="text-success pb-3"><span class="text-danger font-weight-bold">Closing soon: 6 Feb 2022</span></div>
<div class="d-flex flex-wrap align-items-center text-center justify-content-center justify-content-md-start xmb-2"><a class="popover-dismiss text-darkx px-0x py-1 me-3 btnbtn-lightborder" style="box-sizing: border-box; font-family: Roboto, 'Segoe UI', 'Sans Serif', 'Open Sans', Arial, cursive, sans-serif; color: #0d6efd; text-decoration: none; overflow-wrap: break-word; word-break: break-word; cursor: pointer; margin-right: 1rem !important; padding-top: 0.25rem !important; padding-bottom: 0.25rem !important;" tabindex="0" title="" role="button" data-bs-toggle="popover" data-bs-trigger="focus hover" data-bs-delay="50" data-bs-placement="bottom" data-bs-html="true" data-bs-content="&lt;h6 class='mt-3 text-uppercase'&gt;Popularity&lt;/h6&gt; &lt;div class='mt-3'&gt; The number of unique views comparing to the average. &lt;/div&gt;" data-bs-original-title=""><i class="bi-bar-chart-line-fill text-success"></i> <span class="small ms-1"><b>New</b></span> <i class="bi-question-circle-fill ms-1"></i></a></div>
</div>
<div class="col-lg-3 text-lg-start text-center py-0"><a class="py-2 me-2 btn btn-sm shadow-sm btn-success" href="https://www.unjobnet.org/jobs/detail/apply/37250701" target="_blank" rel="noopener ”nofollow”">Apply Now</a></p>
<div class="addthis_inline_share_toolbox mt-2" data-url="https://www.unjobnet.org/jobs/detail/37250701" data-title="DRC Economic Recovery Assistant (Cash Assistant)">
<div id="atstbx2" class="at-resp-share-element at-style-responsive addthis-smartlayers addthis-animated at4-show" role="region" aria-labelledby="at-0e128bcb-3ba1-4e3b-a117-7a12f0135bad"><span id="at-0e128bcb-3ba1-4e3b-a117-7a12f0135bad" class="at4-visually-hidden"></span></p>
<div class="at-share-btn-elements"></div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="small text-secondary gfont-lite mt-2">Added 14 hours ago</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div id="user-toolbar"></div>
<div id="vjd" class="container my-3" data-v-app="">
<div class="row">
<div class="col-lg-8 col-md-12 col-sm-12 border bg-white py-4 mb-3">
<div class="h5 gfont-lite border-bottom pb-2 mt-3 mb-3 px-2 px-lg-3 text-uppercase">JOB DESCRIPTION</div>
<div id="jd" class="jd px-2 px-lg-3 DRC" data-id="37250701">
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Tripoli, Libya</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The Danish Refugee Council assists refugees and internally displaced persons across the globe: we provide emergency aid, fight for their rights, and strengthen their opportunity for a brighter future. We work in conflict-affected areas, along the displacement routes, and in the countries where refugees settle. In cooperation with local communities, we strive for responsible and sustainable solutions. We work toward successful integration and – whenever possible – for the fulfilment of the wish to return home.</p>
<p>The Danish Refuge Council was founded in Denmark in 1956 and has since grown to become an international humanitarian organization with more than 7,000 staff and 8,000 volunteers. Our vision is a dignified life for all displaced.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>All of our efforts are based on our value compass: humanity, respect, independence and neutrality, participation, and honesty and transparency.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>About the job</strong></p>
<p>The Cash Assistant is responsible for the daily operation of the Cash component of the Economic Recovery Unit under the supervision of the Economic Recovery Manager and will support in the implementation of DRC’s Economic Recovery activities including Cash and Voucher Assistance (CVA) programming and Cash for Work (CfW).</p>
<p><strong>Responsibities:</strong></p>
<p>Programming</p>
<ul>
<li>Implement Economic recovery programme activities including CVA and CfW as directed by Team Leader and/or Project Manager. Identify and report challenges and concerns to Team Leader and/or Project Manager;</li>
<li>Conduct field assessments and surveys such as market assessments, price monitoring, household assessments, site assessments as required;</li>
<li>Conduct follow up visits during implementation of CfW activities and monitor activities and provide timely inputs and feedback to the Team Leader and/or Project Manager;</li>
<li>Ensure that all activities are clearly documented as per DRC’s procedures and requirements;</li>
<li>Support in data collection and identification of beneficiaries in CVA and CfW programs</li>
<li>Support in the smooth and timely implementation of CVA and CfW distributions as outlined by the Team leader and/or Project Manager</li>
<li>Provide feedback through DRC’s Complaints and Response Mechanism by providing advice and support to project beneficiaries whether through the hotline or on the field and ensure an appropriate follow-up of all cases referred to the unit through the beneficiary feedback mechanism;</li>
</ul>
<p>Reporting</p>
<ul>
<li>Provide weekly/monthly reports to the Economic recovery Team Leader and/or Project Manager, including accurate figures of distributions/number of individuals supported with temporary income opportunities, referrals done and challenges encountered, in the agreed format;</li>
</ul>
<p>Representation</p>
<ul>
<li>Develop and strengthen relationships with local partners and communities in order to maintain trust in DRC’s professional standard and quality of work among all stakeholders;</li>
<li>Maintain respectful and constructive relations with partner organizations, local authorities and humanitarian actors;</li>
</ul>
<p>Operations</p>
<ul>
<li>Ensure the preparation of required documentation for the procurement of goods and services in compliance with DRC requirements and delivered in a timely manner;</li>
</ul>
<p>Other</p>
<ul>
<li>Conduct any other duties as may be assigned by the Line Manager;</li>
<li>Conduct duties in accordance with DRC Libya programme Standard Operating Procedures (SOPs);</li>
<li>Conduct duties in accordance with DRC Code of Conduct;</li>
<li>Make sure to spread a positive image of DRC and its activities by explaining what DRC is doing and why DRC operates in that way;</li>
<li>Uphold the highest standard of confidentiality when managing records to ensure beneficiary dignity and privacy;</li>
</ul>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Experience and technical competencies:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>At least 1 year professional experience in Cash programming including multipurpose cash assistance or cash for work programming;</li>
<li>Experience in the field of social work, humanitarian intervention, community development, or any other relevant field is desirable;</li>
<li>Previous experience working with Civil Society Organizations (CSOs) and local communities is desirable;</li>
<li>Good level of computer literacy;</li>
<li>Strong organizational and time management skills;</li>
<li>Strong interpersonal skills and ability to maintain good communication channels with relevant stakeholders;</li>
</ul>
<div class="my-4 d-print-none">
<div class="text-center text-muted small mb-0"></div>
<p><ins class="adsbygoogle" data-ad-layout="in-article" data-ad-format="fluid" data-ad-client="ca-pub-8750099643106632" data-ad-slot="9936450564" data-adsbygoogle-status="done" data-ad-status="filled"><ins id="aswift_1_expand" tabindex="0" title="Advertisement" aria-label="Advertisement"><ins id="aswift_1_anchor"></ins></ins></ins></div>
<p><strong>Education</strong>:</p>
<ul>
<li>University Degree in the field of Business Administration, social sciences, psychology, political sciences, development or any other related field</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Languages:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Fluency in written and spoken English and Arabic</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>In this position, you are expected to demonstrate DRC’ five core competencies:</strong></p>
<p><strong>Striving for excellence: </strong>You focus on reaching results while ensuring an efficient process.</p>
<p><strong>Collaborating:</strong> You involve relevant parties and encourage feedback.</p>
<p><strong>Taking the lead:</strong> You take ownership and initiative while aiming for innovation.</p>
<p><strong>Communicating:</strong> You listen and speak effectively and honestly.</p>
<p><strong>Demonstrating integrity:</strong> You uphold and promote the highest standards of ethical and professional conduct in relation to our values and Code of Conduct, including safeguarding against sexual exploitation, abuse and harassment.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>We Offer:</strong></p>
<p><strong>Contract length</strong>: 3 Months</p>
<p><strong>Duty Station</strong>: Tripoli</p>
<p><strong>Start date</strong>: 15 Feb, 2022</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Application process:</strong></p>
<p>All Applicants must upload a cover letter and an updated CV (no longer than four pages) in English. <strong>A</strong><strong>pplications sent by email will not be considered.</strong></p>
<p>Closing date for Application: <strong>06 Feb 2022</strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>For further information about the Danish Refugee Council, please consult our website <a href="https://drc.ngo/">drc.ngo</a>.</p>
</div>
<div class="text-center mt-4"><a class="px-5 py-2 apply btn btn-sm btn-success fw-bold shadow-sm" href="https://www.unjobnet.org/jobs/detail/apply/37250701" target="_blank" rel="noopener ”nofollow”">Apply at DRC&#8217;s Website</a></div>
<div class="addthis_inline_share_toolbox mt-3 text-center" data-url="https://www.unjobnet.org/jobs/detail/37250701" data-title="DRC Economic Recovery Assistant (Cash Assistant)">
<div id="atstbx3" class="at-resp-share-element at-style-responsive addthis-smartlayers addthis-animated at4-show" role="region" aria-labelledby="at-869b5412-e667-4d92-8567-5de875d1b214"><span id="at-869b5412-e667-4d92-8567-5de875d1b214" class="at4-visually-hidden"></span></p>
<div class="at-share-btn-elements"></div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div><p>The post <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly/en/jobs/economic-recovery-assistant-cash-assistant/">Economic Recovery Assistant (Cash Assistant)</a> first appeared on <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly/en/">Libyanjobs</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
				<company>DRC Libya</company>
		<job_address>Tripoli</job_address>
		<job_category>organization</job_category>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>4Mi Coordinator</title>
		<link>https://libyanjobs.ly/en/jobs/4mi-coordinator/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[mohamed]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jan 2022 13:40:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://libyanjobs.ly/?post_type=noo_job&#038;p=247896</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>4Mi Coordinator DRC’s North Africa Regional Office offers support and advice to four country operations in North Africa. Under the management of the 4Mi Project Manager, the 4Mi Coordinator for Libya will be in charge of the implementation of the 4Mi research project in Libya. He/she supervises data collection collected by 4Mi Field enumerators, ensures quality control over the data collection,</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly/en/jobs/4mi-coordinator/">4Mi Coordinator</a> first appeared on <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly/en/">Libyanjobs</a>.</p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="standard-page-hero-text-wrapper">
<h1 class="standard-page-hero-title">4Mi Coordinator</h1>
<p class="standard-page-hero-manchet">DRC’s North Africa Regional Office offers support and advice to four country operations in North Africa. Under the management of the 4Mi Project Manager, the 4Mi Coordinator for Libya will be in charge of the implementation of the 4Mi research project in Libya. He/she supervises data collection collected by 4Mi Field enumerators, ensures quality control over the data collection, coordinates with MMC in North Africa on management and strategic development of activities in Libya, and supports MMC operations in Libya. Occasionally, he/she contributes to the analysis of data and writing of the research outputs.</p>
<div class="line-divider"></div>
</div>
<div class="single-recruiter-position-page-info-bar-wrapper box-wide">
<div class="single-recruiter-position-page-info-bar-items-wrapper">
<div class="single-recruiter-position-page-info-bar-item-wrapper"><span class="single-recruiter-position-page-info-bar-item-text label">Location </span><span class="single-recruiter-position-page-info-bar-item-text">Libya</span></div>
<div class="single-recruiter-position-page-info-bar-item-wrapper"><span class="single-recruiter-position-page-info-bar-item-text label">Workplace </span><span class="single-recruiter-position-page-info-bar-item-text">Tripoli, Libya</span></div>
<div class="single-recruiter-position-page-info-bar-item-wrapper"><span class="single-recruiter-position-page-info-bar-item-text label">Contract Type<br />
</span><span class="single-recruiter-position-page-info-bar-item-text">National contract</span></div>
<div class="single-recruiter-position-page-info-bar-item-wrapper"><span class="single-recruiter-position-page-info-bar-item-text label">Due Date</span><span class="single-recruiter-position-page-info-bar-item-text">18 February 2022</span></div>
</div>
<div class="single-recruiter-position-page-info-bar-item-wrapper with-button"><a class="button" href="https://candidate.hr-manager.net/ApplicationInit.aspx?cid=1036&amp;ProjectId=163346&amp;DepartmentId=19105&amp;MediaId=5&amp;SkipAdvertisement=true" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Apply Now</a></div>
</div>
<div class="narrow">
<div class="editor-content">
<p>DRC’s North Africa Regional Office offers support and advice to four country operations in North Africa. Under the management of the 4Mi Project Manager, the 4Mi Coordinator for Libya will be in charge of the implementation of the 4Mi research project in Libya. He/she supervises data collection collected by 4Mi Field enumerators, ensures quality control over the data collection, coordinates with MMC in North Africa on management and strategic development of activities in Libya, and supports MMC operations in Libya. Occasionally, he/she contributes to the analysis of data and writing of the research outputs.</p>
<p>Your main responsibilities will be:</p>
<p><strong>Team and quality management</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Responsible for the daily supervision of the 4Mi operations in Libya and ensuring a high level of quality in data collected; under the responsibility of the 4Mi PM</li>
<li>Recruits, trains, and coordinates 4Mi Field enumerators, as per regional guidelines;</li>
<li>Supervise between 10 and 20 4Mi monitors in Libya in coordination with the 4Mi Project Manager</li>
<li>In coordination with the 4Mi regional team, ensure the development of adequate tracking, monitoring and internal communication tools;</li>
<li>Work closely with support departments to make timely payments to all field-based enumerators;</li>
<li>Responsible for sending weekly updates to the monitors on their submissions and to feedback on their surveys, based on the weekly validation prepared by Information Management Officers.</li>
<li>Proactively contribute to the 4Mi strategy in Libya and in the region;</li>
<li>Take initiative in proposing improvements to existing tools.</li>
<li>Take the lead in proposing creative solutions when meeting challenges in project implementation;</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Coordination</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Daily monitoring and reporting of relevant information that might affect the smooth implementation of project activities in the country;</li>
<li>Report any security updates to the 4Mi manager and DRC security focal points, and ensure dissemination of information to the enumerators.</li>
<li>Occasionally represent MMC at coordination meetings with DRC teams or humanitarian partners working on Libya;</li>
<li>Communicate on MMC’s activities to DRC programme teams;</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Research</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Occasionally, contribute to the design of qualitative and quantitative questionnaires, conduct fieldwork and contributes to data analysis and report writing;</li>
<li>Stay up-to-date on the latest mixed migration research in Libya;</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Other</strong></p>
<p>Any additional tasks in support of the 4Mi project.</p>
<p><strong>About you</strong></p>
<p>To be successful in this role we expect you to have at least 2 years of experience working in data collection, collecting surveys, or other research activities. Moreover, we expect the following:</p>
<ul>
<li>Demonstrated knowledge and understanding of mixed migration issues, particularly within the Libyan context;</li>
<li>Outstanding communication skills with enumerators of various nationalities and language groups</li>
<li>Proficiency in IT systems, including android-based applications;</li>
<li>Outstanding organizational skills;</li>
<li>Excellent ability to work under minimal supervision and strong problem-solving skills;</li>
<li>Enthusiastic about learning, excellent interpersonal and communication skills;</li>
<li>Strong verbal and written communication.</li>
<li>Sensitivity to issues affecting refugees and migrants in Libya</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Education</strong>: (include certificates, licenses etc.)</p>
<p>Preferably Master’s degree in a relevant field, including but not limited to research methods, international development, migration studies or business administration.</p>
<p><strong>Languages</strong>:  (indicate fluency level)</p>
<ul>
<li>Written and verbal fluency in English and Arabic;</li>
<li>Professional proficiency of French is an asset.</li>
</ul>
<p>In this position, you are expected to demonstrate DRC’ five core competencies:</p>
<p><strong>Striving for excellence: </strong>You focus on reaching results while ensuring an efficient process.</p>
<p><strong>Collaborating:</strong> You involve relevant parties and encourage feedback.</p>
<p><strong>Taking the lead:</strong> You take ownership and initiative while aiming for innovation.</p>
<p><strong>Communicating:</strong> You listen and speak effectively and honestly.</p>
<p><strong>Demonstrating integrity:</strong> You uphold and promote the highest standards of ethical and professional conduct in relation to our values and Code of Conduct, including safeguarding against sexual exploitation, abuse and harassment.</p>
<p><strong>We offer</strong></p>
<p>Contract length: 6 months</p>
<p>Band: G non-management</p>
<p>Designation of Duty Station: Non-family Duty Station</p>
<p><strong>Start date: 13 March 2022</strong></p>
<p>Salary and conditions will be in accordance with Danish Refugee Council’s Terms of Employment for Expatriates; please refer to <a target="_blank" rel="noopener">drc.ngo under Vacancies</a>.</p>
<p><strong>Application process</strong></p>
<p>All applicants must upload to the DRC website (all in English) a cover letter and an updated CV (no longer than four pages). <strong>A</strong><strong>pplications sent by email will not be considered.</strong> Shortlisted candidates will be asked to sit for an interview.</p>
<p>Closing date for applications: 17 February 2022.</p>
</div>
</div>
<section class="narrow">
<div class="editor-content">
<p><strong>DRC as an employer</strong><br />
By working in DRC, you will be joining a global workforce of around 8000 employees in 40 countries. We pride ourselves on our:</p>
<ul>
<li>Professionalism, impact &amp; expertise</li>
<li>Humanitarian approach &amp; the work we do</li>
<li>Purpose, meaningfulness &amp; own contribution</li>
<li>Culture, values &amp; strong leadership</li>
<li>Fair compensation &amp; continuous development</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Providing equal opportunities<br />
</strong>We are committed to creating an inclusive and positive work environment based on mutual respect for all employees. All applicants are considered for employment without attention to race, age, ability, ethnicity, nationality, religion, gender identity, sexual orientation, marital status, or any other factor. At DRC we celebrate diversity and appreciate our employees for the people they are and their unique skills, backgrounds, and perspectives. We encourage all interested candidates to apply.</p>
<p><strong>Promoting high standards</strong><br />
DRC’s capacity to ensure the protection of and assistance to refugees, IDP’s and other persons of concern depends on the ability of our staff to uphold and promote the highest standards of ethical and professional conduct in relation DRC’s values and Code of Conduct, including safeguarding against sexual exploitation, abuse and harassment. DRC conducts thorough and comprehensive background checks as part of the recruitment process.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
</div>
</section><p>The post <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly/en/jobs/4mi-coordinator/">4Mi Coordinator</a> first appeared on <a href="https://libyanjobs.ly/en/">Libyanjobs</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
				<company>DRC Libya</company>
		<job_address>Tripoli</job_address>
		<job_category>organization</job_category>
	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>